<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Evening on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-evening/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Evening on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-evening/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Midnight Prayer in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/ab06528mid/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/ab06528mid/en/</guid>
      <description>#Midnight
*O seeker of Truth! If thou desirest that God may open thine eye, thou must supplicate unto God, pray to and commune with Him at midnight, saying:
O Lord, I have turned my face unto Thy kingdom of oneness and am immersed in the sea of Thy mercy. O Lord, enlighten my sight by beholding Thy lights in this dark night, and make me happy by the wine of Thy love in this wonderful age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009HOW in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009how/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009how/en/</guid>
      <description>How can I choose to sleep, O God, my God, when the eyes of them that long for Thee are wakeful because of their separation from Thee; and how can I lie down to rest whilst the souls of Thy lovers are sore vexed in their remoteness from Thy presence? I have committed, O my Lord, my spirit and my entire being into the right hand of Thy might and Thy protection, and I lay my head on my pillow through Thy power, and lift it up according to Thy will and Thy good pleasure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009SER in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009ser/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009ser/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God, my Master, the Goal of my desire! This, Thy servant, seeketh to sleep in the shelter of Thy mercy, and to repose beneath the canopy of Thy grace, imploring Thy care and Thy protection. I beg of Thee, O my Lord, by Thine eye that sleepeth not, to guard mine eyes from beholding aught beside Thee. Strengthen, then, their vision that they may discern Thy signs, and behold the Horizon of Thy Revelation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12480 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12480/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12480/</guid>
      <description>O my God, my Master, the Goal of my desire!
Lo’u Atua e, lo’u Matai, le Sini o lo’u mana’o! O Lau auauna lenei e saili atu ina ia moe i le malu o Lou alofa mutimutivale, ma mapu i lalo ifo o le faapaologa o Lou alofa tunoa, o loo ole atu i Lau tausiga ma Lau puipuiga.
Lo’u Alii e, ou te ole atu ia te Oe i Ou fofoga e le moe, e leoleoina o’u mata mai le vaai atu i se tasi mea vagana Lau Afio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12481 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12481/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12481/</guid>
      <description>How can I choose to sleep, O God, my God
Le Atua e, lo’u Atua, pe faapefea ona ou moe a o loo ala pea mata o i latou o loo naunau ia te Oe ona o le vavaeeseina o i latou mai ia te Oe; pe faapefea ona ou taoto e malolo a o loo mapuitiga loto o Au pele ona o lo latou taumamao mai Lou faatasi mai?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13334 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13334/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13334/</guid>
      <description>Pa fodd y gallaf gysgu, O Dduw, fy Nuw, pan fo llygaid y rhai a hiraethant amdanat yn effro oherwydd eu hymnieulltuaeth oddi wrthyt; a pha fodd y gallaf orwedd i orffwys pan fo eneidiau Dy anwyliaid yn eu pellter oddi wrthyt?
Ymrwymais, O f&amp;rsquo;Arglwydd, f&amp;rsquo;ysbryd a&amp;rsquo;m holl fodolaeth i ddeheulaw Dy nerth a&amp;rsquo;th nodded, a rhof fy mhen ar fy ngobennydd trwy Dy allu, a chodaf ef yn ôl Dy ewyllys a&amp;rsquo;th bleser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13335 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13335/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13335/</guid>
      <description>O fy Arglwydd, rwyf wedi ymddiried fy ysbryd a&amp;rsquo;m holl fodolaeth i ddeheulaw Dy nerth a Dy amddiffyn, a rhoddaf fy mhen ar fy ngobennydd trwy dy rym,a&amp;rsquo;i godi yn ôl Dy ewyllys a Dy fodd daionus Di. Tydi, yn wir,yw&amp;rsquo;r Amddiffynnwr, y Ceidwad,yr Hollalluog, y Mwyaf Grymus.
I have committed, O my Lord, my spirit and my entire being into the right hand of Thy might and Thy protection, and I lay my head on my pillow through Thy power, and lift it up according to Thy will and Thy good-pleasure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
