<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB10275 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab10275/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB10275 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab10275/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10275 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab10275/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab10275/en/</guid>
      <description>Remove not, O Lord, the festal board that hath been spread in Thy Name, and extinguish not the burning flame that hath been kindled by Thine unquenchable fire. Withhold not from flowing that living water of Thine that murmureth with the melody of Thy glory and Thy remembrance, and deprive not Thy servants from the fragrance of Thy sweet savors breathing forth the perfume of Thy love. Lord! Turn the distressing cares of Thy holy ones into ease, their hardship into comfort, their abasement into glory, their sorrow into blissful joy, O Thou that holdest in Thy grasp the reins of all mankind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10275 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab10275/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab10275/es/</guid>
      <description>No retires, oh Señor, la mesa festiva que ha sido puesta en Tu Nombre, y no apagues la llama ardiente prendida por Tu fuego inextinguible. No impidas que fluya esa agua de vida Tuya que susurra la melodía de Tu gloria y Tu recuerdo, y no prives a Tus siervos de la fragancia de Tus delicados aromas que exhalan el perfume de Tu amor. ¡Señor! Convierte las penosas inquietudes de Tus seres santos en tranquilidad, sus fatigas en sosiego, su humillación en gloria, su tristeza en dichosa alegría, oh Tú que sujetas con Tu mano las riendas de toda la humanidad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10275 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab10275/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab10275/nl/</guid>
      <description>Neem, o Heer, de feestdis niet weg die in Uw Naam is gespreid en doof niet de brandende vlam die door Uw onblusbaar vuur is ontstoken. Stuit niet het stromen van Uw levend water dat voortkabbelt met de melodie van Uw heerlijkheid en Uw gedachtenis, en onthoud Uw dienaren niet de welriekendheid van Uw zoete geuren die het parfum van Uw liefde verspreiden. Heer! Verander de kwellende zorgen van Uw heiligen in rust, hun tegenspoed in voorspoed, hun vernedering in heerlijkheid, hun verdriet in zalige vreugde, o Gij die de teugels van de gehele mensheid in Uw greep houdt!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
