<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH09864 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09864/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH09864 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09864/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09864 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09864/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09864/en/</guid>
      <description>Lauded be Thy name, O my God! I entreat Thee by the fragrances of the Raiment of Thy grace which at Thy bidding and in conformity with Thy desire were diffused throughout the entire creation, and by the Daystar of Thy will that hath shone brightly, through the power of Thy might and of Thy sovereignty, above the horizon of Thy mercy, to blot out from my heart all idle fancies and vain imaginings, that with all my affections I may turn unto Thee, O Thou Lord of all mankind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09864 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09864/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09864/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Alabado sea Tu Nombre, oh mi Dios! Te imploro, por las fragancias de la Vestidura de Tu gracia, que fueron esparcidas por toda la creación mediante Tu mandato y en conformidad con Tu deseo, y por el Sol de Tu voluntad, que ha resplandecido mediante la fuerza de Tu poder y Tu soberanía en el horizonte de Tu misericordia, que borres de mi corazón toda ociosa fantasía y vana imaginación, para que me vuelva hacia Ti con todo mi corazón, oh Señor de toda la humanidad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09864 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09864/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09864/pt/</guid>
      <description>Louvado seja o Teu Nome, ó meu Deus! Suplico-Te - pela fragrância das Vestes da Tua graça que, a Teu mando e segundo o Teu desejo, se difundiu entre todos os seres, e pelo Alvorecer da Tua vontade, reluzindo sobre o horizonte da Tua misericórdia, graças ao poder da Tua soberania e grandeza – que apagues do meu coração todas as vãs fantasias e ideias fúteis para que a Ti eu possa dirigir-me com toda a afeição, ó Senhor de todos os homens!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
