<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Healing on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-healing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Healing on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-healing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Long Healing Prayer in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh00870/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh00870/en/</guid>
      <description>##Long Healing Prayer
He is the Healer, the Sufficer, the Helper, the All-Forgiving, the All-Merciful.
I call on Thee O Exalted One, O Faithful One, O Glorious One! Thou the Sufficing, Thou the Healing, Thou the Abiding, O Thou Abiding One!
I call on Thee O Sovereign, O Upraiser, O Judge! Thou the Sufficing, Thou the Healing, Thou the Abiding, O Thou Abiding One!
I call on Thee O Peerless One, O Eternal One, O Single One!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH04475 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh04475/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh04475/en/</guid>
      <description>##For Women
Glory be to Thee, O Lord my God! I beg of Thee by Thy Name through which He Who is Thy Beauty hath been stablished upon the throne of Thy Cause, and by Thy Name through which Thou changest all things, and gatherest together all things, and callest to account all things, and rewardest all things, and preservest all things, and sustainest all things—I beg of Thee to guard this handmaiden who hath fled for refuge to Thee, and hath sought the shelter of Him in Whom Thou Thyself art manifest, and hath put her whole trust and confidence in Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH04990 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh04990/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh04990/en/</guid>
      <description>##For Infants
Thou art He, O my God, through Whose names the sick are healed and the ailing are restored, and the thirsty given drink and the sore vexed are tranquillized, and the wayward are guided, and the abased are exalted, and the poor are enriched, and the ignorant are enlightened, and the gloomy are illumined, and the sorrowful are cheered, and the chilled are warmed, and the downtrodden are raised up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07105 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh07105/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh07105/en/</guid>
      <description>Praised be Thou, O Lord my God! I implore Thee, by Thy Most Great Name through which Thou didst stir up Thy servants and build up Thy cities, and by Thy most excellent titles, and Thy most august attributes, to assist Thy people to turn in the direction of Thy manifold bounties, and set their faces towards the Tabernacle of Thy wisdom. Heal Thou the sicknesses that have assailed the souls on every side, and have deterred them from directing their gaze towards the Paradise that lieth in the shelter of Thy shadowing Name, which Thou didst ordain to be the King of all names unto all who are in heaven and all who are on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07721 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh07721/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh07721/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O Lord my God! I implore Thee by Thy Name, through which Thou didst lift up the ensigns of Thy guidance, and didst shed the radiance of Thy loving-kindness, and didst reveal the sovereignty of Thy Lordship; through which the lamp of Thy names hath appeared within the niche of Thine attributes, and He Who is the Tabernacle of Thy unity and the Manifestation of detachment hath shone forth; through which the ways of Thy guidance were made known, and the paths of Thy good pleasure were marked out; through which the foundations of error have been made to tremble, and the signs of wickedness have been abolished; through which the fountains of wisdom have burst forth, and the heavenly table hath been sent down; through which Thou didst preserve Thy servants and didst vouchsafe Thy healing; through which Thou didst show forth Thy tender mercies unto Thy servants and revealedst Thy forgiveness amidst Thy creatures—I implore Thee to keep safe him who hath held fast and returned unto Thee, and clung to Thy mercy, and seized the hem of Thy loving providence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08013 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh08013/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh08013/en/</guid>
      <description>O God my God! I beg of Thee by the ocean of Thy healing, and by the splendors of the Daystar of Thy grace, and by Thy Name through which Thou didst subdue Thy servants, and by the pervasive power of Thy most exalted Word and the potency of Thy most august Pen, and by Thy mercy that hath preceded the creation of all who are in heaven and on earth, to purge me with the waters of Thy bounty from every affliction and disorder, and from all weakness and feebleness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12028 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12028/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12028/</guid>
      <description>*Thy Name is my healing O my God!
Lo’u Atua e, o Lou suafa o lo’u faamaloloina lea, ma le manatua o Lau Afio o la’u vaifofo lea. O le fa’alatalata atu ia te Oe o lo’u fa’amoemoega lea, ma le alofa ia te Oe o lo’u soatau lea. O le alofa mutimutivale o Lau Afio ia te a’u o lo’u fa’amalologa lea ma lo’u fesoasoani i lenei lalolagi ma le olaga atalī.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12486 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12486/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12486/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! I beg of Thee by the ocean of Thy healing,…
Le Atua e, lou Atua! Ou te ole atu ia te Oe ona o le vasa o Lau fa’amalologa, ma pupula o le Fetu Ao o Lou Alofa tunoa, ma, ona o Lou Suafa na pulea ai e Oe Au auauna, ma le mana malosi o Lau Afioga aupito silisili, atoa ma le mata’utia o Lau Peni mamalu faasilisiliina, ae maise Lou alofa mutimutivale sa faamuamuaina i le foafoaga o mea uma o lo’o i le lagi ma luga o le lalolagi, ia faamāmāina a’u i vai o Lau foa’ialofa mai so o se puapuagā ma se faalētonu , atoa fo’i ma vaivaiga uma ma le lē lavā.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12952 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12952/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12952/</guid>
      <description>O God bilong mi. Nem bilong Yu i helpim mi long winim sik. Sapos mi tingim Yu, dispela tingting i olsem marasin bilong mi. Sapos mi stap klostu long Yu, orait, bai mi wetim ol gutpela samting i kamap. Mi laikim tumas Yu na dispela lav i stap olsem poroman bilong mi. Marimari bilong Yu i save rausim ol sik bilong mi na helpim mi long dispela taim we mi stap long dispela graun na long laip bihain wantaim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12953 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12953/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12953/</guid>
      <description>O God, O God bilong mi! Mi askim strong long Yu long solwara bilong Yu bilong winim sik. Na long bikpela lait bilong San bilong marimari bilong Yu. Na long Nem bilong Yu, em Nem i save bosim ol wokman bilong Yu. Na long strongpela pawa bilong Tok bilong Yu, em Tok i stap antap tru long olgeta samting. Na long pawa bilong Ing na Pen bilong Yu, em Pen i gutpela tru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12954 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12954/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12954/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! I beg of Thee by the ocean of Thy healing, and by the splendors of the Day-Star of Thy grace, and by Thy Name through which Thou didst subdue Thy servants, and by the pervasive power of Thy most exalted Word and the potency of Thy most august Pen, and by Thy mercy that hath preceded the creation of all who are in heaven and on earth, to purge me with the waters of Thy bounty from every affliction and disorder, and from all weakness and feebleness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13352 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13352/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13352/</guid>
      <description>Dy Enw yw fy iachâd, O fy Nuw, a choffadwriaeth amdanat yw fy meddyginiaeth. Agosrwydd atat yw fy ngobaith, a chariad atat yw fy nghydymaith. Dy drugaredd tuag ataf fi yw iachâd a&amp;rsquo;m cymorth yn y byd hwn a&amp;rsquo;r byd i ddod. Tydi, yn wir, wyt yr Holl Haelionus, yr Holl Wybodol, yr Holl-Ddoeth.
Thy name is my healing, O my God, and remembrance of Thee is my remedy. Nearness to Thee is my hope, and love for Thee is my companion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thy name is my healing in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/en/</guid>
      <description>Thy name is my healing, O my God, and remembrance of Thee is my remedy. Nearness to Thee is my hope, and love for Thee is my companion. Thy mercy to me is my healing and my succor in both this world and the world to come. Thou, verily, art the All-Bountiful, the All-Knowing, the All-Wise.
(Source category: Healing) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 257)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
