<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Spiritual Growth on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-spiritual-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Spiritual Growth on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-spiritual-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00044PRO in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00044pro/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00044pro/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou Provider! Thou hast breathed over the friends in the West the sweet fragrance of the Holy Spirit, and with the light of divine guidance Thou hast lit up the western sky. Thou hast made those who were once remote to draw near unto Thyself; Thou hast turned strangers into loving friends; Thou hast awakened those who slept; Thou hast made the heedless mindful.
O Thou Provider! Assist Thou these noble friends to win Thy good pleasure, and make them well wishers of stranger and friend alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00044PRO in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00044pro/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00044pro/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij Verzorger! Gij hebt de zoete geur van de Heilige Geest over de vrienden in het Westen geademd en met het licht van goddelijke leiding de westelijke hemel verlicht. Gij hebt hen die ooit veraf waren nader tot Uzelf gebracht; Gij hebt vreemden in liefdevolle vrienden veranderd; Gij hebt de slapenden doen ontwaken; Gij hebt de achtelozen opmerkzaam gemaakt. O Gij Verzorger! Sta deze nobele vrienden bij om Uw welbehagen te verwerven en laat hen mensen worden die het goed voor hebben met zowel vriend als vreemdeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00083RAD in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00083rad/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00083rad/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! This is thy radiant servant, Thy spiritual thrall, who hath drawn nigh unto Thee and approached Thy presence. He hath turned his face unto Thine, acknowledging Thy oneness, confessing Thy singleness, and he hath called out in Thy name among the nations, and led the people to the streaming waters of Thy mercy, O Thou Most generous Lord! To those who asked He hath given to drink from the cup of guidance that brimmeth over with the wine of Thy measureless grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00128FEE in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00128fee/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00128fee/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! These are Thy feeble servants; they are Thy loyal bondsmen and Thy handmaidens, who have bowed themselves down before Thine exalted Utterance and humbled themselves at Thy Threshold of light, and borne witness to Thy oneness through which the Sun hath been made to shine in midday splendor. They have listened to the summons Thou didst raise from out Thy hidden Realm, and with hearts quivering with love and rapture, they have responded to Thy call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00128FEE in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00128fee/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00128fee/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh Dios, mi Dios! Estos son Tus débiles siervos; son Tus esclavos leales y Tus siervas, que se han inclinado ante Tu exaltada Palabra y se han mostrado humildes ante Tu Umbral de luz, y han dado testimonio de Tu unicidad, mediante la cual se ha hecho brillar el Sol en su esplendor meridiano. Han escuchado el llamamiento que elevaste desde Tu Dominio oculto y, con corazones estremecidos de amor y embeleso, han respondido a Tu llamado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00128FEE in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00128fee/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00128fee/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Deus, meu Deus! Estes são os Teus servos fracos, os Teus leais escravos e as Tuas servas que se curvaram diante das Tuas Palavras excelsas e se humilharam no Teu Limiar de luz, e deram testemunho da Tua unicidade, através da qual se fez brilhar o sol em esplendor meridiano. Escutaram o chamado que levantaste do Teu Reino Oculto e, com corações trémulos de amor e êxtase, responderam à Tua convocação.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02326 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/en/</guid>
      <description>He is God! O God, my God! These are servants attracted in Thy days by the fragrances of Thy holiness, enkindled with the flame burning in Thy holy tree, responding to Thy voice, uttering Thy praise, awakened by Thy breeze, stirred by Thy sweet savors, beholding Thy signs, understanding Thy Revelation and assured of Thy loving-kindness. Their eyes, O Lord, are fixed upon Thy kingdom of effulgent glory and their faces turned toward Thy dominion on high, their hearts beating with the love of Thy radiant and glorious beauty, their souls consumed with the flame of Thy love, O Lord of this world and the world hereafter, their lives seething with the ardor of their longing for Thee, and their tears poured forth for Thy sake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02326 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/nl/</guid>
      <description>Hij is God! O God, mijn God! Dit zijn dienaren die in Uw dagen bekoord zijn door de geuren van Uw heiligheid, die aangestoken zijn door de vlam die brandt in Uw heilige boom, gehoor geven aan Uw stem, Uw lof uiten, gewekt zijn door Uw bries, geroerd zijn door Uw zoete geuren, Uw tekenen aanschouwen, Uw verzen begrijpen, Uw woorden beluisteren, in Uw Openbaring geloven en zeker zijn van Uw goedertierenheid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02326 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ele é Deus! Ó Deus, meu Deus! Estes são servos atraídos em Teus dias pelo perfume da Tua santidade, acesos com a chama que resplandece em Tua santa árvore, atendendo à Tua voz, expressando-Te louvor, despertados pela Tua brisa, animados pelas Tuas doces fragrâncias, contemplando os Teus sinais, compreendendo os Teus versículos, escutando as Tuas palavras, acreditando na Tua Revelação e confiantes da Tua misericórdia. Os seus olhos, ó Senhor, fitam o Teu reino de fulgente glória, e as suas faces volvem-se para o Teu domínio nas alturas; os seus corações pulsam de amor pela Tua beleza radiante e gloriosa; as suas almas consomem-se com a chama do Teu amor, ó Senhor deste mundo e do vindouro, as suas vidas fervem com o ardor da sua ânsia por Ti, e as suas lágrimas vertem por Tua causa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB07709CON in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O my God! Glory be unto Thee for that Thou hast confirmed me to the confession of Thy oneness, attracted me unto the word of Thy singleness, enkindled me by the fire of Thy love, and occupied me with Thy mention and the service of Thy friends and maidservants.
O Lord, help me to be meek and lowly, and strengthen me in severing myself from all things and in holding to the hem of the garment of Thy glory, so that my heart may be filled with Thy love and leave no space for love of the world and attachment to its qualities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB07709CON in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh mi Dios, oh mi Dios! Gloria a Ti por cuanto me has confirmado para reconocer Tu unicidad, me has atraído hacia la palabra de Tu singularidad, me has encendido con el fuego de Tu amor y has hecho que me ocupe en Tu mención y en el servicio a Tus amigos y siervas. Oh Señor, ayúdame a ser sumiso y humilde, y fortaléceme para que pueda desligarme de todas las cosas y asirme al borde de la vestidura de Tu gloria, para que mi corazón se llene con Tu amor y no deje lugar para el amor al mundo y el apego a sus cualidades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB07709CON in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/nl/</guid>
      <description>O mijn God! O mijn God! Glorie zij U daar Gij mij hebt bevestigd in het belijden van Uw één-zijn, mij hebt aangetrokken tot het woord van Uw enig-zijn, in vlam hebt gezet met het vuur van Uw liefde en mij vervuld hebt van het U noemen en het dienen van Uw vrienden en dienaressen. O Heer, help mij deemoedig en nederig te zijn en sterk mij om mijzelf los te maken van alle dingen en mij vast te houden aan de zoom van de mantel van Uw glorie, zodat mijn hart vervuld mag worden van Uw liefde en er geen ruimte meer is voor liefde voor de wereld en gehechtheid aan haar eigenschappen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09139 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O my God! This, Thy servant, hath advanced towards Thee, is passionately wandering in the desert of Thy love, walking in the path of Thy service, anticipating Thy favors, hoping for Thy bounty, relying upon Thy kingdom, and intoxicated by the wine of Thy gift. O my God! Increase the fervor of his affection for Thee, the constancy of his praise of Thee, and the ardor of his love for Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09139 in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/fr/</guid>
      <description>Ô mon Dieu, ô mon Dieu, voici que ton serviteur s’avance vers toi et qu’il parcourt avec passion le désert de ton amour, suivant la voie de ton service, dans l’attente de tes faveurs et dans l’espoir de ta générosité, confiant en ton royaume et grisé du vin de tes bienfaits. Ô mon Dieu, accrois sa piété, sa constance à te célébrer et l’ardeur de son amour. En vérité, tu es le Très-Généreux, le Seigneur de toute grâce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09139 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/nl/</guid>
      <description>O mijn God! O mijn God! Deze dienaar is nader tot U gekomen, zwerft hartstochtelijk door de woestijn van Uw liefde, bewandelt het pad van dienstbaarheid aan U, ziet uit naar Uw gunsten, hoopt op Uw gaven, vertrouwt op Uw koninkrijk en is bedwelmd door de wijn van Uw gift. O mijn God! Vermeerder het vuur van zijn genegenheid voor U, de standvastigheid van zijn lof voor U en het vuur van zijn liefde voor U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09139 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó meu Deus! ó meu Deus! Este Teu servo apressou-se na Tua direção, trilhando o caminho em Teu serviço, antecipando os Teus favores, esperando as Tuas bênçãos, confiando no Teu reino, e intoxicado pelo vinho do Teu favor. Ó meu Deus! Aumenta o fervor da sua afeição por Ti, a constância do seu louvor por Ti, e o ardor do seu amor por Ti. Verdadeiramente, Tu és o Mais Generoso, o Senhor de graça copiosa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB11281 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab11281/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab11281/en/</guid>
      <description>O my Lord! O my Lord! This is a lamp lighted by the fire of Thy love and ablaze with the flame which is ignited in the tree of Thy mercy. O my Lord! Increase his enkindlement, heat and flame, with the fire which is kindled in the Sinai of Thy Manifestation. Verily, Thou art the Confirmer, the Assister, the Powerful, the Generous, the Loving.
(Source category: Spiritual Growth) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 424)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB11281 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab11281/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab11281/nl/</guid>
      <description>O mijn Heer! O mijn Heer! Dit is een lamp die is aangestoken met het vuur van Uw liefde en brandt met de vlam die in de boom van Uw barmhartigheid is ontstoken. O mijn Heer! Vergroot zijn ontvlambaarheid, hitte en vuur met de vlam die in de Sinaï van Uw Manifestatie is ontstoken. Waarlijk, Gij zijt de Bekrachtiger, de Helper, de Krachtige, de Edelmoedige, de Liefderijke.
(Source category: Geestelijke groei) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00374 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bb00374/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bb00374/en/</guid>
      <description>Vouchsafe unto me, O my God, the full measure of Thy love and Thy good-pleasure, and through the attractions of Thy resplendent light enrapture our hearts, O Thou Who art the Supreme Evidence and the All-Glorified. Send down upon me, as a token of Thy grace, Thy vitalizing breezes, throughout the daytime and in the night season, O Lord of bounty. No deed have I done, O my God, to merit beholding Thy face, and I know of a certainty that were I to live as long as the world lasts I would fail to accomplish any deed such as to deserve this favor, inasmuch as the station of a servant shall ever fall short of access to Thy holy precincts, unless Thy bounty should reach me and Thy tender mercy pervade me and Thy loving-kindness encompass me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00374 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bb00374/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bb00374/es/</guid>
      <description>Concédeme, oh mi Dios, la plenitud de Tu amor y Tu complacencia, y, con la atracción de Tu luz resplandeciente, extasía nuestros corazones, oh Tú que eres la Evidencia Suprema y el Todoglorificado. Como señal de Tu gracia, sopla sobre mí Tus brisas vivificadoras durante el día y por la noche, oh Señor de munificencia. Ninguna acción he realizado, oh mi Dios, que me haga merecedor de contemplar Tu rostro, y sé de cierto que, aunque viviera tanto tiempo como dure el mundo, no lograría realizar acción alguna que mereciera este favor, pues la condición de un siervo jamás le permitirá acceder a Tus sagrados recintos, a no ser que Tu generosidad me alcance y Tu tierna misericordia me inunde, y Tu bondad me circunde.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00531TRA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00531tra/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00531tra/en/</guid>
      <description>I beseech Thee, O my God, by all the transcendent glory of Thy Name, to clothe Thy loved ones in the robe of justice and to illumine their beings with the light of trustworthiness. Thou art the One that hath power to do as He pleaseth and Who holdeth within His grasp the reins of all things, visible and invisible.
(Source category: Spiritual Growth) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 309)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00531TRA in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00531tra/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00531tra/es/</guid>
      <description>Te imploro, oh mi Dios, por toda la gloria trascendente de Tu Nombre, que atavíes a Tus amados con el manto de la justicia e ilumines su ser con la luz de la honradez. Tú eres Quien tiene poder de hacer lo que Le plazca y Quien sujeta con Su mano las riendas de todas las cosas, visibles e invisibles.
(Source category: Cualidades espirituales) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 11489)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00531TRA in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00531tra/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00531tra/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik smeek U, o mijn God, bij de alles te boven gaande glorie van Uw Naam, Uw geliefden te kleden met de mantel van rechtvaardigheid en hun wezen te verlichten met het licht van betrouwbaarheid. Gij zijt Degeen die de macht heeft te doen naar Zijn behagen en Degeen die de teugels aller dingen, zichtbaar en onzichtbaar, in Zijn greep houdt.
(Source category: Geestelijke groei) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9570)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00554 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00554/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00554/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God, the God of bounty and mercy! Thou art that King by Whose commanding word the whole creation hath been called into being; and Thou art that All-Bountiful One the doings of Whose servants have never hindered Him from showing forth His grace, nor have they frustrated the revelations of His bounty. Suffer this servant, I beseech Thee, to attain unto that which is the cause of his salvation in every world of Thy worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00554 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00554/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00554/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Dio, la Dio de donacado kaj kompato! Vi estas la Reĝo, per Kies ordona vorto la tuta kreitaro estis kreita; kaj Vi estas tiu Ĉion-donanto, la faroj de Kies servantoj neniam malebligas al Li montri Sian favoron, nek nuligas la signojn de Lia donacemo. Permesu al ĉi tiu servanto, mi petegas al Vi, atingi tion, kio estas la kaŭzo de lia saviĝo en ĉiu mondo el Viaj mondoj. Vere, Vi estas la Ĉio-pova, la Plej Potenca, la Ĉio-scia, la Plej-saĝa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00554 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00554/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh00554/nl/</guid>
      <description>O mijn God, de God van milddadigheid en erbarmen! Gij zijt de Koning door Wiens gebiedend Woord de gehele schepping tot bestaan is gewekt, en Gij zijt de Almilddadige die door de daden van Zijn dienaren nimmer is weerhouden Zijn genade te betonen, noch hebben deze de openbaring van Zijn milddadigheid kunnen tegenhouden. Ik smeek U, laat deze dienaar datgene bereiken wat in elk van Uw werelden tot zijn verlossing zal leiden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03562 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh03562/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh03562/en/</guid>
      <description>He is the prayer-hearing, prayer-answering God! By Thy glory, O Beloved One, Thou giver of light to the world! The flames of separation have consumed me, and my waywardness hath melted my heart within me. I ask of Thee, by Thy Most Great Name, O Thou the Desire of the world and the Well-Beloved of mankind, to grant that the breeze of Thine inspiration may sustain my soul, that Thy wondrous voice may reach my ear, that my eyes may behold Thy signs and Thy light as revealed in the manifestations of Thy names and Thine attributes, O Thou within Whose grasp are all things!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03562 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh03562/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh03562/nl/</guid>
      <description>Hij is de God die gebeden verhoort en beantwoordt! Bij Uw glorie, o Geliefde, Gij die de wereld licht schenkt! Het vuur van scheiding verslindt mij, en mijn weerspannigheid verteert mijn hart. Ik vraag U, bij Uw Allergrootste Naam, o Gij het Verlangen der wereld en de Welbeminde der mensheid, te geven dat de bries van Uw bezieling mijn ziel steunt, opdat Uw wondere stem mijn oor bereikt en mijn oog Uw tekenen en Uw licht aanschouwt zoals dat is onthuld in de openbaring van Uw Namen en Uw eigenschappen, o Gij in Wiens greep alle dingen liggen!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH04421HEA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh04421hea/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh04421hea/en/</guid>
      <description>Create in me a pure heart, O my God, and renew a tranquil conscience within me, O my Hope! Through the spirit of power confirm Thou me in Thy Cause, O my Best-Beloved, and by the light of Thy glory reveal unto me Thy path, O Thou the Goal of my desire! Through the power of Thy transcendent might lift me up unto the heaven of Thy holiness, O Source of my being, and by the breezes of Thine eternity gladden me, O Thou Who art my God!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH04421HEA in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh04421hea/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh04421hea/eo/</guid>
      <description>Kreu en mi puran koron, ho mia Dio, kaj renovigu en mi trankvilan konsciencon, ho mia Espero! Per la spirito de potenco firmigu min en Via Kredo, ho mia Plejamata, kaj per la lumo de Via gloro revelaciu al mi Vian vojon, ho Vi, la Celo de mia deziro! Per la potenco de Via transcenda forto levu min en la ĉielon de Via sankteco, ho Fonto de mia ekzisto, kaj per la brizoj de Via eterneco ĝojigu min, ho Vi, Kiu estas mia Dio!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH04421HEA in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh04421hea/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh04421hea/fy/</guid>
      <description>Skep yn my in suver hert, o myn God, en fernij yn my in rêstich gewisse, o myn Hoop! Bekrêftigje my yn Jo Saak troch de geast fan macht, o myn Meast-Dierbere, en iepenbierje my Jo wei troch it ljocht fan Jo gloarje, o Jo, Doel fan myn langstme! Ferhef my ta de himel fan Jo hillichheid troch de krêft fan Jo alles oertreffende macht, o Boarne fan myn wêzen, en ferbliidzje my troch de amme fan Jo ivichheid, o Jo, Dy&amp;rsquo;t myn God binne!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH04421HEA in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh04421hea/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh04421hea/nl/</guid>
      <description>Schep in mij een zuiver hart, o mijn God, en vernieuw in mij een rustig geweten, o mijn Hoop! Bekrachtig mij in Uw Zaak door de geest van macht, o mijn Meestgeliefde, en toon mij Uw weg door het licht van Uw heerlijkheid, o Gij het doel van mijn verlangen! Verhef mij tot de hemel van Uw heiligheid door de kracht van Uw alles te boven gaande macht, o Bron van mijn wezen, en verblijd mij door de ademtocht van Uw eeuwigheid, o Gij die mijn God zijt!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH05543 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh05543/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh05543/en/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! I give Thee thanks inasmuch as Thou hast called me into being in Thy days, and infused into me Thy love and Thy knowledge. I beseech Thee, by Thy name whereby the goodly pearls of Thy wisdom and Thine utterance were brought forth out of the treasuries of the hearts of such of Thy servants as are nigh unto Thee, and through which the Daystar of Thy name, the Compassionate, hath shed its radiance upon all that are in Thy heaven and on Thy earth, to supply me, by Thy grace and bounty, with Thy wondrous and hidden bounties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH06026 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/en/</guid>
      <description>He is the Gracious, the All-Bountiful!
O God, my God! Thy call hath attracted me, and the voice of Thy Pen of Glory awakened me. The stream of Thy holy utterance hath enraptured me, and the wine of Thine inspiration entranced me. Thou seest me, O Lord, detached from all things but Thee, clinging to the cord of Thy bounty and craving the wonders of Thy grace. I ask Thee, by the eternal billows of Thy loving-kindness and the shining lights of Thy tender care and favor, to grant that which shall draw me nigh unto Thee and make me rich in Thy wealth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH06026 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/nl/</guid>
      <description>Hij is de Genadige, de Almilddadige! O God, mijn God! Uw roep trok mij aan en de stem van Uw Pen van heerlijkheid heeft mij gewekt. De stroom van Uw heilige woorden heeft mij betoverd en de wijn van Uw bezieling heeft mij in vervoering gebracht. Gij ziet mij, o Heer, onthecht van alles buiten U, mij vastklemmend aan het koord van Uw milddadigheid en hunkerend naar de wonderen van Uw genade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH06026 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ele é o Bondoso, o Generosíssimo! Ó Deus, meu Deus! O Teu chamado atraiu-me e a voz da Tua Pena de Glória despertou-me. O fluxo das Tuas santas palavras enlevou-me, e com o vinho da Tua inspiração extasiei-me. Tu me vês, ó Senhor, desprendido de tudo, menos de Ti, agarrado à corda das Tuas dádivas e desejoso das maravilhas da Tua graça. Peço-Te, pelas ondas eternas da Tua misericórdia e pelas luzes cintilantes da Tua ternura e dos Teus favores – concede o que me aproxime de Ti e me torne rico em Tua riqueza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07426FOO in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/en/</guid>
      <description>O my Lord! Make Thy beauty to be my food, and Thy presence my drink, and Thy pleasure my hope, and praise of Thee my action, and remembrance of Thee my companion, and the power of Thy sovereignty my succorer, and Thy habitation my home, and my dwelling-place the seat Thou hast sanctified from the limitations imposed upon them who are shut out as by a veil from Thee. Thou art, verily, the Almighty, the All-Glorious, the Most Powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07426FOO in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Eternulo! Faru Vian belecon mia mangaĵo kaj Vian ĉeeston mia trinkaĵo, kaj Vian plaĉon mia espero, kaj gloradon al Vi mia agado, kaj rememoron pri Vi mia akompananto, kaj la potencon de Via suvereneco mia helpo, kaj Vian restadejon mia hejmo, kaj mian vivejon la loko, kiun Vi sanktigis de la limoj metitaj al tiuj, kiuj kvazaŭ per vualo estas forfermitaj de Vi. Vi estas vere la Ĉio-pova, la Plejglora, la Plejpotenca.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07426FOO in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/it/</guid>
      <description>O mio Signore! Fa’ che la Tua bellezza sia il mio cibo e la Tua presenza il mio nèttare, e il Tuo compiacimento la mia speranza. e la lode di Te il mio agire, e il ricordo di Te il mio compagno, e la potenza della Tua sovranità il mio soccorso, e la Tua dimora la mia casa, e la mia dimora il seggio che Tu hai purificato dalle limitazioni imposte a coloro che sono separati da Te come da un velo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07780 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07780/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07780/en/</guid>
      <description>Lauded be Thy Name, O Lord my God! I am Thy servant who hath laid hold on the cord of Thy tender mercies, and clung to the hem of Thy bounteousness. I entreat Thee by Thy name whereby Thou hast subjected all created things, both visible and invisible, and through which the breath that is life indeed was wafted over the entire creation, to strengthen me by Thy power which hath encompassed the heavens and the earth, and to guard me from all sickness and tribulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07780 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07780/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07780/pt/</guid>
      <description>Louvado seja o Teu nome, ó Senhor meu Deus! Sou o Teu servo, que se segurou à corda da Tua benévola compaixão e à fímbria das vestes da Tua generosidade. Suplico-Te - pelo Teu nome, através do qual dominaste todas as coisas criadas visíveis e invisíveis, e insuflaste em toda a criação a verdadeira vida – fortalece-me com o Teu poder que envolveu os céus e a terra e guarda-me de toda a enfermidade e tribulação.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08594 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh08594/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh08594/en/</guid>
      <description>Praised be Thou, O Lord my God! I bear witness that from eternity Thou wert exalted in Thy transcendent majesty and might, and wilt to eternity abide in Thy surpassing power and glory. None in the kingdoms of earth and heaven can frustrate Thy purpose; none throughout the realms of revelation and of creation can prevail against Thee. At Thy command Thou doest what Thou willest, and by the power of Thy sovereignty Thou rulest as Thou pleasest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08594 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh08594/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh08594/pt/</guid>
      <description>Louvado sejas, ó Senhor meu Deus! Dou testemunho de que Tu, desde toda a eternidade, estás elevado em Tua transcendente majestade e grandeza e por toda a eternidade permanecerás em Teu supremo poder e glória. Nos reinos da terra como do céu não há quem possa frustrar o Teu desígnio; nem existe, em todos os domínios da revelação e da criação, quem possa prevalecer contra Ti. Segundo a Tua Vontade, realizas o que desejas e, através do poder da Tua soberania, reges como Te apraz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08824 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh08824/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh08824/en/</guid>
      <description>Magnified, O Lord my God, be Thy Name, whereby the trees of the garden of Thy Revelation have been clad with verdure, and been made to yield the fruits of holiness during this Springtime when the sweet savors of Thy favors and blessings have been wafted over all things, and caused them to bring forth whatsoever had been preordained for them in the Kingdom of Thine irrevocable decree and the Heaven of Thine immutable purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
