<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH02524 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh02524/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH02524 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh02524/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH02524 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/bh02524/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/bh02524/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory to Thee, O my God! But for the tribulations which are sustained in Thy path, how could Thy true lovers be recognized; and were it not for the trials which are borne for love of Thee, how could the station of such as yearn for Thee be revealed? Thy might beareth me witness! The companions of all who adore Thee are the tears they shed, and the comforters of such as seek Thee are the groans they utter, and the food of them who haste to meet Thee is the fragments of their broken hearts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH02524 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/bh02524/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/bh02524/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Gloria sea a Ti, oh mi Dios! Si no fuera por las tribulaciones sufridas en Tu camino, ¿cómo podría reconocerse a quienes verdaderamente Te aman? Y, si no fuera por las pruebas sufridas por amor a Ti, ¿cómo podría revelarse la posición de aquellos que Te anhelan? ¡Tu poder me lo atestigua! Las lágrimas que derraman son la compañía de todos cuantos Te adoran, y los lamentos que profieren, el consuelo de los que Te buscan, y los pedazos de sus corazones rotos, el alimento de los que se apresuran por encontrarte.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
