<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Children on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-children/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Children on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-children/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB04004BAB in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04004bab/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04004bab/en/</guid>
      <description>##Infants
O God! Rear this little babe in the bosom of Thy love, and give it milk from the breast of Thy Providence. Cultivate this fresh plant in the rose garden of Thy love and aid it to grow through the showers of Thy bounty. Make it a child of the kingdom, and lead it to Thy heavenly realm. Thou art powerful and kind, and Thou art the Bestower, the Generous, the Lord of surpassing bounty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB04004BAB in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04004bab/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04004bab/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Dio! Eduku ĉi tiun malgrandan bebon en la sino de Via amo kaj donu al ĝi lakton el la mamo de Via Providenco. Kultivu ĉi freŝan planton en la rozĝardeno de Via amo kaj helpu ĝin kreski per la pluvo de Via donacemo. Faru ĝin infano de la regno kaj gvidu ĝin al Via ĉiela reĝlando. Vi estas potenca kaj bona, kaj Vi estas la Donacanto, la Grandanima, la Sinjoro de nesuperebla donacemo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB04004BAB in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04004bab/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04004bab/it/</guid>
      <description>O Dio! Alleva questo pargoletto al seno del Tuo amore e allattalo al petto della Tua Provvidenza. Coltiva questa tenera pianta nel roseto del Tuo amore e aiutala a crescere con le piogge della Tua generosità. Fanne un figlio del Regno e guidalo al Tuo Celeste Reame. Tu sei potente e benigno. Tu sei l’Elargitore, il Generoso, il Signore di insorpassata munificenza. ‘Abdu’l-Bahá
(Source category: Bambini) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 7804)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB04427LMP in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04427lmp/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04427lmp/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, guide me, protect me, make of me a shining lamp and a brilliant star. Thou art the Mighty and the Powerful.
(Source category: Children) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 193)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB04427LMP in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04427lmp/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04427lmp/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Dio! Gvidu min, protektu min, faru min lumanta lampo kaj stelo brila. Vi estas la Pova kaj la Potenca.
(Source category: Infanoj kaj Junuloj) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 4319)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB04427LMP in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04427lmp/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04427lmp/fy/</guid>
      <description>O God! Lied my en hoedzje my; ferljochtsje de lampe fan myn hert en meitsje my ta in strieljende stjer. Jo binne de Machtige en de Krêftige.
(Source category: Bern) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 6018)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB04427LMP in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04427lmp/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04427lmp/nl/</guid>
      <description>O God, leid mij, bescherm mij, maak mij een stralende lamp en een schitterende ster. Gij zijt de Machtige en de Krachtige.
(Source category: Kinderen) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9616)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB04427LMP in Papiamentu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04427lmp/pap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab04427lmp/pap/</guid>
      <description>*Oh, God guide me
O Dios, guiami, protehami, iluminá e lampi di mi kurason, i hasimi un strea briyante. Bo ta esun poderoso i fuerte.
(Source category: Children) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 6873)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB08693 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab08693/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab08693/en/</guid>
      <description>O Peerless Lord! Be Thou a shelter for this poor child and a kind and forgiving Master unto this erring and unhappy soul. O Lord! Though we are but worthless plants, yet we belong to Thy garden of roses. Though saplings without leaves and blossoms, yet we are a part of Thine orchard. Nurture this plant then through the outpourings of the clouds of Thy tender mercy and quicken and refresh this sapling through the reviving breath of Thy spiritual springtime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09040 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09040/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09040/en/</guid>
      <description>O my Lord! O my Lord! I am a child of tender years. Nourish me from the breast of Thy mercy, train me in the bosom of Thy love, educate me in the school of Thy guidance and develop me under the shadow of Thy bounty. Deliver me from darkness, make me a brilliant light; free me from unhappiness, make me a flower of the rose garden; suffer me to become a servant of Thy threshold and confer upon me the disposition and nature of the righteous; make me a cause of bounty to the human world, and crown my head with the diadem of eternal life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09794CHI in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! I am a child; enable me to grow beneath the shadow of Thy loving-kindness. I am a tender plant; cause me to be nurtured through the outpourings of the clouds of Thy bounty. I am a sapling of the garden of love; make me into a fruitful tree. Thou art the Mighty and the Powerful, and Thou art the All-Loving, the All-Knowing, the All-Seeing.
(Source category: Children) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 197)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09794CHI in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Heer! Ik ben een kind, laat mij groeien in de schaduw van Uw goedertierenheid. Ik ben een teer plantje, voed mij met de regen uit de wolken van Uw milddadigheid. Ik ben een jong boompje in de tuin van liefde, laat mij een vruchtdragende boom worden. Gij zijt de Machtige en de Krachtige, en Gij zijt de Liefderijke, de Alwetende, de Alziende.
(Source category: Kinderen) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9620)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09794CHI in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Senhor! Sou uma criança; permite-me crescer à sombra da Tua benevolência. Sou uma tenra planta; faze com que eu seja nutrida pelas emanações das nuvens da Tua generosidade. Sou um pequeno arbusto no jardim do amor; torna-me uma árvore frutífera. Tu és o Forte e o Poderoso, o Amor Supremo, o Omnisciente, Aquele que tudo vê.
(Source category: Criança) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 1086)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10324 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10324/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10324/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O my God! Thou seest these children who are the twigs of the tree of life, the birds of the meads of salvation, the pearls of the ocean of Thy grace, the roses of the garden of Thy guidance. O God, our Lord! We sing Thy praise, bear witness to Thy sanctity and implore fervently the heaven of Thy mercy to make us lights of guidance, stars shining above the horizons of eternal glory amongst mankind, and to teach us a knowledge which proceedeth from Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10324 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10324/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10324/nl/</guid>
      <description>O mijn God! O mijn God! Gij ziet deze kinderen die de twijgen van de boom des levens zijn, de vogels van de weiden van verlossing, de parelen in de oceaan van Uw genade, de rozen in de tuin van Uw leiding. O God, onze Heer! Wij zingen Uw lof, getuigen van Uw heiligheid en smeken de hemel van Uw genade vurig om ons tot lichten van leiding te maken, sterren die te midden van de mensheid boven de horizon van eeuwige glorie schijnen, en ons de kennis die uit U voortkomt te onderwijzen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10685 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10685/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10685/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou most glorious Lord! Make this little maidservant of Thine blessed and happy; cause her to be cherished at the threshold of Thy oneness, and let her drink deep from the cup of Thy love so that she may be filled with rapture and ecstasy and diffuse sweet-scented fragrance. Thou art the Mighty and the Powerful, and Thou art the All-Knowing, the All-Seeing.
(Source category: Children) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 198)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10685 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10685/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10685/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij glorierijkste Heer! Maak deze kleine dienares van U gezegend en gelukkig. Koester haar aan de drempel van Uw één-zijn en laat haar met volle teugen drinken uit de beker van Uw liefde, opdat zij vervuld mag worden van verrukking en vervoering, en zoete geuren mag verspreiden. Gij zijt de Machtige en de Krachtige, en Gij zijt de Alwetende, de Alziende.
(Source category: Kinderen) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9621)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10701 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10701/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10701/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Make these children excellent plants. Let them grow and develop in the Garden of Thy Covenant, and bestow freshness and beauty through the outpourings from the clouds of the all-glorious Kingdom. O Thou kind Lord! I am a little child, exalt me by admitting me to the kingdom. I am earthly, make me heavenly; I am of the world below, let me belong to the realm above; gloomy, suffer me to become radiant; material, make me spiritual, and grant that I may manifest Thine infinite bounties.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10701 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10701/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10701/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh Señor! Haz de estos niños plantas excelentes. Permite que crezcan y se desarrollen en el Jardín de Tu Alianza, y otórgales lozanía y belleza mediante las efusiones de las nubes del Reino de Abhá. ¡Oh Dios bondadoso! Soy una criatura pequeña, enaltéceme admitiéndome en el reino. Soy terrenal, hazme celestial; pertenezco al mundo inferior, deja que pertenezca al reino superior; estoy apagado, haz que me vuelva radiante; soy material, hazme espiritual, y permite que pueda manifestar Tus infinitas bondades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10701 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10701/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10701/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Heer! Maak deze kinderen tot voortreffelijke planten. Laat hen groeien en zich ontwikkelen in de Tuin van Uw Verbond en maak hen fris en mooi door de uitstortingen vanuit de wolken van het Alglorierijke Koninkrijk. O Gij vriendelijk Heer! Ik ben een klein kind, verhef mij door mij tot het koninkrijk toe te laten. Ik ben aards, maak mij hemels; ik ben van de wereld hier beneden, laat mij tot het hemelse rijk behoren; somber, laat mij stralen; stoffelijk, maak mij geestelijk, en geef dat ik Uw oneindige gaven ten toon mag spreiden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10714 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10714/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10714/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! These lovely children are the handiwork of the fingers of Thy might and the wondrous signs of Thy greatness. O God! Protect these children, graciously assist them to be educated and enable them to render service to the world of humanity. O God! These children are pearls, cause them to be nurtured within the shell of Thy loving-kindness.
Thou art the Bountiful, the All-Loving.
(Source category: Children) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10714 in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10714/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10714/fr/</guid>
      <description>Ô toi, Seigneur de bonté, ces beaux enfants sont l’œuvre des mains de ta puissance et les signes merveilleux de ta grandeur. Ô Dieu, protège ces enfants. Par ta grâce, aide-les à s’instruire et permets-leur de servir l’humanité. Ô Dieu, ces enfants sont des perles ; qu’ils soient nourris dans le cocon de ta tendre bonté ! Tu es le Généreux, le Très-Aimant.
(Source category: Enfants et jeunes) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9163)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10714 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10714/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab10714/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij vriendelijk Heer! Deze liefelijke kinderen zijn het werk van de vingers van Uw macht en de wondere tekenen van Uw grootheid. O God! Bescherm deze kinderen, help hen door Uw genade om opgeleid te worden en stel hen in staat dienstbaar te zijn aan de mensheid. O God! Deze kinderen zijn parelen, laat hen gekoesterd worden in de schelp van Uw goedertierenheid. Gij zijt de Genadige, de Liefderijke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB11356 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab11356/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab11356/en/</guid>
      <description>##Infants
O Thou peerless Lord! Let this suckling babe be nursed from the breast of Thy loving-kindness, guard it within the cradle of Thy safety and protection and grant that it be reared in the arms of Thy tender affection.
(Source category: Children) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 200)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB11605 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab11605/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab11605/en/</guid>
      <description>He is God! O God, my God! Bestow upon me a pure heart, like unto a pearl.
(Source category: Children) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 192)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0129EDU in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/en/</guid>
      <description>O God! Educate these children. These children are the plants of Thine orchard, the flowers of Thy meadow, the roses of Thy garden. Let Thy rain fall upon them; let the Sun of Reality shine upon them with Thy love. Let Thy breeze refresh them in order that they may be trained, grow and develop, and appear in the utmost beauty. Thou art the Giver. Thou art the Compassionate.
(Source category: Children) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0129EDU in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Dio! Eduku ĉi tiujn infanojn. Ĉi infanoj estas la plantoj de Via horto, la floroj de Via kampo, la rozoj de Via ĝardeno. Faru, ke Via pluvo akvumu ilin, ke la Suno de l&amp;rsquo;Realo brilu sur ilin per Via amo. Viaj brizoj freŝigu ilin, por ke ili estu edukataj, kresku kaj evoluu, kaj montriĝu en pleja beleco. Vi estas la Donanto. Vi estas la Mizerikorda.
(Source category: Infanoj kaj Junuloj) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0129EDU in Papiamentu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/pap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/pap/</guid>
      <description>*Oh, God! Educate these children.
O Dios! Eduka e yunan aki. E yunan aki ta matanan di Bo hòfi, ta flornan di Bo sabana, ta rosanan di Bo hardin. Laga awasero kai riba nan. Laga e solo di realidat lumbranan ku Bo amor. Laga Bo brisa refreskanan, pa nan por siñá, kresé, desaroyá i aparesé den e bunitesa di mas grandi. Bo ta esun ku ta duná, Bo ta esun miserikordioso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09855 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/bh09855/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/bh09855/en/</guid>
      <description>##Infants
Praised be Thou, O Lord my God! Graciously grant that this infant be fed from the breast of Thy tender mercy and loving providence and be nourished with the fruit of Thy celestial trees. Suffer him not to be committed to the care of anyone save Thee, inasmuch as Thou, Thyself, through the potency of thy sovereign will and power, didst create and call him into being. There is none other God but Thee, the Almighty, the All-Knowing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09855 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/bh09855/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/bh09855/es/</guid>
      <description>##Bebés
¡Alabado seas, oh Señor mi Dios! Permite bondadosamente que esta criatura se alimente del pecho de Tu tierna merced y Tu amorosa providencia, y que se nutra con el fruto de Tus árboles celestiales. No dejes que se encomiende al cuidado de nadie salvo de Ti, puesto que Tú mismo la creaste y le diste la existencia mediante la fuerza de Tu soberana voluntad y poder. No hay otro Dios más que Tú, el Todopoderoso, el Sapientísimo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10076 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/bh10076/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/bh10076/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord, my God! This is a child that hath sprung from the loins of one of Thy servants to whom Thou hast granted a distinguished station in the Tablets of Thine irrevocable decree in the Books of Thy behest. I beseech Thee by Thy name, whereby everyone is enabled to attain the object of his desire, to grant that this child may become a more mature soul amongst Thy servants; cause him to shine forth through the power of Thy name, enable him to utter Thy praise, to set his face towards Thee and to draw nigh unto Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
