<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Forgiveness on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-forgiveness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Forgiveness on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-forgiveness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0030SHE in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/abu0030she/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/abu0030she/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou forgiving Lord! Thou art the shelter of all these Thy servants. Thou knowest the secrets and art aware of all things. We are all helpless, and Thou art the Mighty, the Omnipotent. We are all sinners, and Thou art the Forgiver of sins, the Merciful, the Compassionate. O Lord! Look not at our shortcomings. Deal with us according to Thy grace and bounty. Our shortcomings are many, but the ocean of Thy forgiveness is boundless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0030SHE in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/abu0030she/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/abu0030she/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh Señor perdonador! Tú eres el refugio de todos estos siervos Tuyos. Tú conoces los secretos y estás informado de todas las cosas. Todos somos débiles y Tú eres el Fuerte, el Omnipotente. Todos somos pecadores y Tú eres el Perdonador de los pecados, el Misericordioso, el Compasivo. ¡Oh Señor! No consideres nuestras faltas. Trátanos de acuerdo con Tu gracia y generosidad. Nuestras faltas son muchas, pero el océano de Tu perdón es ilimitado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0030SHE in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/abu0030she/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/abu0030she/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Vi, pardonema Sinjoro! Vi estas la ŝirmo de ĉiuj ĉi Viaj servantoj. Vi konas la sekretojn kaj scias pri ĉiuj aferoj. Ni ĉiuj estas senhelpaj, kaj Vi estas la Potenca, la Ĉiopova. Ni ĉiuj estas pekantoj, kaj Vi estas la Pardonanto de pekoj, la Mizerikorda, la Kompatema. Ho Eternulo! Ne atentu niajn malperfektecojn. Traktu nin laŭ Via graco kaj malavaro. Multaj estas niaj malperfektecoj, sed senlima estas la oceano de Via pardonemo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0030SHE in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/abu0030she/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/abu0030she/fr/</guid>
      <description>Ô toi, Dieu indulgent, tu es le refuge de tous tes serviteurs. Tu connais les secrets, rien ne t’échappe. Nous sommes tous faibles, tu es le Puissant, l’Omnipotent. Nous sommes tous des pécheurs, tu pardonnes les péchés, toi, le Miséricordieux, le Compatissant. Ô Seigneur, ne considère pas nos faiblesses. Traite-nous selon ta grâce et ta miséricorde. Nombreux sont nos défauts, mais infini est l’océan de ton pardon, grande est notre indigence, mais manifestes sont les signes de ton aide et de ton soutien.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00002MEN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00002men/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00002men/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be unto Thee, O God. How can I make mention of Thee while Thou art sanctified from the praise of all mankind. Magnified be Thy Name, O God, Thou art the King, the Eternal Truth; Thou knowest what is in the heavens and on the earth, and unto Thee must all return. Thou hast sent down Thy divinely ordained Revelation according to a clear measure. Praised art Thou, O Lord!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00002MEN in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00002men/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00002men/pt/</guid>
      <description>Glória a Ti, ó Deus. Como posso de Ti fazer menção, quando Tu estás santificado acima do louvor de toda a humanidade? Magnificado seja o Teu Nome, ó Deus. Tu és o Rei, a Verdade Eterna; sabes o que está nos céus e na terra, e a Ti devem todos voltar. Mandaste descer a Tua Revelação, divinamente ordenada, segundo uma medida clara. Louvado és, ó Senhor! A Teu mando, tornas vitorioso a quem Tu desejas, através das hostes do céu e da terra e de tudo o que entre eles existe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00485TRE in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00485tre/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00485tre/en/</guid>
      <description>I am aware, O Lord, that my trespasses have covered my face with shame in Thy presence, and have burdened my back before Thee, have intervened between me and Thy beauteous countenance, have compassed me from every direction and have hindered me on all sides from gaining access unto the revelations of Thy celestial power. O Lord! If Thou forgivest me not, who is there then to grant pardon, and if Thou hast no mercy upon me who is capable of showing compassion?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00485TRE in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00485tre/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00485tre/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik ben mij ervan bewust, o Heer, dat mijn overtredingen mijn gezicht met schaamte bedekken in Uw tegenwoordigheid en als een last op mijn schouders drukken in Uw bijzijn, dat zij tussen mij en Uw schone gelaat zijn gekomen, mij rondom insluiten en mij aan alle kanten beletten de openbaringen van Uw hemelse macht te bereiken. O Heer! Als Gij mij niet vergeeft, wie is er dan om vergeving te schenken, en als Gij mij niet genadig zijt, wie kan er dan mededogen betonen?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00617 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00617/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00617/en/</guid>
      <description>I beg Thee to forgive me, O my Lord, for every mention but the mention of Thee, and for every praise but the praise of Thee, and for every delight but delight in Thy nearness, and for every pleasure but the pleasure of communion with Thee, and for every joy but the joy of Thy love and of Thy good-pleasure, and for all things pertaining unto me which bear no relationship unto Thee, O Thou Who art the Lord of lords, He Who provideth the means and unlocketh the doors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00617 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00617/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bb00617/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik smeek U, o mijn Heer, mij te vergeven voor ieder noemen buiten het noemen van U, voor alle lof buiten de lof aan U, voor ieder genot buiten het genot U nabij te zijn, voor ieder genoegen buiten het genoegen van omgang met U, voor alle vreugde buiten de vreugde van Uw liefde en welbehagen, en voor alle dingen die mij eigen zijn doch geen verband houden met U, o Gij die de Heer der heren zijt, Degeen die de middelen verschaft en de deuren ontsluit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00005SEE in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh00005see/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh00005see/en/</guid>
      <description>Thou seest me, O my Lord, with my face turned towards the heaven of Thy bounty and the ocean of Thy favor, withdrawn from all else beside Thee. I ask of Thee, by the splendors of the Sun of Thy revelation on Sinai, and the effulgences of the Orb of Thy grace which shineth from the horizon of Thy Name, the Ever-Forgiving, to grant me Thy pardon and to have mercy upon me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00005SEE in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh00005see/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh00005see/nl/</guid>
      <description>Gij ziet mij, o mijn Heer, met mijn gelaat gekeerd naar de hemel van Uw milddadigheid en de oceaan van Uw gunst, teruggetrokken van alles buiten U. Ik vraag U, bij de glans van de zon van Uw openbaring op de Sinaï, en de luister van de hemelbol van Uw genade die schijnt van de horizon van Uw Naam, de Immervergevende, mij Uw gratie te schenken en erbarmen met mij te hebben.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00593 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh00593/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh00593/en/</guid>
      <description>O God our Lord! Protect us through Thy grace from whatsoever may be repugnant unto Thee, and vouchsafe unto us that which well beseemeth Thee. Give us more out of Thy bounty, and bless us. Pardon us for the things we have done, and wash away our sins, and forgive us with Thy gracious forgiveness. Verily, Thou art the Most Exalted, the Self-Subsisting. Thy loving providence hath encompassed all created things in the heavens and on the earth, and Thy forgiveness hath surpassed the whole creation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00593 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh00593/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh00593/nl/</guid>
      <description>O God onze Heer! Bescherm ons door Uw genade tegen al hetgeen U weerzinwekkend is, en verleen ons hetgeen U voegt. Geef ons meer van Uw gaven, en zegen ons. Schenk ons vergiffenis voor de dingen die wij hebben gedaan, en neem onze zonden weg, en vergeef ons met Uw genadige vergeving. Waarlijk, Gij zijt de Verhevenste, de Bij-zich-bestaande. Uw liefdevolle voorzienigheid omvat al het geschapene in de hemelen en op aarde, en Uw vergiffenis gaat de gehele schepping te boven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00634 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh00634/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh00634/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise be unto Thee, O Lord. Forgive us our sins, have mercy upon us and enable us to return unto Thee. Suffer us not to rely on aught else besides Thee, and vouchsafe unto us, through Thy bounty, that which Thou lovest and desirest and well beseemeth Thee. Exalt the station of them that have truly believed, and forgive them with Thy gracious forgiveness. Verily, Thou art the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH05768 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh05768/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh05768/en/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! Every time I venture to make mention of Thee, I am held back by my mighty sins and grievous trespasses against Thee, and find myself wholly deprived of Thy grace, and utterly powerless to celebrate Thy praise. My great confidence in Thy bounty, however, reviveth my hope in Thee, and my certitude that Thou wilt bountifully deal with me emboldeneth me to extol Thee, and to ask of Thee the things Thou dost possess.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07106 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh07106/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh07106/en/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! I beseech Thee by Thy Chosen Ones, and by the Bearers of Thy Trust, and by Him Whom Thou hast ordained to be the Seal of Thy Prophets and of Thy Messengers, to let Thy remembrance be my companion, and Thy love my aim, and Thy face my goal, and Thy name my lamp, and Thy wish my desire, and Thy pleasure my delight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08600FAC in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/en/</guid>
      <description>I am he, O my Lord, that hath set his face towards Thee, and fixed his hope on the wonders of Thy grace and the revelations of Thy bounty. I pray Thee that Thou wilt not suffer me to turn away disappointed from the door of Thy mercy, nor abandon me to such of Thy creatures as have repudiated Thy Cause. I am, O my God, Thy servant and the son of Thy servant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08600FAC in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/es/</guid>
      <description>Soy aquel, oh mi Señor, que ha vuelto el rostro hacia Ti y ha fijado su esperanza en las maravillas de Tu gracia y en las revelaciones de Tu munificencia. Te ruego que no permitas que me aleje desilusionado de la puerta de Tu misericordia, ni me dejes a merced de aquellas criaturas Tuyas que han repudiado Tu Causa. ¡Oh mi Dios! Soy Tu siervo y el hijo de Tu siervo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08600FAC in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik ben degeen, o mijn Heer, die zijn gelaat naar U heeft gekeerd en zijn hoop heeft gevestigd op de wonderen van Uw genade en de openbaringen van Uw milddadigheid. Ik bid U dat Gij mij niet teleurgesteld van de deur van Uw erbarmen laat weggaan, noch mij overlevert aan diegenen onder Uw schepselen die Uw Zaak hebben verworpen. Ik ben Uw dienaar, o mijn God, en de zoon van Uw dienaar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08855 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08855/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08855/en/</guid>
      <description>Lauded be Thy name, O my God and the God of all things, my Glory and the Glory of all things, my Desire and the Desire of all things, my Strength and the Strength of all things, my King and the King of all things, my Aim and the Aim of all things, my Mover and the Mover of all things! Suffer me not, I implore Thee, to be kept back from the ocean of Thy tender mercies, nor to be far removed from the shores of nearness to Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
