<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Birth of Bahá’u’lláh on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-birth-of-bah%C3%A1ull%C3%A1h/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Birth of Bahá’u’lláh on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-birth-of-bah%C3%A1ull%C3%A1h/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6309 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6309/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6309/</guid>
      <description>##Birth of Bahá’u’lláh
He is the Most Holy, the Most Great.
This is the month wherein was born He Who beareth the Most Great Name, Whose appearance hath caused the limbs of humankind to quake and the dust of Whose footsteps the Concourse on high and the dwellers of the cities of names have sought for a blessing. Whereupon they rendered praise unto God and cried out in joy and exultation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8269 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8269/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8269/</guid>
      <description>#Lawh-i-Mawlúd ##Tablet of the Birth
O concourse of the seen and the unseen! Rejoice with exceeding gladness in your hearts and souls, for the night hath come for the harvesting of the ages and the gathering up of past cycles, the night wherein all days and nights were called into being and the time preordained for this Revelation was fulfilled at the behest of Him Who is the Lord of might and power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8270 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8270/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8270/</guid>
      <description>He is the Most Holy, the Most Exalted, the Most Great.
The Birthday Festival is come, and He Who is the Beauty of God, the All-Powerful, the All-Compelling, the All-Loving, hath ascended His throne. Well is it with the one who in this Day hath attained His presence and towards whom the gaze of God, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting, hath been directed. Say: We have celebrated this Festival in the Most Great Prison at a time when the kings of the earth have risen against Us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8271 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8271/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8271/</guid>
      <description>He is God.
O concourse of ardent lovers! By the righteousness of God, this is a night the like of which hath never been witnessed in the world of creation. And this, verily, is from the grace of God, the All-Glorious, the Most Bountiful. This is the night wherein the Spirit intoned such a melody as to throw into commotion the inner realities of all men, proclaiming: “Rejoice, O Concourse on high, within your retreats of Paradise!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
