<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Youth on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-youth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Youth on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-youth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00314HOR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab00314hor/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab00314hor/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! From the horizon of detachment Thou hast manifested souls that, even as the shining moon, shed radiance upon the realm of heart and soul, rid themselves from the attributes of the world of existence and hastened forth unto the kingdom of immortality. With a drop from the ocean of Thy loving-kindness Thou didst oft-times moisten the gardens of their hearts until they gained incomparable freshness and beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00949WIN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab00949win/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab00949win/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! Graciously bestow a pair of heavenly wings unto each of these fledglings, and give them spiritual power that they may wing their flight through this limitless space and may soar to the heights of the Abhá Kingdom. O Lord! Strengthen these fragile seedlings that each one may become a fruitful tree, verdant and flourishing. Render these souls victorious through the potency of Thy celestial hosts, that they may be able to crush the forces of error and ignorance and to unfurl the standard of fellowship and guidance amidst the people; that they may, even as the reviving breaths of the spring, refresh and quicken the trees of human souls and like unto vernal showers make the meads of that region green and fertile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02825 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab02825/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab02825/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise and glory be to Thee, O Lord my God! This is a choice sapling which Thou hast planted in the meads of Thy love and hast nurtured with the fingers of Thy Lordship. Thou hast watered it from the well-spring of everlasting life which streameth forth from the gardens of Thy oneness and Thou hast caused the clouds of Thy tender mercy to shower Thy favors upon it. It hath now grown and developed beneath the shelter of Thy blessings which are manifest from the Dayspring of Thy divine essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10492 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! Bestow heavenly confirmation upon this daughter of the kingdom, and graciously aid her that she may remain firm and steadfast in Thy Cause and that she may, even as a nightingale of the rose garden of mysteries, warble melodies in the Abhá Kingdom in the most wondrous tones, thereby bringing happiness to everyone. Make her exalted among the daughters of the kingdom and enable her to attain life eternal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10703RAD in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Make this youth radiant, and confer Thy bounty upon this poor creature. Bestow upon him knowledge, grant him added strength at the break of every morn and guard him within the shelter of Thy protection so that he may be freed from error, may devote himself to the service of Thy Cause, may guide the wayward, lead the hapless, free the captives and awaken the heedless, that all may be blessed with Thy remembrance and praise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn10130 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10130/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10130/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Make this youth radiant and confer Thy bounty upon this poor creature. Bestow upon him knowledge, grant him added strength at the break of every morn and guard him within the shelter of Thy protection so that he may be freed from error, may devote himself to the service of Thy Cause, may guide the wayward, lead the hapless, free the captives and awaken the heedless, that all may be blessed with Thy remembrance and praise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn10137 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10137/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10137/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! Graciously bestow a pair of heavenly wings unto each of these fledglings and give them spiritual power that they may wing their flight through this limitless space and may soar to the heights of the Abhá Kingdom. O Lord! Strengthen these fragile seedlings that each one may become a fruitful tree, verdant and flourishing. Render these souls victorious through the potency of Thy celestial hosts, that they may be able to crush the forces of error and ignorance and to unfurl the standard of fellowship and guidance amidst the people; that they may, even as the reviving breaths of the spring, refresh and quicken the trees of human souls and like unto vernal showers make the meads of that region green and fertile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn10142 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10142/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10142/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind lord! Bestow heavenly confirmation upon this daughter of the Kingdom and graciously aid her that she may remain firm and steadfast in Thy Cause and that she may, even as a nightingale of the rose-garden of mysteries, warble melodies in the Abhá Kingdom in most wondrous tones, thereby bringing happiness to everyone. Make her exalted among the daughters of the Kingdom and enable her to attain life eternal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12982 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12982/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12982/</guid>
      <description>*PRAYER FOR YOUTH (FEAST OF ASMA, 20 AUGUST 2000)
O Bikpela! Mekim dispela yangpela i pulap long lait, na givim blesing bilong Yu long dispela tarangu. Givim bikpela save long em, givim bikpela strong moa long em long stat bilong wan wan de na lukautim em gut tru long gutpela ples bilong Yu. Inap em i no ken mekim rong. Inap em i makim laip bilong en yet long wokim wok bilong Lotu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6871 in Papiamentu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/pap/bpn6871/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/pap/bpn6871/</guid>
      <description>*Oh, God! Make this youth radiant
O Dios! Hasi e hoben aki radiante i konfiere su bondat riba e kriatura pober aki. Duné konosementu i un forsa nobo kada dia, asina ku e tin kuido i salbashon den Bo protekshon di tur pika pa e sirbí Bo kousa, pa guia esnan ku ta pober i debil, pa librá esnan ku ta den prison i esklabitut, pa lanta esnan ku ta na soño i pa ta felis kordando i pensando riba Bo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
