<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB05996 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab05996/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB05996 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab05996/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB05996 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab05996/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab05996/en/</guid>
      <description>##For Women
O Lord, O Thou Whose mercy hath encompassed all, Whose forgiveness is transcendent, Whose bounty is sublime, Whose pardon and generosity are all-embracing, and the lights of Whose forgiveness are diffused throughout the world! O Lord of Glory! I entreat Thee, fervently and tearfully, to cast upon Thy handmaiden who hath ascended unto Thee the glances of the eye of Thy mercy. Robe her in the mantle of Thy grace, bright with the ornaments of the celestial Paradise, and, sheltering her beneath the tree of Thy oneness, illumine her face with the lights of Thy mercy and compassion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB05996 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab05996/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab05996/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Senhor, ó Tu cuja misericórdia circundou a todos, cujo perdão é transcendente, cuja bondade é sublime, cuja absolvição e generosidade envolve a todos, e as luzes de cujo perdão estão difundidas por toda parte! Ó Senhor da glória! Suplico-Te fervorosamente e em lágrimas, para que lances os brilhos do olhar da Tua misericórdia sobre a Tua serva que a Ti ascendeu. Envolve-a com o manto da Tua graça, resplandecente com os ornamentos do Paraíso celestial, e, abrigando-a sob a árvore da Tua unicidade, ilumina a sua face com as luzes da Tua misericórdia e compaixão.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
