<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-The Fast on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-the-fast/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-The Fast on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-the-fast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00154FIR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00154fir/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00154fir/en/</guid>
      <description>*The Kitáb-i-Aqdas states: “We have commanded you to pray and fast from the beginning of maturity [15 years]; this is ordained by God, your Lord and the Lord of your forefathers&amp;hellip; The traveler, the ailing, those who are with child or giving suck, are not bound by the fast&amp;hellip; Abstain from food and drink from sunrise to sundown, and beware lest desire deprive you of this grace that is appointed in the Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00154FIR in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00154fir/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00154fir/nl/</guid>
      <description>*In De Kitáb-i-Aqdas staat: “Wij hebben u opgedragen vanaf het begin der volwassenheid (15 jaar) te bidden en te vasten; dit is verordend door God, uw Heer en de Heer uwer voorvaderen… Reizigers, zieken en zij die een kind verwachten of zogen, zijn niet verplicht te vasten… Onthoudt u van zonsopgang tot zonsondergang van spijs en drank en hoedt u dat begeerte u deze genade die in het Boek is vastgelegd niet ontneemt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00778 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O Lord my God! These are the days whereon Thou hast bidden all men to observe the Fast, that through it they may purify their souls and rid themselves of all attachment to anyone but Thee, and that out of their hearts may ascend that which will be worthy of the court of Thy majesty and may well beseem the seat of the revelation of Thy oneness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00778 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Gloria sea a Ti, oh Señor mi Dios! Tú has ordenado a todos, oh mi Dios, observar el ayuno durante estos días, para que mediante él purifiquen sus almas y se liberen de todo apego a otro que no seas Tú, y que de sus corazones ascienda lo que sea digno de la corte de Tu majestad y propio de la sede de la revelación de Tu unicidad. Permite, oh mi Señor, que este ayuno llegue a ser un río de aguas vivifi-cantes y produzca la virtud con que lo has dotado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00778 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/nl/</guid>
      <description>Glorie zij U, o Heer mijn God! Dit zijn de dagen waarop Gij alle mensen hebt geboden te vasten, dat zij daardoor hun ziel kunnen zuiveren en zich van alle gehechtheid aan iemand buiten U kunnen ontdoen, en datgene uit hun hart omhoog mag komen wat het hof van Uw majesteit waardig is en de zetel van de openbaring van Uw één-zijn past. Geef, o mijn God, dat deze vasten een rivier van levengevend water moge worden en de deugd moge voortbrengen waarmee Gij hem hebt begiftigd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01125 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/en/</guid>
      <description>I beseech Thee, O my God, by Thy mighty Sign, and by the revelation of Thy grace amongst men, to cast me not away from the gate of the city of Thy presence, and to disappoint not the hopes I have set on the manifestations of Thy grace amidst Thy creatures. Thou seest me, O my God, holding to Thy Name, the Most Holy, the Most Luminous, the Most Mighty, the Most Great, the Most Exalted, the Most Glorious, and clinging to the hem of the robe to which have clung all in this world and in the world to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01125 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/es/</guid>
      <description>Te imploro, oh mi Dios, por Tu poderoso Signo y por la revelación de Tu gracia entre los hombres, que no me eches de la puerta de la ciudad de Tu presencia, ni frustres las esperanzas que he puesto en las manifestaciones de Tu gracia entre Tus criaturas. Tú me ves, oh mi Dios, aferrado a Tu Nombre, el Más Santo, el Más Luminoso, el Más Poderoso, el Más Grande, el Más Exaltado, el Más Glorioso, y adherido al borde del manto al cual se han aferrado todos, en este mundo y en el venidero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01125 in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/fr/</guid>
      <description>##Prières pour le jeûne
*Le Kitáb-i-Aqdas dit : « Nous vous avons ordonné de prier et de jeûner dès l’âge de maturité (15 ans) ; c’est un ordre de Dieu, votre Seigneur et le Seigneur de vos pères&amp;hellip; Les voyageurs, les malades et les femmes enceintes ou allaitantes ne sont pas tenus de jeûner&amp;hellip; Abstenez-vous de toute nourriture et boisson du lever au coucher du soleil et prenez garde de ne pas laisser le désir vous priver de ce bienfait prescrit dans le Livre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01125 in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/it/</guid>
      <description>*L’Aqdas dice: «Vi abbiamo comandato di pregare e digiunare dall’inizio della maturità [15 anni]; questo è ordinato da Dio, vostro Signore e Signore dei vostri avi. Egli ne ha dispensato coloro che sono deboli per malattia o età. &amp;hellip; Viaggiatori, sofferenti, gestanti e nutrici non sono vincolati al digiuno. &amp;hellip; Astenetevi da cibi e bevande dall’aurora al tramonto e badate di non privarvi di questa grazia che è stabilita nel Libro».</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01125 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik smeek U, o mijn God, bij Uw machtige Teken en bij de openbaring van Uw genade onder de mensen, mij niet weg te houden van de poort van de stad van Uw tegenwoordigheid en mij niet teleur te stellen in mijn hoop op de openbaringen van Uw genade onder Uw schepselen. Gij ziet mij, o mijn God, getrouw aan Uw Naam, de Heiligste, de Stralendste, de Machtigste, de Grootste, de Verhevenste, de Heerlijkste, en mij vasthouden aan de zoom van de mantel waaraan allen in deze wereld en in de wereld die komen gaat zich vasthouden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01503ENJ in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01503enj/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01503enj/en/</guid>
      <description>Praised be Thou, O God, my God! These are the days whereon Thou hast enjoined Thy chosen ones, Thy loved ones and Thy servants to observe the Fast, which Thou hast made a light unto the people of Thy kingdom, even as Thou didst make obligatory prayer a ladder of ascent unto those who acknowledge Thy unity. I beg of Thee, O my God, by these two mighty pillars, which Thou hast ordained as a glory and honor for all mankind, to keep Thy religion safe from the mischief of the ungodly and the plotting of every wicked doer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01503ENJ in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01503enj/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01503enj/nl/</guid>
      <description>Geprezen zijt Gij, o God mijn God! Dit zijn de dagen waarop Gij Uw uitverkorenen, Uw geliefden en Uw dienaren hebt opgedragen de Vasten, die Gij tot een licht voor het volk van Uw koninkrijk hebt gemaakt, in acht te nemen, evenals Gij verplicht gebed tot een ladder naar omhoog hebt gemaakt voor hen die Uw eenheid erkennen. Ik smeek U, o mijn God, bij deze twee machtige pilaren die Gij hebt beschikt tot glorie en eer van de gehele mensheid, Uw religie te behoeden voor het kwaad van de verdorvenen en het samenzweren van alle boosdoeners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01888 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01888/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01888/en/</guid>
      <description>These are, O my God, the days whereon Thou didst enjoin Thy servants to observe the Fast. With it Thou didst adorn the preamble of the Book of Thy Laws revealed unto Thy creatures, and didst deck forth the Repositories of Thy commandments in the sight of all who are in Thy heaven and all who are on Thy earth. Thou hast endowed every hour of these days with a special virtue, inscrutable to all except Thee, Whose knowledge embraceth all created things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01888 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01888/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01888/nl/</guid>
      <description>Dit zijn, o mijn God, de dagen waarop Gij Uw dienaren hebt geboden te vasten. Daarmee hebt Gij de inleiding gesierd van Uw Wetboek dat aan Uw schepselen is geopenbaard, en de schatkamers van Uw geboden getooid voor het oog van allen die in Uw hemel en allen die op Uw aarde zijn. Gij hebt ieder uur van deze dagen begiftigd met een bijzondere kracht die ondoorgrondelijk is voor allen buiten U, Gij Wiens kennis al het geschapene omvat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07657 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh07657/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh07657/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise be to Thee, O Lord my God! I beseech Thee by this Revelation whereby darkness hath been turned into light, through which the Frequented Fane hath been built, and the Written Tablet revealed, and the Outspread Roll uncovered, to send down upon me and upon them who are in my company that which will enable us to soar into the heavens of Thy transcendent glory, and will wash us from the stain of such doubts as have hindered the suspicious from entering into the tabernacle of Thy unity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07657 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh07657/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh07657/eo/</guid>
      <description>Laŭdo estu al Vi, ho Sinjoro mia Dio! Mi petegas al Vi je tiu ĉi Revelacio, per kiu malhelo estas renversita al lumo, per kiu la Templo Frekventata estas konstruita, kaj estas revelaciita la Skribita Epistolo, kaj la fermita Skrib-rulaĵo elvolvita, alsendu sur min kaj sur tiujn apud mi tion, kio ebligos al ni sori en la ĉielojn de Via transcenda gloro kaj kio forlavos de ni la makulojn de tiaj duboj, kiuj baris al la suspektemaj la vojon al la tabernaklo de Via unueco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10127 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10127/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10127/en/</guid>
      <description>In the Name of Him Who hath been promised in the Books of God, the All-Knowing, the All-Informed! The days of fasting have arrived wherein those servants who circle round Thy throne and have attained Thy presence have fasted. Say: O God of names and creator of heaven and earth! I beg of Thee by Thy Name, the All-Glorious, to accept the fast of those who have fasted for love of Thee and for the sake of Thy good-pleasure and have carried out what Thou hast bidden them in Thy Books and Tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10581 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise be unto Thee, O Lord my God! We have observed the Fast in conformity with Thy bidding and break it now through Thy love and Thy good-pleasure. Deign to accept, O my God, the deeds that we have performed in Thy path wholly for the sake of Thy beauty with our faces set towards Thy Cause, free from aught else but Thee. Bestow, then, Thy forgiveness upon us, upon our forefathers, and upon all such as have believed in Thee and in Thy mighty signs in this most great, this most glorious Revelation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10581 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/nl/</guid>
      <description>Lof zij U, o Heer mijn God! Wij hebben ons aan de Vasten gehouden overeenkomstig Uw gebod en beëindigen die nu door Uw liefde en Uw welbehagen. Wilt Gij dan, o mijn God, de daden aanvaarden die wij geheel omwille van Uw schoonheid op Uw pad verrichten met ons gelaat naar Uw Zaak gekeerd, vrij van alles buiten U. Schenk dan Uw vergeving aan ons, aan onze voorvaderen en aan allen die in U en in Uw machtige tekenen geloven in deze grootste, deze glorierijkste Openbaring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10581 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/pt/</guid>
      <description>Louvado sejas, ó Senhor meu Deus! Observámos o Jejum de acordo com a Tua vontade e quebrámo-lo agora pelo Teu amor e pelo Teu agrado. Digna-Te aceitar, ó meu Deus, as obras que temos realizado no Teu caminho inteiramente por amor à Tua beleza, com as nossas faces voltadas para a Tua Causa, livres de tudo senão de Ti. Concede, pois, o Teu perdão a todos nós e aos nossos antepassados, e a todos os que acreditaram em Ti e nos Teus poderosos sinais nesta mais sublime, nesta mais gloriosa Revelação.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
