<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-ABU0129EDU on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-abu0129edu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-ABU0129EDU on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-abu0129edu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0129EDU in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/en/</guid>
      <description>O God! Educate these children. These children are the plants of Thine orchard, the flowers of Thy meadow, the roses of Thy garden. Let Thy rain fall upon them; let the Sun of Reality shine upon them with Thy love. Let Thy breeze refresh them in order that they may be trained, grow and develop, and appear in the utmost beauty. Thou art the Giver. Thou art the Compassionate.
(Source category: Children) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0129EDU in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Dio! Eduku ĉi tiujn infanojn. Ĉi infanoj estas la plantoj de Via horto, la floroj de Via kampo, la rozoj de Via ĝardeno. Faru, ke Via pluvo akvumu ilin, ke la Suno de l&amp;rsquo;Realo brilu sur ilin per Via amo. Viaj brizoj freŝigu ilin, por ke ili estu edukataj, kresku kaj evoluu, kaj montriĝu en pleja beleco. Vi estas la Donanto. Vi estas la Mizerikorda.
(Source category: Infanoj kaj Junuloj) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0129EDU in Papiamentu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/pap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/abu0129edu/pap/</guid>
      <description>*Oh, God! Educate these children.
O Dios! Eduka e yunan aki. E yunan aki ta matanan di Bo hòfi, ta flornan di Bo sabana, ta rosanan di Bo hardin. Laga awasero kai riba nan. Laga e solo di realidat lumbranan ku Bo amor. Laga Bo brisa refreskanan, pa nan por siñá, kresé, desaroyá i aparesé den e bunitesa di mas grandi. Bo ta esun ku ta duná, Bo ta esun miserikordioso.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
