<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Unity on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-unity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Unity on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-unity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0023UNI in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/abu0023uni/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/abu0023uni/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O my God! Verily, I invoke Thee and supplicate before Thy threshold, asking Thee that all Thy mercies may descend upon these souls. Specialize them for Thy favor and Thy truth. O Lord! Unite and bind together the hearts, join in accord all the souls, and exhilarate the spirits through the signs of Thy sanctity and oneness. O Lord! Make these faces radiant through the light of Thy oneness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10505 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O my God! Unite the hearts of Thy servants, and reveal to them Thy great purpose. May they follow Thy commandments and abide in Thy law. Help them, O God, in their endeavor, and grant them strength to serve Thee. O God! Leave them not to themselves, but guide their steps by the light of Thy knowledge, and cheer their hearts by Thy love. Verily, Thou art their Helper and their Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10505 in Papiamentu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/pap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/pap/</guid>
      <description>*Oh, my God! Oh my God! Unite the hearts of Thy servants
O mi Dios! O mi Dios! Uni e kurasonnan di Bo sirbidornan i rebela nan Bo obhetivo grandi. Hasí nan sigi Bo mandamentunan i biba den Bo ley. Yuda nan, o Dios, den nan esfuerso, i duna nan forsa pa sirbi Bo. O Dios, no laga nan pa nan kuenta, pero guia nan pasonan ku e lus di Bo sabidoria, i hubilá nan kurasonnan den Bo amor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12944 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12944/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12944/</guid>
      <description>O God bilong mi! O God bilong mi! Bungim wantaim ol bel bilong olgeta wokman bilong Yu, na soim ol long as bilong bikpela wok bilong Yu. I gutpela sapos ol i bihainim ol lo na ol tok bilong Yu. O God. Helpim ol long mekim wok bilong Yu na strongim ol bai ol inap long wok long Yu. O God, Yu no ken lusim ol. Lait bilong Yu i mas soim ol long rot ol i ken wokabaut long en, na Yu mas amamasim bel bilong ol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12945 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12945/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12945/</guid>
      <description>Glori i go long Yu, O God, long wanem Yu bin soimaut bikpela laik long ol manmeri! O Yu, Husat i Laip na Lait bilong mipela. Soim rot bilong Yu long ol wokmanmeri bilong Yu. Mekim mipela i kamap olsem papa bilong planti samting long wanem mipela i bilip long Yu. Na helpim mipela long lusim tingting long ol arapela samting na holimpas long Yu tasol.
O God, skulim mipela long Yu Yet I Wanpela.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12946 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12946/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12946/</guid>
      <description>Plis God, inap Yu karamapim olgeta hap graun wantaim lait bilong bung wantaim. Na putim wanpela mak olsem, em &amp;ldquo;dispela Kingdom em Kingdom bilong God&amp;rdquo; i stap long poret bilong ol lain manmeri long dispela graun.
God grant that the light of unity may envelop the whole earth, and that the seal, &amp;ldquo;the Kingdom is God’s&amp;rdquo;, may be stamped upon the brow of all its peoples.
(Source category: UNITY) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 12946)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12947 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12947/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12947/</guid>
      <description>O gutpela Papa! Yu bin mekim kamap olgeta manmeri long wanpela papa na wanpela mama tasol. Yu bin tokaut olsem olgeta i mas i stap insait long wanpela haus tasol. Long ai bilong Yu, olgeta man i wokman bilong Yu na Yu lukautim olgeta insait long Haus Holi bilong Yu. Olgeta i bung wantaim long Tebol bilong Blesing bilong Yu. Olgeta i kisim lait long lait bilong Marimari bilong Yu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13360 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13360/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13360/</guid>
      <description>O Tydi yr hwn wyt Arglwydd yr Arglwyddi. Tystiaf mai Ti yw Arglwydd yr holl greadigaeth, ac Addysgwr pob creadur, gweledig ac anweledig. Tystiaf i&amp;rsquo;th nerth amgylchynu&amp;rsquo;r holl fydysawd, ac na all lluoedd y ddaear fyth Dy ddigaloni na rheolaeth yr holl bobloedd na&amp;rsquo;r cenhedloedd Dy atal rhag cyflawni Dy ewyllys. Cyfaddefaf nad oes i Ti ddymuniad ond ailenedigaeth yr holl fyd, a sefydliad undod ei bobloedd, a iachawdwriaeth pawb sy&amp;rsquo;n trigi ynddo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13361 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13361/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13361/</guid>
      <description>Bydded i Dduw ganiatau i olau undod amgylchynu&amp;rsquo;r holl ddaear, a&amp;rsquo;r sêl &amp;lsquo;Eiddo Duw yw y Deyrnas&amp;rsquo; ei osod ar dalcen ei holl bobloedd.
God grant that the light of unity may envelop the whole earth, and that the seal, &amp;ldquo;the Kingdom is God&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rdquo;, may be stamped upon the brow of all its peoples.
(Source category: Unity) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 13361)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13362 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13362/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13362/</guid>
      <description>O fy Nuw! O Fy Nuw! Una galonnau Dy weision a datguddia Dy fwriad mawr iddynt. Bydded iddynt ddilyn Dy orchmynion ac aros yn Dy gyfraith. Cynorthwya hwy, O Dduw, yn eu hymdrech a dyroiddnyt nerth i&amp;rsquo;th wasanaethu. O Dduw, paid a&amp;rsquo;u gadael i&amp;rsquo;w hunain ond arwain eu camre drwy lewyrch Dy wybodaeth a chysura eu calonnau â&amp;rsquo;th gariad. Yn wir, Tydi yw eu Cynorthwywr a&amp;rsquo;u Harglwydd.
O my God! O my God!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6790 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6790/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6790/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O God, for Thy manifestation of love to mankind! O Thou Who art our Life and Light, guide Thy servants in Thy way, and make us rich in Thee and free from all save Thee.
O God, teach us Thy Oneness and give us a realization of Thy Unity, that we may see no one save Thee. Thou art the Merciful and the Giver of bounty!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6791 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6791/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6791/</guid>
      <description>God grant that the light of unity may envelop the whole earth, and that the seal, “the Kingdom is God’s,” may be stamped upon the brow of all its peoples.
*Gleanings, VII
(Source category: Unity) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 6791)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6792 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6792/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6792/</guid>
      <description>O Thou Who art the Lord of Lords! I testify that Thou art the Lord of all creation, and the Educator of all beings, visible and invisible. I bear witness that Thy power hath encompassed the entire universe, and that the hosts of the earth can never dismay Thee, nor can the dominion of all peoples and nations deter Thee from executing Thy purpose. I confess that Thou hast no desire except the regeneration of the whole world, and the establishment of the unity of its peoples, and the salvation of all them that dwell therein.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
