<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH05894 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh05894/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH05894 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh05894/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH05894 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh05894/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh05894/en/</guid>
      <description>I know not, O my God, what the Fire is which Thou didst kindle in Thy land. Earth can never cloud its splendor, nor water quench its flame. All the peoples of the world are powerless to resist its force. Great is the blessedness of him that hath drawn nigh unto it, and heard its roaring. Some, O my God, Thou didst, through Thy strengthening grace, enable to approach it, while others Thou didst keep back by reason of what their hands have wrought in Thy days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH05894 in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh05894/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh05894/it/</guid>
      <description>Non so, o mio Dio, cosa sia questo Fuoco che accendesti nelle Tue regioni. La terra non può velarne lo splendore, né l’acqua soffocarne la fiamma. Tutti i popoli del mondo sono impo-tenti a resistere alla sua forza. Grande è la benedizione di colui che gli si è accostato e ha udito il suo crepitare. O mio Dio, Tu facesti che alcuni, per la Tua grazia rafforzatrice, potessero avvicinarlo, mentre altri trattenesti a cagione di quello che le loro mani hanno forgiato nei Tuoi giorni.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH05894 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh05894/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh05894/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik weet niet, o mijn God, wat het vuur is dat Gij in Uw land deed ontvlammen. Aarde kan de glans ervan nooit verduisteren, noch kan water de vlammen ervan blussen. Geen van de volkeren der wereld is bij machte de kracht ervan te weerstaan. Groot is de gelukzaligheid van hem die het is genaderd en het loeien ervan heeft gehoord. Sommigen, o mijn God, stelde Gij door Uw sterkende genade in staat het te naderen, terwijl Gij anderen ervan weerhield vanwege hetgeen hun handen in Uw dagen hebben aangericht.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
