<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Praise and Gratitude on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-praise-and-gratitude/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Praise and Gratitude on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-praise-and-gratitude/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00018MAJ in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bb00018maj/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bb00018maj/en/</guid>
      <description>All majesty and glory, O my God, and all dominion and light and grandeur and splendor be unto Thee. Thou bestowest sovereignty on whom Thou willest and dost withhold it from whom Thou desirest. No God is there but Thee, the All-Possessing, the Most Exalted. Thou art He Who createth from naught the universe and all that dwell therein. There is nothing worthy of Thee except Thyself, while all else but Thee are as outcasts in Thy holy presence and are as nothing when compared to the glory of Thine Own Being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03111 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh03111/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh03111/en/</guid>
      <description>In the Name of God, the Most High! Lauded and glorified art Thou, Lord, God Omnipotent! Thou before Whose wisdom the wise falleth short and faileth, before Whose knowledge the learned confesseth his ignorance, before Whose might the strong waxeth weak, before Whose wealth the rich testifieth to his poverty, before Whose light the enlightened is lost in darkness, toward the shrine of Whose knowledge turneth the essence of all understanding and around the sanctuary of Whose presence circle the souls of all mankind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07180 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh07180/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh07180/en/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! I yield Thee thanks for having enabled me to recognize the Manifestation of Thyself, and for having severed me from Thine enemies, and laid bare before mine eyes their misdeeds and wicked works in Thy days, and for having rid me of all attachment to them, and caused me to turn wholly towards Thy grace and bountiful favors. I give Thee thanks, also, for having sent down upon me from the clouds of Thy will that which hath so sanctified me from the hints of the infidels and the allusions of the misbelievers that I have fixed my heart firmly on Thee, and fled from such as have denied the light of Thy countenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07661 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh07661/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh07661/en/</guid>
      <description>Praised be Thou, O Lord my God! Every time I attempt to make mention of Thee, I am hindered by the sublimity of Thy station and the overpowering greatness of Thy might. For were I to praise Thee throughout the length of Thy dominion and the duration of Thy sovereignty, I would find that my praise of Thee can befit only such as are like unto me, who are themselves Thy creatures, and who have been generated through the power of Thy decree and been fashioned through the potency of Thy will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09401 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh09401/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh09401/en/</guid>
      <description>All praise, O my God, be to Thee Who art the Source of all glory and majesty, of greatness and honor, of sovereignty and dominion, of loftiness and grace, of awe and power. Whomsoever Thou willest Thou causest to draw nigh unto the Most Great Ocean, and on whomsoever Thou desirest Thou conferrest the honor of recognizing Thy Most Ancient Name. Of all who are in heaven and on earth, none can withstand the operation of Thy sovereign Will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09960 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh09960/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh09960/en/</guid>
      <description>Magnified be Thy Name, O Lord my God! Thou art He Whom all things worship and Who worshipeth no one, Who is the Lord of all things and is the vassal of none, Who knoweth all things and is known of none. Thou didst wish to make Thyself known unto men; therefore, Thou didst, through a word of Thy mouth, bring creation into being and fashion the universe. There is none other God except Thee, the Fashioner, the Creator, the Almighty, the Most Powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12489 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12489/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12489/</guid>
      <description>Magnified be Thy name, O Lord my God! Thou art He Whom all things worship…
Le Ali’i e, lo’u Atua e, ia fa’anene’eina pea Lou Suafa!
O lau Afio o Ia lea e tapua’i i ai mea uma a o Le e lē tapua’i i se tasi , o Lē o le Ali’i o mea uma ae lē o se auauna a se tasi, o Lē silafia mea uma ae e lē iloa lava e se tasi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12490 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12490/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12490/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! I yield Thee thanks for having enabled me to recognize the Manifestation of Thyself
Le Ali’i e, lo’u Atua e, ia fa’anene’eina Lau Afio! Ou te tu’uina atu le fa’afetai i Lau Afio ona o le fa’amalosia o a’u ina ia ou iloa le Faifa’aaliga o Lau lava Afio, aemaise le vavae’esea o a’u mai Ou fili, ma ua matuā fa’aaliatino mai ai i luma o o’u mata a latou amio sesē ma galuega leaga i Ou aso, atoa fo’i ma le avae’esea o a’u mai so’otaga uma ma i latou, ma lagaina ai a’u ia ou liliu atu atoatoa i Lou alofa tunoa ma Lau foa’ialofa lelei.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12569 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn12569/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn12569/</guid>
      <description>O thou candle of the Love of God! I ask God to grant thee by His favor and grace that which is thy utmost desire; that the closed doors become opened, the uneven roads become even, thy face shine by the love of God, thy sight become brighter by witnessing the signs of God; that thou mayest attain spiritual joy, eternal happiness and heavenly life.
(Source category: Praise and Gratitude) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6793 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6793/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6793/</guid>
      <description>O Thou Whose remembrance is the delight of the souls of all them that yearn after Thee, Whose name is the exultation of the hearts of all who are wholly devoted to Thy will, Whose praise is cherished by such as have drawn nigh unto Thy court, Whose face is the ardent desire of all them that have recognized Thy truth, Whose trial is the healer of the sicknesses of them who have embraced Thy Cause, Whose calamity is the highest aspiration of such as are rid of all attachment to any one but Thyself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6794 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6794/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6794/</guid>
      <description>God testifieth to the unity of His Godhood and to the singleness of His own Being. On the throne of eternity, from the inaccessible heights of His station, His tongue proclaimeth that there is none other God but Him. He Himself, independently of all else, hath ever been a witness unto His own oneness, the revealer of His own nature, the glorifier of His own essence. He, verily, is the All-Powerful, the Almighty, the Beauteous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6795 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6795/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6795/</guid>
      <description>Lauded be Thy name, O my God! I testify that no thought of Thee, howsoever wondrous, can ever ascend into the heaven of Thy knowledge, and no praise of Thee, no matter how transcendent, can soar up to the atmosphere of Thy wisdom. From eternity Thou hast been removed far above the reach and the ken of the comprehension of Thy servants, and immeasurably exalted above the strivings of Thy bondslaves to express Thy mystery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6796 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6796/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6796/</guid>
      <description>My God, Thou Whom I adore and worship, Who art Most Powerful! I testify that no description by any created thing can ever reveal Thee, and no praise which any being is able to utter can express Thee. Neither the comprehension of any one in the whole world, nor the intelligence of any of its peoples, can, as it befitteth Thee, gain admittance into the court of Thy holiness, or unravel Thy mystery.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
