<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Firmness in the Covenant on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-firmness-in-the-covenant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Firmness in the Covenant on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-firmness-in-the-covenant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00065STE in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab00065ste/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab00065ste/en/</guid>
      <description>O my Lord and my Hope! Help Thou Thy loved ones to be steadfast in Thy mighty Covenant, to remain faithful to Thy manifest Cause, and to carry out the commandments Thou didst set down for them in Thy Book of Splendors; that they may become banners of guidance and lamps of the Company above, wellsprings of Thine infinite wisdom, and stars that lead aright, as they shine down from the supernal sky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02342AWA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/en/</guid>
      <description>O compassionate God! Thanks be to Thee for Thou hast awakened and made me conscious. Thou hast given me a seeing eye and favored me with a hearing ear, hast led me to Thy kingdom and guided me to Thy path. Thou hast shown me the right way and caused me to enter the ark of deliverance. O God! Keep me steadfast and make me firm and staunch. Protect me from violent tests and preserve and shelter me in the strongly fortified fortress of Thy Covenant and Testament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB06211 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab06211/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab06211/en/</guid>
      <description>Make firm our steps, O Lord, in Thy path and strengthen Thou our hearts in Thine obedience. Turn our faces toward the beauty of Thy oneness, and gladden our bosoms with the signs of Thy divine unity. Adorn our bodies with the robe of Thy bounty, and remove from our eyes the veil of sinfulness, and give us the chalice of Thy grace; that the essence of all beings may sing Thy praise before the vision of Thy grandeur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07469 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/en/</guid>
      <description>He is the Mighty, the Pardoner, the Compassionate! O God, my God! Thou beholdest Thy servants in the abyss of perdition and error; where is Thy light of divine guidance, O Thou the Desire of the world? Thou knowest their helplessness and their feebleness; where is Thy power, O Thou in Whose grasp lie the powers of heaven and earth? I ask Thee, O Lord my God, by the splendor of the lights of Thy loving-kindness and the billows of the ocean of Thy knowledge and wisdom and by Thy Word wherewith Thou hast swayed the peoples of Thy dominion, to grant that I may be one of them that have observed Thy bidding in Thy Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07683 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O King of eternity, and the Maker of nations, and the Fashioner of every moldering bone! I pray Thee, by Thy Name through which Thou didst call all mankind unto the horizon of Thy majesty and glory, and didst guide Thy servants to the court of Thy grace and favors, to number me with such as have rid themselves from everything except Thyself, and have set themselves towards Thee, and have not been kept back by such misfortunes as were decreed by Thee, from turning in the direction of Thy gifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn10517 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10517/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10517/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! Give me to drink from the cup of Thy bestowal and illumine my face with the light of guidance. Make me firm in the path of faithfulness, assist me to be steadfast in Thy mighty Covenant, and suffer me to be numbered with Thy chosen servants. Unlock before my face the doors of abundance, grant me deliverance, and sustain me, through means I cannot reckon, from the treasuries of heaven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12496 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12496/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12496/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O King of eternity, and the Maker of nations,..
Le Tupu o le fa’avavau e, ma le Mataisau o malō, le Tufuga o ponaivi pala uma e, ia i lau Afio le vi’iga! Ou te ole atu ia te Oe i Lou Suafa na vala’auina ai e Oe tagata ola uma i le tafa’ilagi o Lau pule ma le mamalu, ma sa ta’ita’ia ai Au ‘au’auna i le maota o Lou alofa tunoa ma le finagalo lelei, ina ia faitauina fa’atasi a’u ma i latou ua vavae’esea mai mea uma vaganā Oe lava, ma fa’atumauina i latou ia te Oe, ma sa lē mafai ona taofia e uiga fa’alētonu e pei ona fa’atulafonoina e Oe, mai le liliu atu i le ala o Au mealaofa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
