<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH01313NAM on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh01313nam/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH01313NAM on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh01313nam/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thy name is my healing in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/en/</guid>
      <description>Thy name is my healing, O my God, and remembrance of Thee is my remedy. Nearness to Thee is my hope, and love for Thee is my companion. Thy mercy to me is my healing and my succor in both this world and the world to come. Thou, verily, art the All-Bountiful, the All-Knowing, the All-Wise.
(Source category: Healing) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 257)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thy name is my healing in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/es/</guid>
      <description>Tu nombre es mi curación, oh mi Dios, y el recuerdo de Ti es mi remedio. La proximidad a Ti es mi esperanza y el amor por Ti es mi compañero. Tu misericordia hacia mí es mi curación y mi socorro, tanto en este mundo como en el venidero. Tú, verdaderamente, eres el Todogeneroso, el Omnisciente, el Sapientísimo.
(Source category: Curación) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 11507)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thy name is my healing in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/eo/</guid>
      <description>Via nomo estas mia kuraco, ho mia Dio, kaj rememoro pri Vi mia medikamento. Proksimeco al Vi estas mia espero, kaj amo al Vi mia akompananto. Via mizerikordo al mi estas mia sanigo kaj mia helpo en tiu ĉi mondo kaj en la mondo venonta. Vi vere estas la Ĉio-dona, la Ĉio-scia, la Plejsaĝa.
(Source category: Sanigo) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 4311)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thy name is my healing in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/fy/</guid>
      <description>Jo namme is myn genêzing, o myn God, en it Jo te betinken is myn medisyn, Jo nei-oan te wêzen is myn hope, en leafde foar Jo is myn selskipsman. Jo genede is myn genêzing en myn stipe yn dizze wrâld en yn de wrâld dy&amp;rsquo;t komme sil. Jo, wierliken, binne de Alfoldedige, de Alwittende, de Alwize.
(Source category: Genêzing) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 6028)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thy name is my healing in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/nl/</guid>
      <description>Uw Naam is mijn genezing, o mijn God, en het U gedenken is mijn medicijn. U nabij te zijn is mijn hoop, en liefde voor U is mijn metgezel. Uw erbarmen met mij is mijn genezing en mijn steun in deze wereld en in de wereld die komen gaat. Gij zijt waarlijk de Almilddadige, de Alwetende, de Alwijze.
(Source category: Genezing) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9584)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thy name is my healing in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/healing/bh01313nam/pt/</guid>
      <description>Teu Nome é minha cura, ó meu Deus, e a lembrança de Ti, o meu remédio. Aproximar-me de Ti é minha esperança, e o meu amor por Ti, meu companheiro. A Tua misericórdia por mim é minha cura e meu socorro, neste mundo como no vindouro. Tu, em verdade, és o Todo-Generoso, o Omnisciente, a Suprema Sabedoria.
(Source category: Cura) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 1181)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
