<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Women on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-women/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Women on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-women/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10769 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/en/</guid>
      <description>O my Lord, my Beloved, my Desire! Befriend me in my loneliness and accompany me in my exile. Remove my sorrow. Cause me to be devoted to Thy beauty. Withdraw me from all else save Thee. Attract me through Thy fragrances of holiness. Cause me to be associated in Thy Kingdom with those who are severed from all else save Thee, who long to serve Thy sacred threshold and who stand to work in Thy Cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10769 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Sinjoro, mia Amato, mia Deziro! Konsolu min en mia soleco kaj akompanu min en mia ekzilo. Forigu mian ĉagrenon. Faru min fidela al Via beleco. Senigu min de ĉio krom Vi. Allogu min per la bonodoro de Via sankteco. Kunigu min en Via Regno kun tiuj, kiuj seniĝis de ĉio krom Vi kaj alstrebas servi ĉe Via sankta sojlo, pretaj labori por Via Afero. Ebligu al mi esti unu el Viaj servantinoj, kiu atingis Vian bonfavoron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10769 in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/it/</guid>
      <description>O mio Signore, mio Benamato, mio Desìo! Siimi Amico nella solitudine e Compagno nell’esilio. Allontana il mio dolore e fa’ ch’io sia devota alla Tua bellezza. Tienimi lontana da tutto fuorché da Te. Attirami con le Tue fragranze di santità. Fa’ ch’io sia unita, nel Tuo Regno, a coloro che sono distaccati da tutto fuorché da Te, che anelano a servire la Tua sacra soglia e che lavorano nella Tua Causa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH06429 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh06429/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh06429/en/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! Thou art He the fire of Whose love hath set ablaze the hearts of them who have recognized Thy unity, and the splendors of Whose countenance have illuminated the faces of such as have drawn nigh unto Thy court. How plenteous, O my God, is the stream of Thy knowledge! How sweet, O my Beloved, is the injury which, in my love for Thee, and for the sake of Thy pleasure, I suffer from the darts of the wicked doers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07426DRE in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh07426dre/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh07426dre/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou, at Whose dreadful majesty all things have trembled, in Whose grasp are the affairs of all men, towards Whose grace and mercy are set the faces of all Thy creatures! I entreat Thee, by Thy Name which Thou hast ordained to be the spirit of all names that are in the kingdom of names, to shield us from the whisperings of those who have turned away from Thee, and have repudiated the truth of Thy most august and most exalted Self, in this Revelation that hath caused the kingdom of Thy names to tremble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07426DRE in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh07426dre/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh07426dre/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij, voor Wiens ontzaglijke majesteit alle dingen beven, in Wiens greep de aangelegenheden van alle mensen liggen, naar Wiens genade en barmhartigheid het gelaat van al Uw schepselen is gericht! Ik smeek U, bij Uw Naam die Gij hebt verordend tot de geest van alle namen die in het koninkrijk van namen bestaan, ons in deze Openbaring die het koninkrijk van Uw namen heeft doen beven af te schermen van de influisteringen van hen die zich van U hebben afgekeerd en de waarheid van Uw grootste en verhevenste Wezen hebben verworpen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07663 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh07663/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh07663/en/</guid>
      <description>Magnified be Thy name, O Lord my God! Behold Thou mine eye expectant to gaze on the wonders of Thy mercy, and mine ear longing to hearken unto Thy sweet melodies, and my heart yearning for the living waters of Thy knowledge. Thou seest Thy handmaiden, O my God, standing before the habitation of Thy mercy, and calling upon Thee by Thy name which Thou hast chosen above all other names and set up over all that are in heaven and on earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08852 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh08852/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh08852/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory to Thee, O my God! One of Thy handmaidens, who hath believed in Thee and in Thy signs, hath entered beneath the shadow of the tree of Thy oneness. Give her to quaff, O my God, by Thy Name, the Manifest and the Hidden, of Thy choice sealed Wine that it may take her away from her own self, and make her to be entirely devoted to Thy remembrance, and wholly detached from any one beside Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08852 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh08852/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh08852/nl/</guid>
      <description>Glorie zij U, o mijn God! Een van Uw dienaressen, die in U en in Uw tekenen gelooft, heeft zich onder de schaduw van de boom van Uw één-zijn begeven. Geef haar, o mijn God, bij Uw Naam, de Kenbare en de Verborgene, volop te drinken van Uw uitgelezen verzegelde wijn, dat die haar zal wegvoeren van haar eigen wezen, en maak haar geheel toegewijd aan het U gedenken en geheel onthecht van eenieder buiten U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09162 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou Whose face is the object of the adoration of all that yearn after Thee, Whose presence is the hope of such as are wholly devoted to Thy will, Whose nearness is the desire of all that have drawn nigh unto Thy court, Whose countenance is the companion of those who have recognized Thy truth, Whose name is the mover of the souls that long to behold Thy face, Whose voice is the true life of Thy lovers, the words of Whose mouth are as the waters of life unto all who are in heaven and on earth!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09162 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh Tú, Cuyo rostro es el objeto de la adoración de todos los que Te anhelan, Cuya presencia es la esperanza de quienes están completamente consagrados a Tu voluntad, Cuya proximidad es el deseo de cuantos se han acercado a Tu corte, Cuyo semblante es el compañero de aquellos que han reconocido Tu verdad, Cuyo nombre es el impulsor de las almas que ansían contemplar Tu rostro, Cuya voz es la verdadera vida de Tus amantes, las palabras de Cuya boca son como aguas de vida para todos los que están en el cielo y en la tierra!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09162 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij, Wiens gelaat het voorwerp van aanbidding is van allen die naar U smachten, Wiens tegenwoordigheid de hoop is van hen die Uw wil geheel zijn toegewijd, Wiens nabijheid het verlangen is van allen die Uw hof zijn genaderd, Wiens aangezicht de metgezel is van hen die Uw waarheid hebben erkend, Wiens Naam de drijfveer is van de zielen die ernaar hunkeren Uw gelaat te aanschouwen, Wiens stem het ware leven is van Uw minnaars, de woorden uit Wiens mond als levend water zijn voor allen in de hemel en op aarde!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09399 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09399/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09399/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O my God! My face hath been set towards Thy face, and my face is, verily, Thy face, and my call is Thy call, and my Revelation Thy Revelation, and my self Thy Self, and my Cause Thy Cause, and my behest Thy behest, and my Being Thy Being, and my sovereignty Thy sovereignty, and my glory Thy glory, and my power Thy power. I implore Thee, O Thou Fashioner of the nations and the King of eternity, to guard Thy handmaidens within the tabernacle of Thy chastity, and to cancel such of their deeds as are unworthy of Thy days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09399 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09399/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09399/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Gloria sea a Ti, oh mi Dios! Mi rostro se ha dirigido hacia Tu rostro, y mi rostro es, ciertamente, Tu rostro, y mi llamamiento es Tu llamamiento, y mi Revelación, Tu Revelación, y mi ser, Tu Ser, y mi Causa, Tu Causa, y mi mandato, Tu mandato, y mi Existencia, Tu Existencia, y mi soberanía, Tu soberanía, y mi gloria, Tu gloria, y mi poder, Tu poder. Yo te imploro, oh Tú Modelador de las naciones y Rey de la eternidad, que resguardes a Tus siervas en el tabernáculo de Tu castidad, y canceles aquellos de sus actos que sean indignos de Tus días.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10231 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh10231/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh10231/en/</guid>
      <description>Thou seest, O my God, how the wrongs committed by such of Thy creatures as have turned their backs to Thee have come in between Him in Whom Thy Godhead is manifest and Thy servants. Send down upon them, O my Lord, what will cause them to be busied with each others&amp;rsquo; concerns. Let, then, their violence be confined to their own selves, that the land and they that dwell therein may find peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10231 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh10231/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh10231/es/</guid>
      <description>Tú ves, oh mi Dios, cómo los males cometidos por aquellas de Tus criaturas que Te han vuelto la espalda se han interpuesto entre Aquel en Quien Tu Deidad está manifiesta y Tus siervos. Haz descender sobre ellos, oh mi Señor, aquello que haga que se ocupen en sus propios afanes. Haz, pues, que su violencia se limite a ellos mismos, para que la tierra y los que en ella habitan encuentren paz.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
