<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BB00018FOR on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bb00018for/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BB00018FOR on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bb00018for/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00018FOR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/en/</guid>
      <description>#Parents
I beg Thy forgiveness, O my God, and implore pardon after the manner Thou wishest Thy servants to direct themselves to Thee. I beg of Thee to wash away our sins as befitteth Thy Lordship, and to forgive me, my parents, and those who in Thy estimation have entered the abode of Thy love in a manner which is worthy of Thy transcendent sovereignty and well beseemeth the glory of Thy celestial power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00018FOR in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/fr/</guid>
      <description>Ô mon Dieu, je sollicite ta clémence et j’implore ton pardon ainsi que tu souhaites entendre tes serviteurs s’adresser à toi. Lave-nous de nos péchés, je t’en supplie, comme il sied à ton empire et accorde-moi ton pardon, ainsi qu’à mes parents et à ceux qui, à tes yeux, se sont réfugiés en ton amour, comme il convient à ta souveraineté transcendante et à la gloire de ton pouvoir céleste. Ô mon Dieu, tu as inspiré mon âme pour qu’elle t’adresse cette supplique, et sans toi, je ne pourrai faire appel à toi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00018FOR in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik smeek om Uw vergeving, o mijn God, en bid om vergiffenis zoals Gij wenst dat Uw dienaren zich tot U wenden. Ik smeek U onze zonden weg te nemen zoals het U, Heer, past en vergeving te schenken aan mij, mijn ouders, en degenen die naar Uw oordeel de verblijfplaats van Uw liefde hebben betreden op een wijze die Uw alles te boven gaande soevereiniteit waardig is en de heerlijkheid van Uw hemelse macht betaamt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
