<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB00065KIN on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00065kin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB00065KIN on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00065kin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00065KIN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! Praise be unto Thee for kindling the fire of divine love in the Holy Tree on the summit of the loftiest mount: that Tree which is “neither of the East nor of the West,”¹ that fire which blazed out till the flame of it soared upward to the Concourse on high, and from it those realities caught the light of guidance, and cried out: “Verily have we perceived a fire on the slope of Mount Sinai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00065KIN in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/nl/</guid>
      <description>O God, mijn God! Geprezen zijt Gij dat Gij het vuur van goddelijke liefde in de Heilige Boom op de top van de verhevenste berg hebt ontstoken; die Boom die “noch van het Oosten, noch van het Westen” is, dat vuur dat oplaaide tot de vlam ervan tot de hemelse Scharen omhoog steeg, en deze werkelijkheden daaruit het licht van leiding opvingen, waarna zij uitriepen: “Waarlijk hebben wij een vuur op de helling van de berg Sinaï ontwaard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00065KIN in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Deus, meu Deus! Louvores a Ti por haveres ateado o fogo do amor divino na Árvore Sagrada - a qual “não é nem do Oriente nem do Ocidente”, sita no cume da mais elevada montanha; fogo esse que se abrasou até a sua flama se elevar e atingir a Assembleia do alto, cujas realidades dela colheram a luz da guia e bradaram: “Percebemos, verdadeiramente, um fogo na encosta do Monte Sinai”.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
