<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB00156LOW on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00156low/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB00156LOW on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00156low/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00156LOW in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/en/</guid>
      <description>Thou seest me, O my God, bowed down in lowliness, humbling myself before Thy commandments, submitting to Thy sovereignty, trembling at the might of Thy dominion, fleeing from Thy wrath, entreating Thy grace, relying upon Thy forgiveness, shaking with awe at Thy fury. I implore Thee with a throbbing heart, with streaming tears and a yearning soul, and in complete detachment from all things, to make Thy lovers as rays of light across Thy realms, and to aid Thy chosen servants to exalt Thy Word, that their faces may turn beauteous and bright with splendor, that their hearts may be filled with mysteries, and that every soul may lay down its burden of sin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00156LOW in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/nl/</guid>
      <description>Gij ziet mij nederig geknield, o mijn God, deemoedig voor Uw geboden, onderworpen aan Uw soevereiniteit, huiverend voor de macht van Uw heerschappij, vluchtend voor Uw gramschap, smekend om Uw genade, vertrouwend op Uw vergiffenis, bevend van ontzag voor Uw toorn. Ik smeek U met bonzend hart, stromende tranen en smachtende ziel, en in volledige onthechting van alle dingen, om Uw minnaars te maken als lichtstralen door al Uw rijken, en Uw uitverkoren dienaren te helpen Uw Woord te verheerlijken, opdat hun gelaat mag stralen van pracht en schoonheid, hun hart vervuld mag worden van mysteriën, en iedere ziel zijn zondenlast mag afleggen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00156LOW in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/pt/</guid>
      <description>Vês-me, ó meu Deus, prostrado em submissão, humilde ante os Teus mandamentos, submisso ante a Tua soberania, estremecendo frente ao poder de Teu domínio, fugindo de Tua ira, suplicando Tua graça, confiando no Teu perdão e trémulo de temor ante a Tua fúria. Imploro-te, com o coração a palpitar, os olhos plenos de lágrimas, a alma anelante e com absoluto desprendimento de tudo, que faças daqueles que Te amam raios de luz através dos Teus reinos e que auxilies os Teus servos eleitos a exaltarem a Tua Palavra, para que suas frontes se façam formosas e resplandecentes, os seus corações fiquem repletos de mistérios, e toda a alma se livre do fardo dos seus pecados.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
