<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH09162 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09162/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH09162 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09162/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09162 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou Whose face is the object of the adoration of all that yearn after Thee, Whose presence is the hope of such as are wholly devoted to Thy will, Whose nearness is the desire of all that have drawn nigh unto Thy court, Whose countenance is the companion of those who have recognized Thy truth, Whose name is the mover of the souls that long to behold Thy face, Whose voice is the true life of Thy lovers, the words of Whose mouth are as the waters of life unto all who are in heaven and on earth!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09162 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh Tú, Cuyo rostro es el objeto de la adoración de todos los que Te anhelan, Cuya presencia es la esperanza de quienes están completamente consagrados a Tu voluntad, Cuya proximidad es el deseo de cuantos se han acercado a Tu corte, Cuyo semblante es el compañero de aquellos que han reconocido Tu verdad, Cuyo nombre es el impulsor de las almas que ansían contemplar Tu rostro, Cuya voz es la verdadera vida de Tus amantes, las palabras de Cuya boca son como aguas de vida para todos los que están en el cielo y en la tierra!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09162 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09162/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij, Wiens gelaat het voorwerp van aanbidding is van allen die naar U smachten, Wiens tegenwoordigheid de hoop is van hen die Uw wil geheel zijn toegewijd, Wiens nabijheid het verlangen is van allen die Uw hof zijn genaderd, Wiens aangezicht de metgezel is van hen die Uw waarheid hebben erkend, Wiens Naam de drijfveer is van de zielen die ernaar hunkeren Uw gelaat te aanschouwen, Wiens stem het ware leven is van Uw minnaars, de woorden uit Wiens mond als levend water zijn voor allen in de hemel en op aarde!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
