<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Naw-Rúz on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-naw-r%C3%BAz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Naw-Rúz on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-naw-r%C3%BAz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03908 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/naw-r%C3%BAz/bh03908/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/naw-r%C3%BAz/bh03908/en/</guid>
      <description>##Naw-Rúz *(Naw-Rúz, March 21, is the first day of the Bahá&amp;rsquo;í year.)
Praised be Thou, O my God, that Thou hast ordained Naw-Rúz as a festival unto those who have observed the Fast for love of Thee and abstained from all that is abhorrent unto thee. Grant, O my Lord, that the fire of Thy love and the heat produced by the Fast enjoined by Thee may inflame them in Thy Cause, and make them to be occupied with Thy praise and with remembrance of Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn10366 in Svenska</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sv/bpn10366/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sv/bpn10366/</guid>
      <description>*Naw-Rúz, den 21 mars, är årets första dag i bahá’í-kalendern. Prisad vare Du, o min Gud, för att Du har föreskrivit Naw-Rúz som en högtid för dem, som har iakttagit fastan av kärlek till Dig och avhållit sig från allt som är Dig motbjudande. Giv, o min Herre, att Din kärleks eld och den hetta som framkallats av fastan, påbjuden av Dig, upptänder dem för Din sak och förmår dem att ägna sig åt att prisa Dig och hålla Dig i åminnelse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn11693 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/es/bpn11693/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/es/bpn11693/</guid>
      <description>Alabado seas, oh mi Dios, por haber ordenado Naw-Rúz como festividad para aquellos que han observado el ayuno por amor a Ti y se han abstenido de todo lo que Te es detestable. Permite, oh mi Señor, que el fuego de Tu amor y el calor producido por el ayuno ordenado por Ti les enardezca en Tu Causa y les haga ocuparse de Tu alabanza y Tu recuerdo. Ya que los has adornado, oh mi Señor, con el ornamento del ayuno prescrito por Ti, adórnalos también con el ornamento de Tu aceptación, mediante Tu gracia y munífico favor, pues las acciones de las personas dependen por entero de Tu complacencia y están condicionados a Tu voluntad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12196 in Bahasa Melayu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ms/bpn12196/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ms/bpn12196/</guid>
      <description>Pujian bagi-Mu, Ya Tuhanku, kerana Engkau telah menetapkan Naw-Rúz sebagai satu hari raya bagi mereka yang telah berpuasa kerana cinta kepada-Mu dan telah menjauhkan diri daripada segala sesuatu yang tak Engkau sukai. Izinkanlah, Ya Tuhanku, api cinta-Mu dan haba yang dihasilkan kerana puasa yang telah Engkau tetapkan agar menyalakan semangat mereka dalam Akidah-Mu, dan membuat mereka asyik dengan pujian dan pengingatan kepada-Mu.
Kerana Engkau telah menghiasi mereka, Ya Tuhanku, dengan perhiasan puasa yang ditetapkan oleh-Mu, maka hiasilah mereka dengan perhiasan penerimaan-Mu melalui kurnia dan rahmat-Mu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12733 in Iban</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/iba/bpn12733/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/iba/bpn12733/</guid>
      <description>*(Naw-Rúz meh hari keterubah ba taun Bahá’í)
Puji meh Nuan, O Petara aku, laban Nuan udah ngeletak Naw-Rúz nyadika pengerami ke sida ti udah ngintu Puasa ketegal pengerindu sida ke Nuan lalu nagang diri ari semua utai ti kamah ba Nuan. Kemendarka, O Tuhan aku, api pengerindu Nuan sereta pengangat ti dikeluar ari Puasa ti diasuh Nuan tau ngemauka sida dalam Pengawa Nuan, lalu ngasuh sida kiruh enggau puji Nuan sereta pengingat Nuan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13241 in Slovensky</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sk/bpn13241/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sk/bpn13241/</guid>
      <description>Chvála buď Tebe, ó môj Bože, že si určil Naw-Rúz za slávnosť pre tých, ktorí dodržiavali pôst z lásky k Tebe a zdržiavali sa všetkého, čo sa Ti prieči. Daj, ó môj Pane, aby ich žiar a oheň Tvojej lásky, ktoré v nich Tebou nariadený pôst roznietil, zapálili pre Tvoju vec, a učiň, aby sa zaoberali Tvojou chválou a spomienkou na Teba. Keďže si ich okrášlil, ó môj Pane, ozdobou pôstu, ktorý si predpísal, ozdob ich tiež ozdobou Svojho prijatia skrze Svoju milosť a štedrú láskavosť.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13247 in Slovensky</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sk/bpn13247/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sk/bpn13247/</guid>
      <description>On je navždy Žijúci, navždy Pretrvávajúci, Sebedostačujúci. Boh dosvedčuje jednotu Svojej božskosti a jedinečnosť Svojej bytosti. Na tróne večnosti, z nedosiahnuteľných výšin Svojho postavenia, Jeho jazyk vyhlasuje, že niet iného Boha okrem Neho. On sám, nezávisle od všetkého ostatného, vždy dosvedčoval Svoju jedinosť, zjavoval Svoju povahu a oslavoval Svoju podstatu. On je, vskutku, Všemohúci, nadovšetko Mocný, Prekrásny. On panuje Svojim služobníkom a stojí nad Svojím tvorstvom. V Jeho ruke spočíva zdroj právomoci a pravdy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13571 in Føroyar</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/fo/bpn13571/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/fo/bpn13571/</guid>
      <description>*Naw-Rúz er tann fyrsti dagurin á Baha&amp;rsquo;i árinum.
Prísaður veri Tú, O mín Gud, at Tú hevur fyriskipað Naw-Rúz sum eina høgtíð fyri tey ið hava hildið føstuna av kærleika fyri Tær og afturhildið seg frá øllum tí sum er Tær andstygd. Gev, O mín Harri, at eldur kærleiks Tíns og hitin framleiddur av føstuni áløgd av Tær kann seta tey í loga í Søk Tínari, og fáa tey at gerast upptikin av Tínari lovprísan og av minning um Teg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13658 in Lëtzebuergesch</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/lb/bpn13658/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/lb/bpn13658/</guid>
      <description>*Naw-Rúz, den 20. oder 21. Mäerz, den éischten Dag vum Bahá&amp;rsquo;í Joer.
Gelueft bass Du, o mäi Gott, dass Du Naw-Rúz deenen zum Fest bestëmmt hues, déi d’Faaschten aus Léift zu Dir agehal hunn a sech allem enthal hunn, wat s Du haass. Erlab, o mäi Gott, dass d’Feier vun Denger Léift an d’Hëtzt, déi sech aus deem vun Dir bestëmmte Faaschten entwéckelt, si an Denger Saach entflamen, an dass si sech doduerch Dengem Luef an Dengem Gedenken higinn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn1771 in Íslenska</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/is/bpn1771/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/is/bpn1771/</guid>
      <description>*(Naw-rúz, fyrsti dagur bahá’í nýársins, hefst sama dag og jafndægur á vori verða í Teheran, fæðingarborg Bahá’u’lláh.)
Lofaður sért Þú, ó Guð minn, fyrir að hafa gert naw-rúz að hátíð fyrir þá sem hafa haldið föstuna vegna ástar á Þér og neitað sér um allt sem Þér er andstyggð. Gef, ó Drottinn minn, að eldur ástar Þinnar og funinn sem glæddist á föstunni sem Þú fyrirskipaðir, megi upptendra þá í málstað Þínum og gera þá upptekna af lofgjörð til Þín og hugsun um Þig.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn2753 in Magyar</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/hu/bpn2753/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/hu/bpn2753/</guid>
      <description>*„A Naw-Rúz ünnepséget tartsátok március 21-én napnyugta előtt. Nincs semmi köze a Tizenkilenc Napi Ünnephez. Az utóbbi adminisztratív jelentőségű, míg a Naw-Rúz az újévi ünnepségünk, a vendégszeretet és az öröm ünnepe.” —egy Shoghi Effendi nevében írt levélből
Dicsőítünk Téged, ó, Istenem, hogy a Naw-Rúzt ünnepnek rendelted azoknak, kik Irántad való szeretetből megtartották a böjtöt, és tartózkodtak mindentől, mi utálatos Előtted. Add, ó, Uram, hogy szereteted lángja és a parázs, amit az Általad rendelt böjt felszított, lelkesítse lángolón őket Ügyed szolgálatában, és tegye őket alkalmassá arra, hogy odaadással dicsőítsenek Téged s megemlékezzenek Rólad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn3243 in Afrikaans</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/af/bpn3243/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/af/bpn3243/</guid>
      <description>*Naw-Rúz, 21 Maart, is die eerste dag van die Bahá&amp;rsquo;í jaar.
Gelof sy U, o my God, dat U Naw-Rúz as &amp;rsquo;n feesdag ingestel het vir diegene wat uit liefde vir U die vas onderhou het en van alles wat vir U verafskuwend is weggebly het. Gee, o my Here, dat die vuur van U liefde en die hitte voortgebring deur die vas wat deur U gelas is, hulle in U Saak mag laat ontbrand, en maak dat hulle met U lof en met aandenking aan U besig mag wees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn3596 in Norsk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/no/bpn3596/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/no/bpn3596/</guid>
      <description>*Naw-rúz, den 21. mars, er den første dag i bahá&amp;rsquo;í året, en gledens dag.
Lovet være du, o min Gud, for at du har forordnet naw-rúz som en høytid for dem som har holdt fasten av kjærlighet til deg og avholdt seg fra alt som er avskyelig for deg. Gi, o min Herre, at din kjærlighets ild og varmen fremkalt av fasten som du har påbudt, kan oppflamme dem for din Sak, og gjøre dem beskjeftiget med å prise deg og ihukomme deg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn4540 in Filipino</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tl/bpn4540/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tl/bpn4540/</guid>
      <description>*Ang Naw-Rúz, Marso21, ay ang unang araw ng taon ng Bahá’í.
Purihin ka, O aking Diyos, sa pag-aatas Mo na ang Naw-Rúz ay maging isang kapistahan sa mga nagsasagawa ng pag-aayuno nang dahil sa pag-ibig sa Iyo at nagsilayo sa lahat ng kasuklam-suklam sa Iyo. Loobin, O aking Panginoon na ang apoy ng Iyong pag-ibig at ang init na nalikha ng pag-aayunong iniatas Mo ay makapagparubdob sa kanila sa Iyong Kapakanan, at gawin silang abala sa pagpuri sa Iyo at sa paggunita sa Iyo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn5323 in Bosanski</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/bs/bpn5323/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/bs/bpn5323/</guid>
      <description>##Naw-Rúz
*‚Naw-Ruz se proslavlja 21. marta prije zalaska sunca i ne treba ga vezivati za Praznik 19 dana. Praznik 19 dana je administrativne prirode, dok je Naw-Ruz proslava naše Nove godine, dan veselja i dobrodošlice&amp;quot;. ‚U vezi Naw-Ruz-a: Ako ekvinocij pada na 21. mart prije zalaska sunca, Naw- Ruz se slavi istoga dana. Ukoliko pada nakon zalaska sunca, Naw- Ruz će se, kao što je rekao Bah{’u’ll{h, slaviti 22. marta. Što se tiče usvajanja standardnog vremena, to je odluka koju mora donijeti Univerzalna Kuća Pravde.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn5766 in Català</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ca/bpn5766/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ca/bpn5766/</guid>
      <description>##NAW-RÚZ
*Naw-Rúz és la festa què es celebra el 21 de març. Significa Any Nou i és el primer dia de l’any bahá’í.
Lloat siguis Tu, oh Déu meu, per haver ordenat Naw-Rúz com a festivitat per aquells qui han observat el dejuni per amor a Tu i s’han abstingut de tot el què T’és detestable. Permet, oh Senyor meu, que el foc del Teu amor i l’escalfor produïda pel dejuni ordenat per Tu els inflami en la Teva Causa i els faci ocupar-se de la Teva lloança i record.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn671 in Deutsch</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/de/bpn671/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/de/bpn671/</guid>
      <description>Gepriesen seiest Du, o mein Gott, da Du Naw-Rúz denen zum Fest bestimmt hast, die das Fasten aus Liebe zu Dir hielten und alles mieden, was Du verabscheust. Gib, o mein Gott, dass das Feuer Deiner Liebe und die Glut, die das von Dir befohlene Fasten erzeugte, sie in Deiner Sache entflamme und sie bestimme, sich Deinem Lobpreis und Deinem Gedenken hinzugeben. Da Du sie schmücktest mit der Zier des von Dir vorgeschriebenen Fastens, so schmücke sie durch Deine Gnade und großmütige Gunst auch mit Deiner Annahme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6991 in Fiji</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/fj/bpn6991/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/fj/bpn6991/</guid>
      <description>#NA I MATAI NI SIGA NI DUA NA YABAKI VAKA-BAHÁ’Í ##‘NAW-RÚZ‘
*(Na i Matai ni Siga ni Yabaki vou Vaka-Bahá&amp;rsquo;í - ‘Naw-Rúz&amp;rsquo;, o ya e na i ka 21 ni Maji, sa i koya na i matai ni siga e na i vola ni vula Vaka-Bahá&amp;rsquo;í.)
Mo ni sa vakalagilagi, O i Kemuni na noqu Kalou, ni O ni sa digitaka me siga ni soqo ni marau na i Matai ni Siga oqo (Naw-Rúz) vei ira ka ra dau vakamuria na lolo e na nodra lomani Kemuni ka vakatatabutaki ira mai na veika e tawakilikili vei Kemuni.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn7467 in Polski</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/pl/bpn7467/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/pl/bpn7467/</guid>
      <description>*Naw-Rúz jest pierwszym dniem roku bahaickiego obchodzonym w dniu marcowej równonocy.
Pochwalony bądź, o mój Boże, żeś ustanowił Naw-Rúz jako święto dla tych, którzy zachowali Post z miłości do Ciebie i powstrzymali się od wszystkiego, co budzi Twoją odrazę. Spraw, o mój Panie, aby ogień Twojej miłości i ciepło wzbudzone przez Post nakazany przez Ciebie, rozpaliły ich w Twojej Sprawie i sprawiły, że zajmować się będą wielbieniem Ciebie i pamiętaniem o Tobie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn7589 in Suomi</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/fi/bpn7589/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/fi/bpn7589/</guid>
      <description>Ylistetty olet Sinä, oi Jumalani, että olet määrännyt Naw-Rúzin juhlapyhäksi niille, jotka ovat noudattaneet paastoa rakkaudesta Sinuun ja pysytelleet erillään kaikesta, mikä ei ole Sinulle mieleen. Suo, oi Herrani, että Sinun rakkautesi tuli ja säätämäsi paastoamisen synnyttämä kuumuus sytyttäisivät heidät asiassasi ja valtaisivat heidän mielensä, niin että he aina ylistäisivät ja muistelisivat Sinua. Koska olet kaunistanut heidät, oi Herrani, säätämäsi paaston koristein, kaunista heidät myös hyväksymisesi koristein armostasi ja anteliaasta suopeudestasi, sillä ihmisten teot ovat kaikki riippuvaisia Sinun mielisuosiostasi ja sidoksissa Sinun käskyysi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn7590 in Suomi</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/fi/bpn7590/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/fi/bpn7590/</guid>
      <description>Oi Herra, minun Herrani! Tämä on päivä, jonka Sinun Pyhä kielesi ja Kirkkauden kynäsi on pyhittänyt ja tehnyt siitä taivaallisten siunausten sekä jumalallisen laupeuden ja suosion päivän. Olet kunnioittanut sitä antimillasi, suonut sille armosi, kietonut sen kirkkauteesi ja tehnyt siitä ilon ja riemun päivän niille, jotka ovat kääntyneet Sinun jumalallisen ilmoituksesi puoleen, niin että sydämet siitä ilahtuisivat, että onnellisuuden säteily valaisisi niiden elämää, jotka muistavat kirkkautesi ilmaisun Sinun pyhällä vuorellasi. Pyhitä se, oi Herra, armollasi ja tee siitä ilon ja siunauksen päivä rakastetuillesi, jotka ovat pysyneet lujina ja horjumattomina Sinun liitossasi, ystävillesi, jotka ovat laulaneet Sinun ylistystäsi, ja erityisesti tälle palvelijallesi, joka on kääntänyt kasvonsa pyhän valtakuntasi puoleen, anonut Sinun mahtisi ja valtasi kirkkautta, kiertänyt Sinun suuruutesi valtaistuinta ja kumartunut maahan Sinun jumalallisen armeliaisuutesi kynnyksellä.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn7935 in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/it/bpn7935/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/it/bpn7935/</guid>
      <description>*(Naw-Rúz, 21 marzo, è il primo giorno dell’anno bahá’í).
Lodato Tu sia, mio Dio, Che destinasti il Naw-Rúz a festività per coloro che hanno osservato il digiuno per amor Tuo e si sono astenuti da tutto ciò che aborri. Concedi, o mio Signore, che il fuoco del Tuo amore e il calore prodotto dal digiuno da Te comandato li infiammino alla Tua Causa e fa’ che si dedichino alla Tua lode e al Tuo ricordo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8232 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8232/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8232/</guid>
      <description>I am the Most Holy, the Most Great, the Most Glorious.
Praise be to Thee, O my God, that Thou hast ordained this day as a festival unto the favoured among Thy servants and the sincere among Thy loved ones. Thou hast called this day by that Name whereby all created things have been subdued and the breezes of Thy Revelation have been wafted between earth and heaven, a Name through which all that hath been recorded in Thy Holy Books and Sacred Scriptures hath been made manifest, and which Thy Messengers and Thy Chosen Ones have foretold, that all men might be made ready to behold Thee, to turn towards the ocean of Thy reunion, to stand before the seat of Thy throne, and to hear Thy wondrous call from the Dayspring of Thine invisible Self and the Dawning-Place of Thine Essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8233 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8233/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8233/</guid>
      <description>He is the Most Holy, the Most Mighty, the Most Exalted.
Praise be unto Thee, O Thou Who art the Lord of the world and the Ruler of the nations! I testify that Thou hast from eternity been sanctified above the mention of all created things and exalted beyond the loftiest descriptions of Thy creatures. Whensoever Thy devoted servants sought to ascend unto the station of Thy recognition, the hosts of Thy knowledge barred their way; and whensoever Thy near ones desired to gain admittance to the heaven of Thy nearness, the overpowering majesty of Thine utterance kept them back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8234 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8234/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8234/</guid>
      <description>He is the Ever-Living, the Ever-Abiding, the Self-Subsisting.
God testifieth to the unity of His Godhood and to the singleness of His own Being. On the throne of eternity, from the inaccessible heights of His station, His tongue proclaimeth that there is none other God but Him. He Himself, independently of all else, hath ever been a witness unto His own oneness, the revealer of His own nature, the glorifier of His own essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8235 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8235/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8235/</guid>
      <description>He is the Sovereign King, the Holy of Holies.
Praise be unto Thee, O Lord my God! This is that Day among Thy Days and that Hour among Thy blessed Hours which Thou hast reserved for Thine own Self, related to Thine own Being, and exalted in station, that Thy Name may endure and Thy sovereignty be made manifest. Thou hast made this Day to be the source of all days, inasmuch as Thou hast showered upon it the revelations of the Throne of Thy majesty and the signs of Thy transcendent favour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9307 in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/fr/bpn9307/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/fr/bpn9307/</guid>
      <description>##Naw-Rúz
Loué sois-tu, Ô mon Dieu ! Tu as fait du Naw-Rúz un jour de fête pour ceux qui ont observé le jeûne par amour pour toi et se sont abstenus de tout ce que tu réprouves. Ô mon Seigneur, permets que le feu de ton amour et la chaleur produite par le jeûne que tu as prescrit, les enflamment en ta cause. Qu’ils se consacrent à ta mention et à ton souvenir !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9742 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nl/bpn9742/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nl/bpn9742/</guid>
      <description>Geprezen zijt Gij, o mijn God, dat Gij Naw-Rúz hebt ingesteld als een feestdag voor hen die de Vasten hebben gehouden uit liefde voor U en zich hebben onthouden van al wat U weerzinwekkend is. Vergun, o mijn Heer, dat het vuur van Uw liefde en de gloed die de door U opgelegde Vasten teweeg heeft gebracht hen in vlam zet voor Uw Zaak, en laat hen zich bezighouden met het U eren en gedenken.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
