<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB02326 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab02326/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB02326 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab02326/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02326 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/en/</guid>
      <description>He is God! O God, my God! These are servants attracted in Thy days by the fragrances of Thy holiness, enkindled with the flame burning in Thy holy tree, responding to Thy voice, uttering Thy praise, awakened by Thy breeze, stirred by Thy sweet savors, beholding Thy signs, understanding Thy Revelation and assured of Thy loving-kindness. Their eyes, O Lord, are fixed upon Thy kingdom of effulgent glory and their faces turned toward Thy dominion on high, their hearts beating with the love of Thy radiant and glorious beauty, their souls consumed with the flame of Thy love, O Lord of this world and the world hereafter, their lives seething with the ardor of their longing for Thee, and their tears poured forth for Thy sake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02326 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/nl/</guid>
      <description>Hij is God! O God, mijn God! Dit zijn dienaren die in Uw dagen bekoord zijn door de geuren van Uw heiligheid, die aangestoken zijn door de vlam die brandt in Uw heilige boom, gehoor geven aan Uw stem, Uw lof uiten, gewekt zijn door Uw bries, geroerd zijn door Uw zoete geuren, Uw tekenen aanschouwen, Uw verzen begrijpen, Uw woorden beluisteren, in Uw Openbaring geloven en zeker zijn van Uw goedertierenheid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02326 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab02326/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ele é Deus! Ó Deus, meu Deus! Estes são servos atraídos em Teus dias pelo perfume da Tua santidade, acesos com a chama que resplandece em Tua santa árvore, atendendo à Tua voz, expressando-Te louvor, despertados pela Tua brisa, animados pelas Tuas doces fragrâncias, contemplando os Teus sinais, compreendendo os Teus versículos, escutando as Tuas palavras, acreditando na Tua Revelação e confiantes da Tua misericórdia. Os seus olhos, ó Senhor, fitam o Teu reino de fulgente glória, e as suas faces volvem-se para o Teu domínio nas alturas; os seus corações pulsam de amor pela Tua beleza radiante e gloriosa; as suas almas consomem-se com a chama do Teu amor, ó Senhor deste mundo e do vindouro, as suas vidas fervem com o ardor da sua ânsia por Ti, e as suas lágrimas vertem por Tua causa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
