<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH00778 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh00778/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH00778 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh00778/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00778 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O Lord my God! These are the days whereon Thou hast bidden all men to observe the Fast, that through it they may purify their souls and rid themselves of all attachment to anyone but Thee, and that out of their hearts may ascend that which will be worthy of the court of Thy majesty and may well beseem the seat of the revelation of Thy oneness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00778 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Gloria sea a Ti, oh Señor mi Dios! Tú has ordenado a todos, oh mi Dios, observar el ayuno durante estos días, para que mediante él purifiquen sus almas y se liberen de todo apego a otro que no seas Tú, y que de sus corazones ascienda lo que sea digno de la corte de Tu majestad y propio de la sede de la revelación de Tu unicidad. Permite, oh mi Señor, que este ayuno llegue a ser un río de aguas vivifi-cantes y produzca la virtud con que lo has dotado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00778 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/nl/</guid>
      <description>Glorie zij U, o Heer mijn God! Dit zijn de dagen waarop Gij alle mensen hebt geboden te vasten, dat zij daardoor hun ziel kunnen zuiveren en zich van alle gehechtheid aan iemand buiten U kunnen ontdoen, en datgene uit hun hart omhoog mag komen wat het hof van Uw majesteit waardig is en de zetel van de openbaring van Uw één-zijn past. Geef, o mijn God, dat deze vasten een rivier van levengevend water moge worden en de deugd moge voortbrengen waarmee Gij hem hebt begiftigd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
