<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Teaching on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-teaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Teaching on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-teaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00156LOW in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/en/</guid>
      <description>Thou seest me, O my God, bowed down in lowliness, humbling myself before Thy commandments, submitting to Thy sovereignty, trembling at the might of Thy dominion, fleeing from Thy wrath, entreating Thy grace, relying upon Thy forgiveness, shaking with awe at Thy fury. I implore Thee with a throbbing heart, with streaming tears and a yearning soul, and in complete detachment from all things, to make Thy lovers as rays of light across Thy realms, and to aid Thy chosen servants to exalt Thy Word, that their faces may turn beauteous and bright with splendor, that their hearts may be filled with mysteries, and that every soul may lay down its burden of sin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00189AID in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00189aid/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00189aid/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! Aid Thou Thy trusted servants to have loving and tender hearts. Help them to spread, amongst all the nations of the earth, the light of guidance that cometh from the Company on high. Verily, Thou art the Strong, the Powerful, the Mighty, the All-Subduing, the Ever-Giving. Verily, Thou art the Generous, the Gentle, the Tender, the Most Bountiful.
(Source category: Teaching) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 327)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB05167 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab05167/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab05167/en/</guid>
      <description>Thou knowest, O God, and art my witness that I have no desire in my heart save to attain Thy good pleasure, to be confirmed in servitude unto Thee, to consecrate myself in Thy service, to labor in Thy great vineyard and to sacrifice all in Thy path. Thou art the All-Knowing and the All-Seeing. I have no wish save to turn my steps, in my love for Thee, towards the mountains and the deserts to loudly proclaim the advent of Thy Kingdom, and to raise Thy call amidst all men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB05805SER in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab05805ser/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab05805ser/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God, aid Thou Thy servant to raise up the Word, and to refute what is vain and false, to establish the truth, to spread the sacred verses abroad, reveal the splendors, and make the morning&amp;rsquo;s light to dawn in the hearts of the righteous. Thou art, verily, the Generous, the Forgiving.
(Source category: Teaching) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 326)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00223MAG in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh00223mag/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh00223mag/en/</guid>
      <description>Say: Magnified be Thy Name, O Lord my God! I beseech Thee by Thy Name through which the splendor of the light of wisdom shone resplendent when the heavens of divine utterance were set in motion amidst mankind, to graciously aid me by Thy heavenly confirmations and enable me to extol Thy Name amongst Thy servants. O Lord! Unto Thee have I turned my face, detatched from all save Thee and holding fast to the hem of the robe of Thy manifold blessings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00308DES in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh00308des/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh00308des/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be unto Thee, O Lord of the world and Desire of the nations, O Thou Who hast become manifest in the Greatest Name, whereby the pearls of wisdom and utterance have appeared from the shells of the great sea of Thy knowledge, and the heavens of divine revelation have been adorned with the light of the appearance of the sun of Thy countenance. I beg of Thee, by that Word through which Thy proof was perfected among Thy creatures and Thy testimony was fulfilled amidst Thy servants, to strengthen Thy people in that whereby the face of the Cause will radiate in Thy dominion, the standards of Thy power will be planted among Thy servants, and the banners of Thy guidance will be raised throughout Thy dominions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08242 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08242/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08242/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise be to Thee, O Lord my God! I implore Thee, by Thy Name which none hath befittingly recognized, and whose import no soul hath fathomed; I beseech Thee, by Him Who is the Fountainhead of Thy Revelation and the Dayspring of Thy signs, to make my heart to be a receptacle of Thy love and of remembrance of Thee. Knit it, then, to Thy most great Ocean, that from it may flow out the living waters of Thy wisdom and the crystal streams of Thy glorification and praise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08363 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08363/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08363/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, Who art the Author of all Manifestations, the Source of all Sources, the Fountainhead of all Revelations, and the Wellspring of all Lights! I testify that by Thy Name the heaven of understanding hath been adorned, and the ocean of utterance hath surged, and the dispensations of Thy providence have been promulgated unto the followers of all religions. I beseech Thee so to enrich me as to dispense with all save Thee, and be made independent of anyone except Thyself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08433 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/en/</guid>
      <description>Magnified be Thy name, O my God, for that Thou hast manifested the Day which is the King of Days, the Day which Thou didst announce unto Thy chosen Ones and Thy Prophets in Thy most excellent Tablets, the Day whereon Thou didst shed the splendor of the glory of all Thy names upon all created things. Great is his blessedness whosoever hath set himself towards Thee, and entered Thy presence, and caught the accents of Thy voice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12962 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12962/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12962/</guid>
      <description>O God! I no gat narapela olsem Yu. O God, Yu Papa bilong Kingdom! Ol dispela lain, em ol ami bilong heven bilong Yu. Helpim ol, bai ol i win wantaim helpim i kam long ol lain ami bilong Ples Bung I Antap Tru. Inap bai wan wan yet i ken kamap olsem wanpela bikpela lain ami na winim ol dispela kantri wantaim lav bilong God na lait bilong ol gutpela tok skul bilong God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13358 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13358/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13358/</guid>
      <description>O Dydi, y Duw Digymar! O Arglwydd y Deyrnas! Yr eneidiau hyn yw Dy fyddin nefol. Cynorthwya hwynt, a chyda minteioedd Llu&amp;rsquo;r Goruchaf dyro iddynt fuddugoliaeth; fel y byddont oll megis catrawd, a gorchfygant y gwledydd hyn drwy gariad Duw a goleuni&amp;rsquo;r ddysgeidiaeth ddwyfol. O Dduw! Bydd yn gynhaliwr ac yn gymorth iddynt, ac yn yr anialwch y mynydd, y dyffryn, y goedwig, y gweindir a&amp;rsquo;r moroedd, bydd yn ymddiriedwr iddynt - fel y bydded iddynt lefain trwy rym y Deyrnas ac anadl yr Ysbryd Glân.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13359 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13359/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13359/</guid>
      <description>O Arglwydd! Trof fy wyneb tuag atat, wedi ymbellhau oddi wrth bawb ond Tydi ac yn dal yn dynn wrth odre Dy amryfal fendithion. Datod fy nhafod, felly,i ddatgan yr hyn a fydd yn cyfareddu meddyliau dynion ac a fydd yn llawenhau eu heneidiau a&amp;rsquo;u hysbryd&amp;hellip; Gwna fi megis llusern yn disgleirio trwy Dy diroedd,fel y bo i&amp;rsquo;r rhai hynny sydd â goleuni Dy wybodaeth yn tywynnu a hiraeth am dy gariad yn aros yn eu calonnau yn cael eu harwain gan ei lewyrch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6670 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6670/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6670/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! I pray Thee, by Him Who is the Dayspring of Thy signs and the Manifestation of Thy names, and the Treasury of Thine inspiration, and the Repository of Thy wisdom, to send upon Thy loved ones that which will enable them to cleave steadfastly to Thy Cause, and to recognize Thy unity, and to acknowledge Thy oneness, and to bear witness to Thy divinity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6787 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6787/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6787/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee Who hast caused all the holy Ones to confess their helplessness before the manifold revelations of Thy might, and every Prophet to acknowledge His nothingness at the effulgence of Thine abiding glory. I beseech Thee, by Thy name that hath unlocked the gates of Heaven and filled with ecstasy the Concourse on high, to enable me to serve Thee, in this Day, and to strengthen me to observe that which Thou didst prescribe in Thy Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6798 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6798/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6798/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O my God! I am a servant attracted to Thee, humbly drawing near to the door of Thy Oneness and supplicating the Kingdom of Thy mercy.
O my God, permit me to be entirely Thine, occupied only with thoughts of Thee, inflamed by the fire of Thy love and separated from all except Thee, so that I may work in Thy Cause, spread Thy wisdom, transmit Thy knowledge and impart the joy of knowing Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6806 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6806/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6806/</guid>
      <description>O my Lord and my Master! O my Desired One and my Best Beloved! O Thou who art the Beloved of all that are in the heavens and on the earth! I beseech Thee to grant, from the ocean of Thy bounty and the day-star of Thy heavenly grace, that I may be cursed, reviled and denounced a myriad times for the sake of Thy love, that these ears of mine may but once be blessed by hearing Thy sweet words: &amp;ldquo;Verily thou art of the people of Bahá&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9524 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn9524/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn9524/</guid>
      <description>He that summoneth men in My name is, verily, of Me, and he will show forth that which is beyond the power of all that are on earth.
(Source category: Teaching) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9524)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
