<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB00218SOU on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00218sou/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB00218SOU on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00218sou/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00218SOU in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00218sou/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00218sou/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá’ís of the United States and Canada
O Thou incomparable God! O Thou Lord of the Kingdom! These souls are Thy heavenly army. Assist them and, with the cohorts of the Supreme Concourse, make them victorious, so that each one of them may become like unto a regiment and conquer these countries through the love of God and the illumination of divine teachings. O God! Be Thou their supporter and their helper, and in the wilderness, the mountain, the valley, the forests, the prairies and the seas, be Thou their confidant—so that they may cry out through the power of the Kingdom and the breath of the Holy Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00218SOU in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00218sou/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00218sou/nl/</guid>
      <description>##Geopenbaard aan de bahá’ís van de Verenigde Staten en Canada
O Gij onvergelijkelijke God! O Gij, Heer van het Koninkrijk! Deze zielen zijn Uw hemels leger. Sta hen bij en laat hen met behulp van de legers van de allerhoogste Schare zegevieren, opdat eenieder van hen een regiment gelijk worde en deze landen verovert door de liefde Gods en de schittering van de goddelijke leringen. O God! Weest Gij hun steun en toeverlaat, en weest Gij hun vertrouweling in de wildernis, de bergen, de dalen, de wouden, de prairies en de zeeën, zodat hun roep luide zal klinken door de kracht van het Koninkrijk en de adem van de Heilige Geest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
