<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB10703RAD on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab10703rad/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB10703RAD on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab10703rad/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10703RAD in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Make this youth radiant, and confer Thy bounty upon this poor creature. Bestow upon him knowledge, grant him added strength at the break of every morn and guard him within the shelter of Thy protection so that he may be freed from error, may devote himself to the service of Thy Cause, may guide the wayward, lead the hapless, free the captives and awaken the heedless, that all may be blessed with Thy remembrance and praise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10703RAD in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Dio! Lumigu ĉi tiun junulon kaj favoru ĉi tiun malfortulon. Donacu al li scion, garantiu al li forton ĉiutage pliiĝantan kaj gardu lin sub la ŝirmo de Via protektado, tiel ke il estu pur-savita de ĉia peko, sindonu por la servo al Via Kredo, konduku la devojiĝintojn, gvidu la malriĉulojn kaj malfortulojn, liberigu la kaptitojn kaj veku la dormantojn, por ke ĉiuj estu benataj per rememoro kaj adoro al Vi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10703RAD in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Senhor! Torna radiante este jovem e derrama a Tua graça sobre este fraco! Concede-lhe conhecimento e, a cada amanhecer, aumenta-lhe as forças. Abriga-o no refúgio da Tua proteção para que seja libertado do erro, possa servir a Tua Causa, guiar os desviados, conduzir os infelizes, livrar os cativos e despertar os letárgicos; de modo que todos sejam abençoados com a Tua lembrança e louvor. És o Forte, o Poderoso.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
