<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Triumph of the Cause on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-triumph-of-the-cause/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Triumph of the Cause on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-triumph-of-the-cause/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00065KIN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! Praise be unto Thee for kindling the fire of divine love in the Holy Tree on the summit of the loftiest mount: that Tree which is “neither of the East nor of the West,”¹ that fire which blazed out till the flame of it soared upward to the Concourse on high, and from it those realities caught the light of guidance, and cried out: “Verily have we perceived a fire on the slope of Mount Sinai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00527 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00527/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00527/en/</guid>
      <description>He is God! O Lord, my God, my Well-Beloved! These are servants of Thine that have heard Thy Voice, given ear to Thy Word and hearkened to Thy Call. They have believed in Thee, witnessed Thy Wonders, acknowledged Thy proof and testified to Thine evidence. They have walked in Thy ways, followed Thy guidance, discovered Thy mysteries, comprehended the secrets of Thy Book, the verses of Thy Scrolls, and the tidings of Thy Epistles and Tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00002ENA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00002ena/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00002ena/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Enable all the peoples of the earth to gain admittance into the Paradise of Thy Faith, so that no created being may remain beyond the bounds of Thy good-pleasure. From time immemorial Thou hast been potent to do what pleaseth Thee and transcendent above whatsoever Thou desirest.
(Source category: Triumph of the Cause) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 351)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00004REN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be unto Thee, O Lord, Thou Who hast brought into being all created things, through the power of Thy behest. O Lord! Assist those who have renounced all else but Thee, and grant them a mighty victory. Send down upon them, O Lord, the concourse of the angels in heaven and earth and all that is between, to aid Thy servants, to succor and strengthen them, to enable them to achieve success, to sustain them, to invest them with glory, to confer upon them honor and exaltation, to enrich them and to make them triumphant with a wondrous triumph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00147GRO in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00147gro/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00147gro/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Provide for the speedy growth of the Tree of Thy divine Unity; water it then, O Lord, with the flowing waters of Thy good-pleasure, and cause it, before the revelations of Thy divine assurance, to yield such fruits as Thou desirest for Thy glorification and exaltation, Thy praise and thanksgiving, and to magnify Thy Name, to laud the oneness of Thine Essence and to offer adoration unto Thee, inasmuch as all this lieth within Thy grasp and in that of none other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00543VIC in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Render victorious Thy forbearing servants in Thy days by granting them a befitting victory, inasmuch as they have sought martyrdom in Thy path. Send down upon them that which will bring comfort to their minds, will rejoice their inner beings, will impart assurance to their hearts and tranquillity to their bodies and will enable their souls to ascend to the presence of God, the Most Exalted, and to attain the supreme Paradise and such retreats of glory as Thou hast destined for men of true knowledge and virtue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH05703KEP in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh05703kep/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh05703kep/en/</guid>
      <description>Suffer me not, O God, my God, to be kept back from the heaven of Thy bounties and the daystar of Thy favors. I beseech Thee by that Word through which Thou hast subdued all things visible and invisible to assist me and to assist Thy chosen ones to accomplish that which shall exalt Thy Cause amidst Thy servants and throughout Thy regions. Do Thou ordain for me, then, every good thing which Thou hast sent down in Thy Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09809 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh09809/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh09809/en/</guid>
      <description>Thou seest, O my God, how Thy loved ones have been encompassed by the rebellious amongst Thy creatures and the wicked amidst Thy people. No land remaineth but the lamentation of Thy lovers and the wailing of Thy chosen ones were lifted up therein. I beseech Thee by Thy Most Great Name to draw forth the hand of power from the bosom of Thy might and to assist therewith all them that love Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH11278RIV in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh11278riv/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh11278riv/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O Lord my God! Make manifest the rivers of Thy sovereign might, that the waters of Thy Unity may flow through the inmost realities of all things, in such wise that the banner of Thine unfailing guidance may be raised aloft in the kingdom of Thy command and the stars of Thy divine splendor may shine brightly in the heaven of Thy majesty. Potent art Thou to do what pleaseth Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn439 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn439/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn439/</guid>
      <description>Lauded be Thy name, O Lord my God! Darkness hath fallen upon every land, and the forces of mischief have encompassed all the nations. Through them, however, I perceive the splendors of Thy wisdom, and discern the brightness of the light of Thy providence.
They that are shut out as by a veil from Thee have imagined that they have the power to put out Thy light, and to quench Thy fire, and to still the winds of Thy grace.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
