<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB07709CON on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab07709con/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB07709CON on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab07709con/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB07709CON in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O my God! Glory be unto Thee for that Thou hast confirmed me to the confession of Thy oneness, attracted me unto the word of Thy singleness, enkindled me by the fire of Thy love, and occupied me with Thy mention and the service of Thy friends and maidservants.
O Lord, help me to be meek and lowly, and strengthen me in severing myself from all things and in holding to the hem of the garment of Thy glory, so that my heart may be filled with Thy love and leave no space for love of the world and attachment to its qualities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB07709CON in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh mi Dios, oh mi Dios! Gloria a Ti por cuanto me has confirmado para reconocer Tu unicidad, me has atraído hacia la palabra de Tu singularidad, me has encendido con el fuego de Tu amor y has hecho que me ocupe en Tu mención y en el servicio a Tus amigos y siervas. Oh Señor, ayúdame a ser sumiso y humilde, y fortaléceme para que pueda desligarme de todas las cosas y asirme al borde de la vestidura de Tu gloria, para que mi corazón se llene con Tu amor y no deje lugar para el amor al mundo y el apego a sus cualidades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB07709CON in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab07709con/nl/</guid>
      <description>O mijn God! O mijn God! Glorie zij U daar Gij mij hebt bevestigd in het belijden van Uw één-zijn, mij hebt aangetrokken tot het woord van Uw enig-zijn, in vlam hebt gezet met het vuur van Uw liefde en mij vervuld hebt van het U noemen en het dienen van Uw vrienden en dienaressen. O Heer, help mij deemoedig en nederig te zijn en sterk mij om mijzelf los te maken van alle dingen en mij vast te houden aan de zoom van de mantel van Uw glorie, zodat mijn hart vervuld mag worden van Uw liefde en er geen ruimte meer is voor liefde voor de wereld en gehechtheid aan haar eigenschappen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
