<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH07469 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh07469/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH07469 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh07469/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07469 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/en/</guid>
      <description>He is the Mighty, the Pardoner, the Compassionate! O God, my God! Thou beholdest Thy servants in the abyss of perdition and error; where is Thy light of divine guidance, O Thou the Desire of the world? Thou knowest their helplessness and their feebleness; where is Thy power, O Thou in Whose grasp lie the powers of heaven and earth? I ask Thee, O Lord my God, by the splendor of the lights of Thy loving-kindness and the billows of the ocean of Thy knowledge and wisdom and by Thy Word wherewith Thou hast swayed the peoples of Thy dominion, to grant that I may be one of them that have observed Thy bidding in Thy Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07469 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/nl/</guid>
      <description>Hij is de Machtige, de Verontschuldiger, de Meedogende! O God, mijn God! Gij ziet Uw dienaren in de peilloze diepte van verderf en dwaling; waar is het licht van Uw goddelijke leiding, o Gij het Verlangen der wereld? Gij kent hun hulpeloosheid en hun zwakheid; waar is Uw kracht, o Gij in Wiens greep de krachten van hemel en aarde liggen? Ik vraag U, o Heer mijn God, bij de pracht van het licht van Uw goedertierenheid en de golven van de oceaan van Uw kennis en wijsheid en bij Uw Woord waarmee Gij de volkeren van Uw heerschappij overtuigt, te geven dat ik mag behoren tot hen die zich aan de geboden in Uw Boek hebben gehouden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07469 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ele é o Poderoso, o Supremo Perdão, o Compassivo! Ó Deus, meu Deus! Vês os Teus servos no abismo da perdição e do erro: onde está a luz da Tua divina orientação, ó Tu, Desejo do mundo? Conheces o seu desamparo e a sua fraqueza: onde está o Teu poder, ó Tu em cujas mãos estão os poderes do céu e da terra? Peço-Te, ó Senhor, meu Deus – pelo esplendor das luzes da Tua benevolência e pelas ondas do oceano do Teu conhecimento e da Tua sabedoria, e pela Tua Palavra, com a qual governaste os povos do Teu domínio – peço-Te que eu seja um dos que observaram o Teu mandamento no Teu Livro.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
