<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Spiritual Assembly on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-spiritual-assembly/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Spiritual Assembly on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-spiritual-assembly/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00774SAB in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-assembly/ab00774sab/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-assembly/ab00774sab/en/</guid>
      <description>*Come ye together in gladness unalloyed, and at the beginning of the meeting, recite ye this prayer:
O Thou Lord of the Kingdom! Though our bodies be gathered here together, yet our spellbound hearts are carried away by Thy love, and yet are we transported by the rays of Thy resplendent face. Weak though we be, we await the revelations of Thy might and power. Poor though we be, with neither goods nor means, still take we riches from the treasures of Thy Kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00774SAB in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-assembly/ab00774sab/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-assembly/ab00774sab/fy/</guid>
      <description>Kom by elkoar yn suvere blydskip en sis dit gebed by it begjin fan de gearkomste.
O Jo, Hear fan it Keninkryk! Alhoewol&amp;rsquo;t ús lichems hjir by elkoar binne, wurde ús betsjoende herten fuortfierd troch Jo leafde en reitsje wy yn ekstaze troch de strielen fan Jo skitterjend antlit. Hoe swak wy ek binne, wy ferwachtsje de iepenbieringen fan Jo krêft en macht. Hoe earm wy ek binne, sûnder goed en middels, dochs helje wy rykdommen út de skatten fan Jo Keninkryk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB01023SAE in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-assembly/ab01023sae/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-assembly/ab01023sae/en/</guid>
      <description>*Whenever ye enter the council-chamber, recite this prayer with a heart throbbing with the love of God and a tongue purified from all but His remembrance, that the All-Powerful may graciously aid you to achieve supreme victory.
O God, my God! We are servants of Thine that have turned with devotion to Thy Holy Face, that have detached ourselves from all besides Thee in this glorious Day. We have gathered in this Spiritual Assembly, united in our views and thoughts, with our purposes harmonized to exalt Thy Word amidst mankind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB01023SAE in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-assembly/ab01023sae/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-assembly/ab01023sae/nl/</guid>
      <description>*Reciteer dit gebed telkens als u de raadskamer binnengaat met een hart dat bonst van liefde voor God en een tong die is gezuiverd van alles buiten het Hem gedenken, opdat de Almachtige u genadiglijk zal bijstaan om de hoogste overwinning te behalen.
O God, mijn God! Wij zijn Uw dienaren die zich vol toewijding tot Uw heilig Gelaat hebben gekeerd en die zich in deze glorierijke Dag van alles buiten U hebben bevrijd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB04620 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-assembly/ab04620/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-assembly/ab04620/en/</guid>
      <description>*Prayer to be said at the close of the meeting of the Spiritual Assembly.
O God! O God! From the unseen kingdom of Thy oneness behold us assembled in this spiritual meeting, believing in Thee, confident in Thy signs, firm in Thy Covenant and Testament, attracted to Thee, set aglow with the fire of Thy love and sincere in Thy Cause. We are servants in Thy vineyard, spreaders of Thy religion, devoted worshipers of Thy countenance, humble towards Thy loved ones, submissive before Thy door, and imploring Thee to confirm us in serving Thy chosen ones, to support us with Thine unseen hosts, to strengthen our loins in Thy servitude and to make us submissive and adoring subjects communing with Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
