<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB09794CHI on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab09794chi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB09794CHI on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab09794chi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09794CHI in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! I am a child; enable me to grow beneath the shadow of Thy loving-kindness. I am a tender plant; cause me to be nurtured through the outpourings of the clouds of Thy bounty. I am a sapling of the garden of love; make me into a fruitful tree. Thou art the Mighty and the Powerful, and Thou art the All-Loving, the All-Knowing, the All-Seeing.
(Source category: Children) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 197)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09794CHI in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Heer! Ik ben een kind, laat mij groeien in de schaduw van Uw goedertierenheid. Ik ben een teer plantje, voed mij met de regen uit de wolken van Uw milddadigheid. Ik ben een jong boompje in de tuin van liefde, laat mij een vruchtdragende boom worden. Gij zijt de Machtige en de Krachtige, en Gij zijt de Liefderijke, de Alwetende, de Alziende.
(Source category: Kinderen) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9620)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09794CHI in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/children/ab09794chi/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Senhor! Sou uma criança; permite-me crescer à sombra da Tua benevolência. Sou uma tenra planta; faze com que eu seja nutrida pelas emanações das nuvens da Tua generosidade. Sou um pequeno arbusto no jardim do amor; torna-me uma árvore frutífera. Tu és o Forte e o Poderoso, o Amor Supremo, o Omnisciente, Aquele que tudo vê.
(Source category: Criança) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 1086)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
