<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB00169FRA on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00169fra/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB00169FRA on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00169fra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00169FRA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00169fra/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00169fra/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá&amp;rsquo;ís of Canada and Greenland Praise be to Thee, O my God! These are Thy servants who are attracted by the fragrances of Thy mercifulness, are enkindled by the fire burning in the tree of Thy singleness, and whose eyes are brightened by beholding the splendors of the light shining in the Sinai of Thy oneness.
O Lord! Loose their tongues to make mention of Thee amongst Thy people, suffer them to speak forth Thy praise through Thy grace and loving-kindness, assist them with the cohorts of Thine angels, strengthen their loins in Thy service, and make them the signs of Thy guidance amongst Thy creatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00169FRA in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00169fra/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00169fra/nl/</guid>
      <description>##Geopenbaard aan de bahá’ís van Canada
Ere zij U, o mijn God! Dit zijn Uw dienaren die zijn aangetrokken door de geur van Uw erbarmen, zijn aangestoken door het vuur dat in de boom van Uw enig-zijn brandt, wier ogen oplichten bij het aanschouwen van de pracht van het licht dat schijnt in de Sinaï van Uw één-zijn. O Heer! Maak hun tong los om gewag van U te maken onder Uw volk, vergun hen te getuigen van Uw lof door Uw genade en goedertierenheid, sta hen bij met de scharen van Uw engelen, sterk hun lendenen in dienstbaarheid aan U en maak hen het teken van Uw leiding onder Uw schepselen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00169FRA in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00169fra/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00169fra/pt/</guid>
      <description>Louvor a Ti, ó meu Deus! Estes são os Teus servos, atraídos pelas fragrâncias da Tua misericórdia, ardentes com o fogo aceso na árvore da Tua singularidade, com os seus olhos a brilhar ao contemplar os esplendores da luz que brilha no Sinai da Tua unicidade! Ó Senhor! Descerra os seus lábios em Tua comemoração entre o Teu povo; permite que, através da Tua graça e amorosa bondade, expressem louvores a Ti; ajuda-os com as hostes dos Teus anjos; fortalece-os em Teu serviço e torna-os sinais da Tua guia entre Tuas criaturas!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
