<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Journey on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-journey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Journey on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-journey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009GRA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh00009gra/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh00009gra/en/</guid>
      <description>I have risen this morning by Thy grace, O my God, and left my home trusting wholly in Thee, and committing myself to Thy care. Send down, then, upon me, out of the heaven of Thy mercy, a blessing from Thy side, and enable me to return home in safety even as Thou didst enable me to set out under Thy protection with my thoughts fixed steadfastly upon Thee.
There is none other God but Thee, the One, the Incomparable, the All-Knowing, the All-Wise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009GRA in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh00009gra/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh00009gra/eo/</guid>
      <description>Mi ellitiĝis ĉi-matene pro Via favoro, ho mia Dio, kaj iris for el mia hejmo, fidante tutplene je Vi kaj konfidante min al Via prizorgo. Donu al mi el la ĉielo de Via kompato benon Vian kaj ebligu al mi reveni hejmen tiel sekure, kiel vi ebligis al mi foriri sub Via protekto, kun miaj pensoj konstante fiksitaj al Vi. Ne estas alia Dio krom Vi, la Unusola, la Ne-komparebla, la Ĉioscia, la Plejsaĝa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009GRA in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh00009gra/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh00009gra/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik ben deze morgen opgestaan door Uw genade, o mijn God, en vol vertrouwen op U heb ik mijn woning verlaten, en mij geheel aan Uw zorg toevertrouwd. Zend dan Uwerzijds een zegening vanuit de hemel van Uw barmhartigheid tot mij neer en laat mij veilig terugkeren, zoals Gij mij ook onder Uw bescherming liet vertrekken, met mijn gedachten standvastig op U gericht. Er is geen ander God dan Gij, de Ene, de Onvergelijkelijke, de Alwetende, de Alwijze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009GRA in Papiamentu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh00009gra/pap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh00009gra/pap/</guid>
      <description>*I have risen this morning by Thy grace
Mi a lanta awe mainta pa fabor di Bo grasia, O mi Dios, i a laga mi kas konfiando henteramente den Bo, i rekomendando mi mes na Bo kuido. Basha anto riba mi for di e shelu de Bo miserikordia un bendishon di Bo, i permitimi di bolbe mi kas sano i salbo, meskos ku Bo a permitimi di sali bou Bo protekshon ku mi pensamentunan fihá firmemente riba Bo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10688 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh10688/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh10688/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! I have set out from my home, holding fast unto the cord of Thy love, and I have committed myself wholly to Thy care and Thy protection. I entreat Thee by Thy power through which Thou didst protect Thy loved ones from the wayward and the perverse, and from every contumacious oppressor, and every wicked doer who hath strayed far from Thee, to keep me safe by Thy bounty and Thy grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10688 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh10688/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/journey/bh10688/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Dio, mia Dio! Mi forlasis mian hejmon, firme tenante la kordonon de Via amo, kaj plene mi subigis min al Via prizorgo kaj Via protektado. Mi petegas Vin je Via povo, per kiu Vi protektis Viajn amatojn kontraŭ la ribelemaj kaj malicaj, kaj kontraŭ ĉiu obstina subpremanto kaj ĉiu malvirta aganto, kiu erarvagadas fore de Vi, gardu min sekura per Via malavaro kaj Via graco. Ebligu al mi do reveni al mia hejmo per Via potenco kaj Via forto.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
