<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH09024 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09024/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH09024 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09024 in Afrikaans</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/af/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/af/</guid>
      <description>Menige verkoelde hart, o my God, is met die vuur van U Saak aan die brand gesteek, en menige sluimeraar is deur die soetheid van U stem wakker gemaak. Hoeveel is die vreemdelinge wat skuilplek in die skaduwee van die boom van U eenheid nie gesoek het nie, en hoe talryk die dorstiges wat na die fontein van U lewende waters in U dae nie gehunker het nie!
Geluksalig is hy wat homself na U ingestel het, en haas gemaak het om die Daeraad van die ligte van U gesig te bereik.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09024 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/en/</guid>
      <description>Many a chilled heart, O my God, hath been set ablaze by the fire of Thy Cause, and many a slumberer hath been wakened by the sweetness of Thy voice. How many are the strangers who have sought shelter beneath the shadow of the tree of Thy oneness, and how numerous the thirsty ones who have panted after the fountain of Thy living waters in Thy days! Blessed is he that hath set himself towards Thee, and hasted to attain the Dayspring of the lights of Thy face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09024 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/es/</guid>
      <description>Muchos corazones yertos, oh mi Dios, han sido encendidos con el fuego de Tu Causa, y muchos de cuantos estaban dormidos han sido despertados por la dulzura de Tu voz. ¡Cuántos son los extraños que han buscado abrigo a la sombra del árbol de Tu unicidad, y cuán numerosos los sedientos que han anhelado en Tus días la fuente de Tus aguas vivas! Bendito es aquel que se ha dirigido hacia Ti y se ha apresurado a alcanzar la Aurora de las luces de Tu semblante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09024 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/eo/</guid>
      <description>Multe da frostaj koroj, ho mia Dio, ekflamis per la fajro de Via Kredo, kaj multaj dormantoj vekiĝis per la dolĉeco de Via voĉo. Kiom da vaguloj serĉis rifuĝon sub la ombro de la arbo de Via unueco, kaj kiom da soifantoj anhele strebis al la fonto de Viaj vivigaj akvoj dum la tagoj Viaj! Benata estas tiu, kiu direktis sin al Vi kaj hastis por atingi la Tagiĝon de la Lumoj de Via Vizaĝo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09024 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/nl/</guid>
      <description>Menig verkild hart is in vlam gezet met het vuur van Uw Zaak, o mijn God, en menig slapende is gewekt door de zoetheid van Uw stem. Hoevele vreemdelingen zoeken beschutting in de schaduw van de boom van Uw één-zijn, en hoe talrijk zijn de dorstigen die in Uw dagen naar de bron van Uw levend water smachten! Gezegend is hij die zich tot U heeft gewend en zich heeft gehaast het ochtendgloren van het licht van Uw aanschijn te bereiken.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
