<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH09498 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09498/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH09498 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09498/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09498 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/service/bh09498/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/service/bh09498/en/</guid>
      <description>O God and the God of all Names, and the Maker of the heavens! I entreat Thee by Thy Name through which He Who is the Dayspring of Thy might and the Dawning-Place of Thy power hath been manifested, through which every solid thing hath been made to flow, and every dead corpse hath been quickened, and every moving spirit confirmed—I entreat Thee to enable me to rid myself of all attachment to any one but Thee, and to serve Thy Cause, and to wish what Thou didst wish through the power of Thy sovereignty, and to perform what is the good pleasure of Thy will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09498 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/service/bh09498/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/service/bh09498/nl/</guid>
      <description>O God, en de God aller namen, en de Maker der hemelen! Ik smeek U bij Uw Naam waardoor Hij die het ochtendgloren van Uw macht en de dageraadsplaats van Uw kracht is werd gemanifesteerd, waardoor alles van vaste stof vloeibaar werd, en elk levenloos lichaam tot leven kwam, en iedere bezielende geest bevestigd werd – ik smeek U mij in staat te stellen mij van alle gehechtheid aan iemand buiten U te ontdoen, en Uw Zaak te dienen, en te wensen hetgeen Gij door de kracht van Uw soevereiniteit wenst, en te volvoeren hetgeen Uw wil behaagt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
