<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH03562 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh03562/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH03562 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh03562/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03562 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh03562/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh03562/en/</guid>
      <description>He is the prayer-hearing, prayer-answering God! By Thy glory, O Beloved One, Thou giver of light to the world! The flames of separation have consumed me, and my waywardness hath melted my heart within me. I ask of Thee, by Thy Most Great Name, O Thou the Desire of the world and the Well-Beloved of mankind, to grant that the breeze of Thine inspiration may sustain my soul, that Thy wondrous voice may reach my ear, that my eyes may behold Thy signs and Thy light as revealed in the manifestations of Thy names and Thine attributes, O Thou within Whose grasp are all things!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03562 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh03562/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh03562/nl/</guid>
      <description>Hij is de God die gebeden verhoort en beantwoordt! Bij Uw glorie, o Geliefde, Gij die de wereld licht schenkt! Het vuur van scheiding verslindt mij, en mijn weerspannigheid verteert mijn hart. Ik vraag U, bij Uw Allergrootste Naam, o Gij het Verlangen der wereld en de Welbeminde der mensheid, te geven dat de bries van Uw bezieling mijn ziel steunt, opdat Uw wondere stem mijn oor bereikt en mijn oog Uw tekenen en Uw licht aanschouwt zoals dat is onthuld in de openbaring van Uw Namen en Uw eigenschappen, o Gij in Wiens greep alle dingen liggen!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
