<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH00009SER on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh00009ser/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH00009SER on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh00009ser/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009SER in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009ser/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009ser/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God, my Master, the Goal of my desire! This, Thy servant, seeketh to sleep in the shelter of Thy mercy, and to repose beneath the canopy of Thy grace, imploring Thy care and Thy protection. I beg of Thee, O my Lord, by Thine eye that sleepeth not, to guard mine eyes from beholding aught beside Thee. Strengthen, then, their vision that they may discern Thy signs, and behold the Horizon of Thy Revelation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009SER in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009ser/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009ser/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Dio, mia Mastro, la Celo de mia deziro! Ĉi tiu servanto Via sopiras dormon en la ŝirmejo de Via kompato kaj ripozon sub la baldakeno de Via favoro, petegante Viajn prizorgon kaj protektadon. Mi petas Vin, ho mia Eternulo, je Via okulo nedorma, protekti miajn okulojn, ke ili vidu nenion krom Vi. Plifortigu, do, ilian vidpovon, por ke ili distingu Viajn signojn kaj ekvidu la Horizonton de Via Revelacio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009SER in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009ser/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009ser/fy/</guid>
      <description>O myn God, myn Master. Doel fan myn langstme! Dizze Jo tsjinner besiket te sliepen yn de beskutting fan Jo genede en te rêsten ûnder it baldakyn fan Jo geunst, smeekjende om Jo soarch en Jo beskerming. Ik smeekje Jo, o myn Hear, by Jo each dat net sliept, myn eagen te hoedzjen om eat oars te sjen útsein Jo. Sterkje dan harren sjen, dat hja Jo tekens waarnimme en de hoarizon fan Jo iepenbiering oanskôgje meie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009SER in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009ser/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/evening/bh00009ser/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó meu Deus, meu Mestre, Alvo do meu desejo! Este servo Teu quer dormir à sombra da Tua misericórdia e repousar sob o pálio da Tua graça, implorando o Teu cuidado e a Tua proteção. Suplico-Te, ó meu Senhor, pelos Teus olhos insones, que guardes os meus olhos para que nada vejam senão a Ti. Fortalece-lhes, pois, a visão para que discirnam os Teus sinais e contemplem o Horizonte da Tua Revelação.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
