<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH08600FAC on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh08600fac/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH08600FAC on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh08600fac/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08600FAC in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/en/</guid>
      <description>I am he, O my Lord, that hath set his face towards Thee, and fixed his hope on the wonders of Thy grace and the revelations of Thy bounty. I pray Thee that Thou wilt not suffer me to turn away disappointed from the door of Thy mercy, nor abandon me to such of Thy creatures as have repudiated Thy Cause. I am, O my God, Thy servant and the son of Thy servant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08600FAC in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/es/</guid>
      <description>Soy aquel, oh mi Señor, que ha vuelto el rostro hacia Ti y ha fijado su esperanza en las maravillas de Tu gracia y en las revelaciones de Tu munificencia. Te ruego que no permitas que me aleje desilusionado de la puerta de Tu misericordia, ni me dejes a merced de aquellas criaturas Tuyas que han repudiado Tu Causa. ¡Oh mi Dios! Soy Tu siervo y el hijo de Tu siervo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08600FAC in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/forgiveness/bh08600fac/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik ben degeen, o mijn Heer, die zijn gelaat naar U heeft gekeerd en zijn hoop heeft gevestigd op de wonderen van Uw genade en de openbaringen van Uw milddadigheid. Ik bid U dat Gij mij niet teleurgesteld van de deur van Uw erbarmen laat weggaan, noch mij overlevert aan diegenen onder Uw schepselen die Uw Zaak hebben verworpen. Ik ben Uw dienaar, o mijn God, en de zoon van Uw dienaar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
