<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Aid and Assistance on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-aid-and-assistance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Aid and Assistance on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-aid-and-assistance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00073SER in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab00073ser/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab00073ser/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! We are servants of Thy Threshold, taking shelter at Thy holy Door. We seek no refuge save only this strong pillar, turn nowhere for a haven but unto Thy safekeeping. Protect us, bless us, support us, make us such that we shall love but Thy good pleasure, utter only Thy praise, follow only the pathway of truth, that we may become rich enough to dispense with all save Thee, and receive our gifts from the sea of Thy beneficence, that we may ever strive to exalt Thy Cause and to spread Thy sweet savors far and wide, that we may become oblivious of self and occupied only with Thee, and disown all else and be caught up in Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00431PIT in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab00431pit/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab00431pit/en/</guid>
      <description>Lord! Pitiful are we, grant us Thy favor; poor, bestow upon us a share from the ocean of Thy wealth;needy, do Thou satisfy us; abased, give us Thy glory. The fowls of the air and the beasts of the field receive their meat each day from Thee and all beings partake of Thy care and loving kindness. Deprive not this feeble one of Thy wondrous grace and vouchsafe by Thy might unto this helpless soul Thy bounty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00431PIT in Papiamentu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab00431pit/pap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab00431pit/pap/</guid>
      <description>*Lord! Pitiful are we, grant us Thy favor…
Señor, nos tin mester di miserikordia, duna nos Bo fabor; nos ta pober, drama riba nos un parti di e oseano di Bo rikesa; nos ta den nesesidat, satisfase nos; nos ta humiyá, duna nos Bo gloria. E paranan den aire i e bestianan den mondi ta resibí tur dia nan alimentashon di Bo, i tur kriaturanan ta toka parti di Bo kuido i kariño amoroso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10275 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab10275/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/ab10275/en/</guid>
      <description>Remove not, O Lord, the festal board that hath been spread in Thy Name, and extinguish not the burning flame that hath been kindled by Thine unquenchable fire. Withhold not from flowing that living water of Thine that murmureth with the melody of Thy glory and Thy remembrance, and deprive not Thy servants from the fragrance of Thy sweet savors breathing forth the perfume of Thy love. Lord! Turn the distressing cares of Thy holy ones into ease, their hardship into comfort, their abasement into glory, their sorrow into blissful joy, O Thou that holdest in Thy grasp the reins of all mankind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00018DET in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bb00018det/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bb00018det/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God, my Lord and my Master! I have detached myself from my kindred and have sought through Thee to become independent of all that dwell on earth and ever ready to receive that which is praiseworthy in Thy sight. Bestow on me such good as will make me independent of aught else but Thee, and grant me an ampler share of Thy boundless favors. Verily, Thou art the Lord of grace abounding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00553 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bb00553/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bb00553/en/</guid>
      <description>Lauded be Thy Name, O Lord our God! Thou art in truth the Knower of things unseen. Ordain for us such good as Thine all-embracing knowledge can measure. Thou art the sovereign Lord, the Almighty, the Best-Beloved. All praise be unto Thee, O Lord! We shall seek Thy grace on the appointed Day and shall put our whole reliance in Thee, Who art our Lord. Glorified art Thou, O God! Grant us that which is good and seemly that we may be able to dispense with everything but Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00438 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh00438/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh00438/en/</guid>
      <description>My God, my Adored One, my King, my Desire! What tongue can voice my thanks to Thee? I was heedless, Thou didst awaken me. I had turned back from Thee, Thou didst graciously aid me to turn towards Thee. I was as one dead, Thou didst quicken me with the water of life. I was withered, Thou didst revive me with the heavenly stream of Thine utterance which hath flowed forth from the Pen of the All-Merciful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10973 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh10973/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh10973/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou Whose face is the object of my adoration, Whose beauty is my sanctuary, Whose habitation is my goal, Whose praise is my hope, Whose providence is my companion, Whose love is the cause of my being, Whose mention is my solace, Whose nearness is my desire, Whose presence is my dearest wish and highest aspiration, I entreat Thee not to withhold from me the things Thou didst ordain for the chosen ones among Thy servants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn10518 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10518/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10518/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O Thou Who endowest every just power and equitable dominion with abiding glory and everlasting might, with permanence and stability, with constancy and honour! Aid Thou by Thy heavenly grace every government that acteth justly towards its subjects and every sovereign authority, derived from Thee, that shieldeth the poor and the weak under the banner of its protection. I beseech Thee, by Thy divine grace and surpassing bounty, to aid this just government, the canopy of whose authority is spread over vast and mighty lands and the evidences of whose justice are apparent in its prosperous and flourishing regions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn11700 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn11700/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn11700/</guid>
      <description>O God! Grant Thy favour, and bestow Thy blessing. Vouchsafe Thy grace, and give a portion of Thy bounty. Enable these men to witness during this year the fulfilment of their hopes. Send down Thy heavenly rain, and provide Thy plenteousness and abundance. Thou art the Powerful, the Mighty.
(Source category: Aid and Assistance) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 11700)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12366 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12366/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12366/</guid>
      <description>O Thou Whose face is the object of my adoration,… O Oe e Ona fofoga o le sini o la’u tapuaiga, E Ona le matagofie o lo’u sulufaiga, E Ona le afioaga o lo’u sini, E Ona le viiga o lo’u faamoemoega, E Ona le tausiga o lo’u soatau, E Ona le alofa o le mafuaga o lo’u ola, E Ona le ta’uta’uina o lo’u faamafanafanaga, E Ona le faalatalata mai o lo’u manaoga, E Ona le faatasi mai o lo’u moomooga silisili ona pele ma la’u manavaga silisili ona maualuga.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12367 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12367/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12367/</guid>
      <description>Lord! Pitiful are we, grant us Thy favor;… Le alii e! Ua augavale i matou, foa’i mai Lou finagalo alofa; e matitiva, liligi ifo i o matou luga se vaega mai le vasa o Lou tamaoaiga; e mana’ona’o, faamalilieina I matou e Lau Afio, e faatauvaa, aumai mo i matou Lou mamalu. O loo maua pea lava e manulele o le vanimonimo ma manu vaefa o le laueleele a latou meaai i aso ta’itasi mai ia te Oe, ma o tagata uma lava o loo mau vaega i Lau tausiga ma le alofa agalelei.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12488 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12488/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12488/</guid>
      <description>I adjure Thee by Thy might, O my God! Let no harm beset me..
Ou te augani fa’atauanau atu i Lau Afio, e ala i Lou malosi, Lo’u Atua e! Ia fa’asaogalemūina a’u i taimi e o’o mai ai tofotofoga, ma taimi o lo’u tu’ulafoa’ina o a’u, ta’ita’ina mai i o’u la’asaga ia fa’asagatonu atu i le fa’ala’ei’auina a Lau Afioga. O Lau Afio lava o le Atua, o lo’o i Lau Afio lava le mana malosi e faia ai le mea e finagalo malie i ai Lau Afio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13083 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn13083/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn13083/</guid>
      <description>He is God.
O Thou Whose exalted Threshold is my haven and my refuge, Whose hallowed Sanctuary is my shelter and my abode! I entreat Thee, with a heart aglow with the fire of Thy love, and with eyes streaming with tears in my longing to attain Thy presence, in my yearning to gain admittance into the Kingdom of Thy glory, and in my desire to taste the sweetness of faithfulness to Thee, to graciously aid this servant through the breaths of Thy holiness and the delight of communion with Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6342 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6342/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6342/</guid>
      <description>Magnified be Thy Name, O Lord my God! I am the one who hath turned his face towards Thee and hath placed his whole reliance in Thee. I implore Thee by Thy Name whereby the ocean of Thine utterance hath surged and the breezes of Thy knowledge have stirred, to grant that I may be graciously aided to serve Thy Cause and be inspired to remember Thee and praise Thee. Send down then upon me from the heaven of Thy generosity that which will preserve me from anyone but Thee and will profit me in all Thy worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6346 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6346/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6346/</guid>
      <description>O Thou divine Providence, pitiful are we, grant us Thy succour; homeless wanderers, give us Thy shelter; scattered, do Thou unite us; astray, gather us to Thy fold; bereft, do Thou bestow upon us a share and portion; athirst, lead us to the well-spring of Life; frail, strengthen us that we may arise to help Thy Cause and offer ourselves as a living sacrifice in the pathway of guidance.
*Selections from the Writings, p.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6347 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6347/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6347/</guid>
      <description>O my God! I ask Thee, by Thy most glorious Name, to aid me in that which will cause the affairs of Thy servants to prosper, and Thy cities to flourish. Thou, indeed, hast power over all things!
*Summons of the Lord of Hosts, p. 90.
(Source category: Aid and Assistance) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 6347)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
