<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB09139 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab09139/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB09139 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab09139/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09139 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O my God! This, Thy servant, hath advanced towards Thee, is passionately wandering in the desert of Thy love, walking in the path of Thy service, anticipating Thy favors, hoping for Thy bounty, relying upon Thy kingdom, and intoxicated by the wine of Thy gift. O my God! Increase the fervor of his affection for Thee, the constancy of his praise of Thee, and the ardor of his love for Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09139 in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/fr/</guid>
      <description>Ô mon Dieu, ô mon Dieu, voici que ton serviteur s’avance vers toi et qu’il parcourt avec passion le désert de ton amour, suivant la voie de ton service, dans l’attente de tes faveurs et dans l’espoir de ta générosité, confiant en ton royaume et grisé du vin de tes bienfaits. Ô mon Dieu, accrois sa piété, sa constance à te célébrer et l’ardeur de son amour. En vérité, tu es le Très-Généreux, le Seigneur de toute grâce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09139 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/nl/</guid>
      <description>O mijn God! O mijn God! Deze dienaar is nader tot U gekomen, zwerft hartstochtelijk door de woestijn van Uw liefde, bewandelt het pad van dienstbaarheid aan U, ziet uit naar Uw gunsten, hoopt op Uw gaven, vertrouwt op Uw koninkrijk en is bedwelmd door de wijn van Uw gift. O mijn God! Vermeerder het vuur van zijn genegenheid voor U, de standvastigheid van zijn lof voor U en het vuur van zijn liefde voor U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB09139 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab09139/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó meu Deus! ó meu Deus! Este Teu servo apressou-se na Tua direção, trilhando o caminho em Teu serviço, antecipando os Teus favores, esperando as Tuas bênçãos, confiando no Teu reino, e intoxicado pelo vinho do Teu favor. Ó meu Deus! Aumenta o fervor da sua afeição por Ti, a constância do seu louvor por Ti, e o ardor do seu amor por Ti. Verdadeiramente, Tu és o Mais Generoso, o Senhor de graça copiosa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
