<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH10581 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh10581/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH10581 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh10581/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10581 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise be unto Thee, O Lord my God! We have observed the Fast in conformity with Thy bidding and break it now through Thy love and Thy good-pleasure. Deign to accept, O my God, the deeds that we have performed in Thy path wholly for the sake of Thy beauty with our faces set towards Thy Cause, free from aught else but Thee. Bestow, then, Thy forgiveness upon us, upon our forefathers, and upon all such as have believed in Thee and in Thy mighty signs in this most great, this most glorious Revelation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10581 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/nl/</guid>
      <description>Lof zij U, o Heer mijn God! Wij hebben ons aan de Vasten gehouden overeenkomstig Uw gebod en beëindigen die nu door Uw liefde en Uw welbehagen. Wilt Gij dan, o mijn God, de daden aanvaarden die wij geheel omwille van Uw schoonheid op Uw pad verrichten met ons gelaat naar Uw Zaak gekeerd, vrij van alles buiten U. Schenk dan Uw vergeving aan ons, aan onze voorvaderen en aan allen die in U en in Uw machtige tekenen geloven in deze grootste, deze glorierijkste Openbaring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10581 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/pt/</guid>
      <description>Louvado sejas, ó Senhor meu Deus! Observámos o Jejum de acordo com a Tua vontade e quebrámo-lo agora pelo Teu amor e pelo Teu agrado. Digna-Te aceitar, ó meu Deus, as obras que temos realizado no Teu caminho inteiramente por amor à Tua beleza, com as nossas faces voltadas para a Tua Causa, livres de tudo senão de Ti. Concede, pois, o Teu perdão a todos nós e aos nossos antepassados, e a todos os que acreditaram em Ti e nos Teus poderosos sinais nesta mais sublime, nesta mais gloriosa Revelação.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
