<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-ABU0023UNI on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-abu0023uni/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-ABU0023UNI on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-abu0023uni/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0023UNI in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/abu0023uni/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/abu0023uni/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O my God! Verily, I invoke Thee and supplicate before Thy threshold, asking Thee that all Thy mercies may descend upon these souls. Specialize them for Thy favor and Thy truth. O Lord! Unite and bind together the hearts, join in accord all the souls, and exhilarate the spirits through the signs of Thy sanctity and oneness. O Lord! Make these faces radiant through the light of Thy oneness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0023UNI in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/abu0023uni/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/abu0023uni/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Dio! Ho mia Dio! Vere, mi alvokas Vin kaj preĝas antaŭ Via sojlo, petante Vin, ke ĉiuj Viaj benoj descendu sur ĉi tiujn animojn. Distingu ilin per Via favoro kaj Via vero. Ho Eternulo! Unuigu kaj kunligu la korojn, akordigu ĉiujn animojn kaj ĝojigu la spiritojn per la signoj de Viaj sankteco kaj ununureco. Ho Eternulo! Faru ĉi tiujn vizaĝojn radiantaj per la lumo de Via unueco. Fortigu la lumbojn de Viaj servantoj por la servado al Via regno.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0023UNI in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/abu0023uni/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/abu0023uni/nl/</guid>
      <description>O mijn God! O mijn God! Waarlijk, ik roep U aan en smeek aan Uw drempel, en vraag U om al Uw barmhartigheid tot deze zielen te laten neerdalen. Maak hen geschikt voor Uw gunst en Uw waarheid. O Heer! Verenig en verbind de harten, breng alle zielen in harmonie, en verblijd aller geest door de tekenen van Uw heiligheid en één-zijn. O Heer! Laat deze gezichten stralen met het licht van Uw één-zijn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
