<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH03109KIN on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh03109kin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH03109KIN on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh03109kin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03109KIN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/bh03109kin/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/bh03109kin/en/</guid>
      <description>He is God, exalted is He, the Lord of loving-kindness and bounty! Glory be unto Thee, Thou, O my God, the Lord Omnipotent. I testify to Thine Omnipotence and Thy might, Thy sovereignty and Thy loving-kindness, Thy grace and Thy power, the oneness of Thy being and the unity of Thine Essence, Thy sanctity and exaltation above the world of being and all that is therein. O my God! Thou seest me detached from all save Thee, holding fast unto Thee and turning unto the ocean of Thy bounty, to the heaven of Thy favor, to the Daystar of Thy grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03109KIN in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/bh03109kin/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/bh03109kin/fr/</guid>
      <description>Il est Dieu ! Loué soit Dieu, le Seigneur de tendre bonté et de générosité ! Gloire à toi, ô mon Dieu, Seigneur omnipotent ! Je témoigne de ta toutepuissance et de ton pouvoir, de ta souveraineté et de ta tendre bonté, de ta grâce et de ton autorité, de l’unicité de ton être et de l’unité de ton essence, de ta sainteté et de ta grandeur, par-delà le monde de l’existence et tout ce qu’il renferme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03109KIN in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/bh03109kin/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/bh03109kin/it/</guid>
      <description>Egli è Dio, esaltato Egli sia, il Signore amoroso e generoso! Gloria a Te, o mio Dio, Signore Onnipotente. Io fo’ testimonianza della Tua onnipotenza e della Tua forza, della Tua sovranità e del Tuo tenero amore, della Tua grazia e del Tuo potere, dell’unicità del Tuo Essere e dell’unità della Tua Essenza, della Tua santità e della Tua supremazia sul mondo dell’esistenza e su tutto ciò che è in esso.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
