<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Families on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-families/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Families on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-families/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02000DIS in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab02000dis/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab02000dis/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! In this Most Great Dispensation Thou dost accept the intercession of children in behalf of their parents. This is one of the special infinite bestowals of this Dispensation. Therefore, O Thou kind Lord, accept the request of this Thy servant at the threshold of Thy singleness and submerge his father in the ocean of Thy grace, because this son hath arisen to render Thee service and is exerting effort at all times in the pathway of Thy love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB03017CAL in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab03017cal/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab03017cal/en/</guid>
      <description>#Husbands
O God, my God! This Thy handmaid is calling upon Thee, trusting in Thee, turning her face unto Thee, imploring Thee to shed thy heavenly bounties upon her, and to disclose unto her Thy spiritual mysteries, and to cast upon her the lights of Thy Godhead. O my Lord! Make the eyes of my husband to see. Rejoice Thou his heart with the light of the knowledge of Thee, draw Thou his mind unto Thy luminous beauty, cheer Thou his spirit by revealing unto him Thy manifest splendors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00018FOR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/en/</guid>
      <description>#Parents
I beg Thy forgiveness, O my God, and implore pardon after the manner Thou wishest Thy servants to direct themselves to Thee. I beg of Thee to wash away our sins as befitteth Thy Lordship, and to forgive me, my parents, and those who in Thy estimation have entered the abode of Thy love in a manner which is worthy of Thy transcendent sovereignty and well beseemeth the glory of Thy celestial power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00583 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00583/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00583/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be unto Thee, O Lord my God! I beg Thee to forgive me and those who support Thy Faith. Verily, Thou art the sovereign Lord, the Forgiver, the Most Generous. O my God! Enable such servants of Thine as are deprived of knowledge to be admitted into Thy Cause; for once they learn of Thee, they bear witness to the truth of the Day of Judgment and do not dispute the revelations of Thy bounty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6344 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6344/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6344/</guid>
      <description>Thou seest, O Lord, our suppliant hands lifted up towards the heaven of Thy favor and bounty. Grant that they may be filled with the treasures of Thy munificence and bountiful favor. Forgive us, and our fathers, and our mothers, and fulfil whatsoever we have desired from the ocean of Thy grace and Divine generosity. Accept, O Beloved of our hearts, all our works in Thy path. Thou art, verily, the Most Powerful, the Most Exalted, the Incomparable, the One, the Forgiving, the Gracious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9407 in Corsica</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/co/bpn9407/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/co/bpn9407/</guid>
      <description>Benedettu hè u locu, a casa è a piazza, a cità è u core, a muntagna è u riparu, a spilunca è a valle, u paese è u mare, l’ìsula è u pratu, induve Diu hè chjamatu è a so loda glurificata.
(Source category: Families) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9407)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
