<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH00009AWA on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh00009awa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH00009AWA on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh00009awa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009AWA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/en/</guid>
      <description>I give praise to Thee, O my God, that Thou hast awakened me out of my sleep, and brought me forth after my disappearance, and raised me up from my slumber. I have wakened this morning with my face set toward the splendors of the Daystar of thy Revelation, through Which the heavens of Thy power and Thy majesty have been illumined, acknowledging Thy signs, believing in Thy Book, and holding fast unto Thy Cord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009AWA in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/fy/</guid>
      <description>Ik priizgje Jo, o myn God, dat Jo my út &amp;rsquo;e sliep wekker makke hawwe en my út myn fuort-wêzen oproppen hawwe en my út myn slomme ferrize litten hawwe. Ik bin dizze moarn wekker wurden mei myn antlit heve nei de pracht fan de Dei-Stjer fan Jo iepenbiering dêr&amp;rsquo;t de himelen fan Jo macht en Jo majesteit troch ferljochte wurden binne; ik erken Jo tekens, leau yn Jo Boek en hâld fêst oan Jo koarde.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009AWA in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik loof U, o mijn God, dat Gij mij uit mijn slaap deed ontwaken en mij uit mijn verzonken-zijn hebt geroepen en mij uit mijn sluimer deed verrijzen. Ik ben deze morgen ontwaakt met mijn gelaat geheven naar de pracht van de Dagster van Uw Openbaring, die de hemelen van Uw macht en Uw majesteit heeft verlicht; ik erken Uw tekenen, geloof in Uw Boek en houd vast aan Uw koord.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
