<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH10505 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh10505/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH10505 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh10505/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10505 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O my God! Unite the hearts of Thy servants, and reveal to them Thy great purpose. May they follow Thy commandments and abide in Thy law. Help them, O God, in their endeavor, and grant them strength to serve Thee. O God! Leave them not to themselves, but guide their steps by the light of Thy knowledge, and cheer their hearts by Thy love. Verily, Thou art their Helper and their Lord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10505 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Dio! Ho mia Dio! Unuigu la korojn de Viaj servantoj kaj revelaciu al ili Vian grandan celon. Ili sekvu Viajn ordonojn kaj estu fidelaj al Via leĝo. Helpu ilin, ho Dio, en ilia penado kaj donu al ili forton por servi al Vi. Ho Dio! Ne lasu ilin solaj, sed gvidu iliajn paŝojn per la lumo de Via scio kaj ĝojigu iliajn korojn per Via amo. Vere, Vi estas ilia Helpanto kaj ilia Eternulo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10505 in Føroyar</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/fo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/fo/</guid>
      <description>O Gud mín! O Gud mín! Sameina hjørtuni hjá tænarum Tínum og opinbera fyri teimum Títt mikla endamál. Fylgi teir Tínum boðum og haldi teir seg til Tína lóg. Hjálp teimum, O Gud, í teirra strem- ban, og veit teimum styrki at tæna tær. O Gud! Eftirlat teir ikki til sín sjálvs, men leið teirra fóta fet við ljósi kunnleiks Tíns og upplívga hjørtu teirra við kærleika Tínum. Sanniliga, Tú ert teirra Hjálpari og teirra Harri.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10505 in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/fy/</guid>
      <description>O myn God! O myn God! Ferienigje de herten fan Jo tsjinners en iepenbierje oan harren Jo ferheven plan. Meie hja Jo geboaden neikomme en har hâlde oan Jo wet. Help harren, o God, yn har stribjen en jou harren krêft om Jo te tsjinjen. O God, lit harren net oan harsels oer, mar lied har trêden mei it ljocht fan Jo kennis en ferbliidzje har hert mei Jo leafde. Wierliken, Jo binne harren Helper en harren Hear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10505 in Papiamentu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/pap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unity/bh10505/pap/</guid>
      <description>*Oh, my God! Oh my God! Unite the hearts of Thy servants
O mi Dios! O mi Dios! Uni e kurasonnan di Bo sirbidornan i rebela nan Bo obhetivo grandi. Hasí nan sigi Bo mandamentunan i biba den Bo ley. Yuda nan, o Dios, den nan esfuerso, i duna nan forsa pa sirbi Bo. O Dios, no laga nan pa nan kuenta, pero guia nan pasonan ku e lus di Bo sabidoria, i hubilá nan kurasonnan den Bo amor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
