<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB11094 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab11094/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB11094 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab11094/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB11094 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab11094/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab11094/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O Thou forgiver of sins, bestower of gifts, dispeller of afflictions! Verily, I beseech thee to forgive the sins of such as have abandoned the physical garment and have ascended to the spiritual world. O my Lord! Purify them from trespasses, dispel their sorrows, and change their darkness into light. Cause them to enter the garden of happiness, cleanse them with the most pure water, and grant them to behold Thy splendors on the loftiest mount.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB11094 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab11094/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab11094/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh mi Dios! ¡Oh Tú perdonador de los pecados, el que confiere los dones, el que disipa las aflicciones! Verdaderamente, Te suplico que perdones los pecados de quienes han abandonado su vestidura física y han ascendido al mundo espiritual. ¡Oh mi Señor! Purifícalos de sus transgresiones, disipa sus tristezas y cambia su oscuridad en luz. Haz que entren en el jardín de la felicidad, límpialos con el agua purísima y permíteles contemplar Tus esplendores sobre las más sublimes alturas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB11094 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab11094/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab11094/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Dio! Ho Vi, pardonanto de pekoj, donacanto de bonoj, forpelanto de afliktoj! Vere, mi petegas Vin pardoni la pekojn de tiuj, kiuj lasis sian fizikan veston kaj ascendis en la mondon spiritan. Ho mia Eternulo! Purigu ilin de misfaroj, forpelu iliajn ĉagrenojn kaj sanĝu ilian sombron al lumo. Faru, ke ili eniru la ĝardenon de feliĉo, lavu ilin per la plej pura akvo kaj lasu ilin ekvidi Vian helegon sur la monto plej alta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB11094 in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab11094/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab11094/fy/</guid>
      <description>O myn God! O Jo, Ferjouwer fan sûnden! Skinker fan jeften! Ferdriuwer fan smerten! Wierliken, ik smeekje Jo de sûnden te ferjaan fan harren dy&amp;rsquo;t it stoflik klaad ôflein hawwe en nei de geastlike wrâld opstiigd binne. O myn Hear! Suverje harren fan oertrêdings, ferdriuw harren fertriet en feroarje harren tsjusterens yn ljocht. Lit harren de tún fan lok yngean, reinigje harren mei it suverste wetter en stean harren ta, Jo swidens op de ferhevenste berch te oanskôgjen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB11094 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab11094/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/departed/ab11094/nl/</guid>
      <description>O mijn God! O Gij die zonden vergeeft, gaven schenkt en kwellingen verdrijft! Waarlijk, ik smeek U de zonden te vergeven van hen die het stoffelijk gewaad hebben afgelegd en naar de geestelijke wereld zijn opgestegen. O mijn Heer! Zuiver hen van overtredingen, verdrijf hun droefheid en verander hun duisternis in licht. Doe hen de tuin van geluk betreden, reinig hen met het zuiverste water en laat hen Uw luister op de verhevenste berg aanschouwen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
