<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH07683 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh07683/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH07683 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh07683/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07683 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O King of eternity, and the Maker of nations, and the Fashioner of every moldering bone! I pray Thee, by Thy Name through which Thou didst call all mankind unto the horizon of Thy majesty and glory, and didst guide Thy servants to the court of Thy grace and favors, to number me with such as have rid themselves from everything except Thyself, and have set themselves towards Thee, and have not been kept back by such misfortunes as were decreed by Thee, from turning in the direction of Thy gifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07683 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Gloria a Ti, oh Rey de la eternidad, Hacedor de naciones y Modelador de todo hueso que se deshace! Te ruego, por Tu Nombre, mediante el cual llamaste a toda la humanidad hacia el horizonte de Tu majestad y gloria y guiaste a Tus siervos a la corte de Tu gracia y Tus favores, que me cuentes entre aquellos que se han librado de todo excepto de Ti y se han vuelto hacia Ti, y a quienes las desgracias que Tú has decretado no les han impedido volverse hacia Tus dádivas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07683 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/nl/</guid>
      <description>Glorie zij U, o Koning der eeuwigheid en de Maker van natiën, en de Vormer van ieder vermolmd gebeente! Ik smeek U, bij Uw Naam waardoor Gij de gehele mensheid tot de horizon van Uw majesteit en glorie hebt geroepen, en Uw dienaren tot het hof van Uw genade en gaven hebt geleid, mij te rekenen tot hen die zich van alles buiten U ontdaan hebben, en zich tot U gericht hebben, en zich door de tegenspoed die Gij hebt beschikt niet hebben laten weerhouden zich in de richting van Uw gaven te wenden.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
