<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Youth on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-youth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Youth on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-youth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00314HOR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab00314hor/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab00314hor/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! From the horizon of detachment Thou hast manifested souls that, even as the shining moon, shed radiance upon the realm of heart and soul, rid themselves from the attributes of the world of existence and hastened forth unto the kingdom of immortality. With a drop from the ocean of Thy loving-kindness Thou didst oft-times moisten the gardens of their hearts until they gained incomparable freshness and beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00949WIN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab00949win/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab00949win/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! Graciously bestow a pair of heavenly wings unto each of these fledglings, and give them spiritual power that they may wing their flight through this limitless space and may soar to the heights of the Abhá Kingdom. O Lord! Strengthen these fragile seedlings that each one may become a fruitful tree, verdant and flourishing. Render these souls victorious through the potency of Thy celestial hosts, that they may be able to crush the forces of error and ignorance and to unfurl the standard of fellowship and guidance amidst the people; that they may, even as the reviving breaths of the spring, refresh and quicken the trees of human souls and like unto vernal showers make the meads of that region green and fertile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02825 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab02825/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab02825/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise and glory be to Thee, O Lord my God! This is a choice sapling which Thou hast planted in the meads of Thy love and hast nurtured with the fingers of Thy Lordship. Thou hast watered it from the well-spring of everlasting life which streameth forth from the gardens of Thy oneness and Thou hast caused the clouds of Thy tender mercy to shower Thy favors upon it. It hath now grown and developed beneath the shelter of Thy blessings which are manifest from the Dayspring of Thy divine essence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10492 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! Bestow heavenly confirmation upon this daughter of the kingdom, and graciously aid her that she may remain firm and steadfast in Thy Cause and that she may, even as a nightingale of the rose garden of mysteries, warble melodies in the Abhá Kingdom in the most wondrous tones, thereby bringing happiness to everyone. Make her exalted among the daughters of the kingdom and enable her to attain life eternal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10492 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh bondadoso Señor! Otorga confirmaciones divinas a esta hija del reino, y ayúdala bondadosamente a que se mantenga firme y constante en Tu Causa y, cual ruiseñor del rosedal de los misterios, entone melodías en el Reino de Abhá con los más bellos acordes, y traiga con ello alegría a todos. Enaltécela entre las hijas del reino y permítele alcanzar la vida eterna. Tú eres el Otorgador, el Amoroso.
(Source category: Jóvenes) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10492 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij vriendelijk Heer! Schenk deze dochter van het koninkrijk hemelse gaven en help haar genadiglijk standvastig en sterk te blijven in Uw Zaak, opdat zij, gelijk een nachtegaal in de rozentuin van mysteriën, wonderschone melodieën mag zingen in het Abhá-koninkrijk en zo iedereen vreugde mag brengen. Verhef haar onder de dochters van het koninkrijk en laat haar eeuwig leven verwerven. Gij zijt de Schenker, de Liefderijke.
(Source category: Jongeren) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10703RAD in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Make this youth radiant, and confer Thy bounty upon this poor creature. Bestow upon him knowledge, grant him added strength at the break of every morn and guard him within the shelter of Thy protection so that he may be freed from error, may devote himself to the service of Thy Cause, may guide the wayward, lead the hapless, free the captives and awaken the heedless, that all may be blessed with Thy remembrance and praise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10703RAD in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Dio! Lumigu ĉi tiun junulon kaj favoru ĉi tiun malfortulon. Donacu al li scion, garantiu al li forton ĉiutage pliiĝantan kaj gardu lin sub la ŝirmo de Via protektado, tiel ke il estu pur-savita de ĉia peko, sindonu por la servo al Via Kredo, konduku la devojiĝintojn, gvidu la malriĉulojn kaj malfortulojn, liberigu la kaptitojn kaj veku la dormantojn, por ke ĉiuj estu benataj per rememoro kaj adoro al Vi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10703RAD in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10703rad/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Senhor! Torna radiante este jovem e derrama a Tua graça sobre este fraco! Concede-lhe conhecimento e, a cada amanhecer, aumenta-lhe as forças. Abriga-o no refúgio da Tua proteção para que seja libertado do erro, possa servir a Tua Causa, guiar os desviados, conduzir os infelizes, livrar os cativos e despertar os letárgicos; de modo que todos sejam abençoados com a Tua lembrança e louvor. És o Forte, o Poderoso.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
