<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Declaration of the Báb on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-declaration-of-the-b%C3%A1b/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Declaration of the Báb on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-declaration-of-the-b%C3%A1b/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8254 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8254/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8254/</guid>
      <description>#Lawh-i-Náqús ##Tablet of the Bell
He is the All-Glorious.
This is the garden of Paradise, wherein arise the anthems of God, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting; wherein ascend the soul-entrancing melodies warbled by the Nightingale of Eternity upon the twigs of the Divine Lote-Tree; wherein abide the Maids of Heaven whom none hath touched save God, the All-Glorious, the Most Holy; and wherein lieth enshrined that which draweth the needy to the shores of the ocean of true wealth and guideth the people to the Word of God.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8255 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8255/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8255/</guid>
      <description>#Lawh-i-Ghulámu’l-Khuld ##Tablet of the Immortal Youth
This is a remembrance of that which was revealed in the year sixty in the days of God, the Almighty, the Help in Peril, the All-Glorious, the All-Knowing.
Lo, the gates of Paradise were unlocked, and the hallowed Youth came forth bearing a serpent plain.[15] Rejoice! This is the immortal Youth, come with crystal waters. Upon His face was a veil woven by the fingers of might and power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8256 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8256/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8256/</guid>
      <description>He is the Ever-Abiding, the Most Exalted, the Most Great.
Lo, the Tongue of Glory hath called aloud and the Word of God hath cried out, proclaiming: “The Kingdom is God’s, the Creator of the heavens and the Lord of all names!” And yet the people, for the most part, are heedless. The entire creation resoundeth with the melodies of the All-Merciful, the realms of sanctity are redolent with the fragrance of His raiment, and the Most Great Name hath shed the splendour of His glory upon all who dwell on earth, and yet the people are wrapped in a palpable veil.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
