<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Marriage on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-marriage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Marriage on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-marriage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02596 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/marriage/ab02596/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/marriage/ab02596/en/</guid>
      <description>O my Lord! O my Lord! These two bright orbs are wedded in Thy love, conjoined in servitude to Thy Holy Threshold, united in ministering to thy Cause. Make Thou this marriage to be as threading lights of Thine abounding grace, O my Lord, the All-Merciful, and luminous rays of Thy bestowals, O Thou the Beneficent, the Ever-Giving, that there may branch out from this great tree boughs that will grow green and flourishing through the gifts that rain down from Thy clouds of grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB05652WIS in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ab05652wis/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ab05652wis/en/</guid>
      <description>He is God! O peerless Lord! In Thine almighty wisdom Thou hast enjoined marriage upon the peoples, that the generations of men may succeed one another in this contingent world, and that ever, so long as the world shall last, they may busy themselves at the Threshold of Thy oneness with servitude and worship, with salutation, adoration and praise. “I have not created spirits and men, but that they should worship me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB07158 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/marriage/ab07158/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/marriage/ab07158/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be unto Thee, O my God! Verily, this thy servant and this Thy maidservant have gathered under the shadow of Thy mercy and they are united through Thy favor and generosity. O Lord! Assist them in this Thy world and Thy kingdom and destine for them every good through Thy bounty and grace. O Lord! Confirm them in Thy servitude and assist them in Thy service. Suffer them to become the signs of Thy Name in Thy world and protect them through Thy bestowals which are inexhaustible in this world and the world to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00001ABI in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/marriage/bh00001abi/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/marriage/bh00001abi/en/</guid>
      <description>*“Bahá’í marriage is union and cordial affection between the two parties. They must, however, exercise the utmost care and become acquainted with each other&amp;rsquo;s character. This eternal bond should be made secure by a firm covenant, and the intention should be to foster harmony, fellowship and unity and to attain everlasting life.” —‘Abdu’l-Bahá
The pledge of marriage, the verse to be spoken individually by the bride and the bridegroom in the presence of at least two witnesses acceptable to the Spiritual Assembly is, as stipulated in the Kitáb-i-Aqdas (The Most Holy Book):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03181 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/marriage/bh03181/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/marriage/bh03181/en/</guid>
      <description>He is the Bestower, the Bounteous! Praise be to God, the Ancient, the Ever-Abiding, the Changeless, the Eternal! He Who hath testified in His Own Being that verily He is the One, the Single, the Untrammelled, the Exalted. We bear witness that verily there is no God but Him, acknowledging His oneness, confessing His singleness. He hath ever dwelt in unapproachable heights, in the summits of His loftiness, sanctified from the mention of aught save Himself, free from the description of aught but Him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12965 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12965/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12965/</guid>
      <description>*Man na meri, taim tupela i laik marit, wan wan i mas autim Tok Promis bilong Marit long ai bilong tupela pesman, husat Spiritual Asembli bilong Ples i bin makim. Bahá’íullÆh i bin raitim dispela Tok Promis bilong Marit insait long Buk i Holi Tru, em Kitab-i-Aqdas, olsem:
*&amp;ldquo;Tru tumas, bai mipela olgeta i bihainim Laik bilong God.&amp;rdquo;
*The pledge of marriage, the verse to be spoken individually by the bride and the bridegroom in the presence of at least two witnesses acceptable to the Spiritual Assembly is written in the Most Holy Book, the Kitab-i-Aqdas, as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12966 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12966/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12966/</guid>
      <description>Em I Givim Planti Samting! Em i Save Blesim Oltaim!
Litimapim nem bilong God, God Bilong Taim Bipo. Em I Save Stap Oltaim. Em I No Save Senis. Em I Stap Oltaim Oltaim! God i singaut long Spirit bilong En Yet. Em i singaut olsem, tru tumas, Em Wanpela Tasol I Stap. I No Gat Wanpela Samting I Ken Banisim God. Em I Stap Antap Tru. Tru tumas. Mipela i tokaut olsem, i no gat narapela God.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
