<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH09508 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09508/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH09508 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09508/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09508 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09508/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09508/en/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O my God! I yield Thee thanks that Thou hast made known unto me Him who is the Dayspring of Thy mercy, and the Dawning-Place of Thy grace, and the Repository of Thy Cause. I beseech Thee by Thy Name, through which the faces of them that are nigh unto Thee have turned white, and the hearts of such as are devoted to Thee have winged their flight towards Thee, to grant that I may, at all times and under all conditions, lay hold on Thy cord, and be rid of all attachment to anyone except Thee, and may keep mine eyes directed towards the horizon of Thy Revelation, and may carry out what Thou hast prescribed unto me in Thy Tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09508 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09508/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09508/pt/</guid>
      <description>Glorificado és Tu, ó meu Deus! Agradeço-Te por me haveres feito conhecer Aquele que é o Alvorecer da Tua mercê, a Aurora da Tua graça e o Santuário da Tua Causa. Imploro-Te, pelo Teu Nome, através do qual se tornaram níveas as faces dos que estão próximos de Ti, e os corações dos Teus devotos alçaram voo na Tua direção - possa eu, em todos os tempos e sob todas as condições, segurar-me à corda que a Ti me prende, livrar-me de todo o apego que não seja a Ti, manter os olhos dirigidos ao horizonte da Tua Revelação e realizar o que me prescreveste nas Tuas Epístolas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
