<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-ABU0070GAT on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-abu0070gat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-ABU0070GAT on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-abu0070gat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0070GAT in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! These are Thy servants who have gathered in this meeting, have turned unto Thy kingdom and are in need of Thy bestowal and blessing. O Thou God! Manifest and make evident the signs of Thy oneness which have been deposited in all the realities of life. Reveal and unfold the virtues which Thou hast made latent and concealed in these human realities.
O God! We are as plants, and Thy bounty is as the rain; refresh and cause these plants to grow through Thy bestowal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0070GAT in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh bondadoso Señor! Estos son Tus siervos que han concurrido a esta reunión, se han vuelto hacia Tu reino y necesitan Tus dádivas y bendiciones. ¡Oh Dios! Manifiesta y haz evidentes las señales de Tu unicidad que han sido depositadas en todas las realidades de la vida. Revela y despliega las virtudes que has dejado latentes y ocultas en estas realidades humanas. ¡Oh Dios! Nosotros somos como plantas y Tu generosidad es como la lluvia; refresca y haz crecer estas plantas mediante Tu favor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0070GAT in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Vi, bonema Dio! Jen Viaj geservantoj, kiuj kolektiĝis en tiu ĉi kunveno, sin turnis al Via regno kaj bezonas Vian favoron kaj benon. Ho Vi Dio! Malkaŝu kaj evidentigu la signojn de Via ununureco entenatajn en ĉiuj realoj de la vivo. Revelaciu kaj disvolvu la virtojn, kiujn Vi metis latentaj kaj kaŝitaj en tiujn ĉi homajn realojn. Ho Dio! Ni estas kvazaŭ plantoj, kaj Via malavaro estas kiel la pluvo; refresigu kaj kreskigu tiujn ĉi plantojn per Via donacado.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
