<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB10769 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab10769/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB10769 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab10769/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10769 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/en/</guid>
      <description>O my Lord, my Beloved, my Desire! Befriend me in my loneliness and accompany me in my exile. Remove my sorrow. Cause me to be devoted to Thy beauty. Withdraw me from all else save Thee. Attract me through Thy fragrances of holiness. Cause me to be associated in Thy Kingdom with those who are severed from all else save Thee, who long to serve Thy sacred threshold and who stand to work in Thy Cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10769 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Sinjoro, mia Amato, mia Deziro! Konsolu min en mia soleco kaj akompanu min en mia ekzilo. Forigu mian ĉagrenon. Faru min fidela al Via beleco. Senigu min de ĉio krom Vi. Allogu min per la bonodoro de Via sankteco. Kunigu min en Via Regno kun tiuj, kiuj seniĝis de ĉio krom Vi kaj alstrebas servi ĉe Via sankta sojlo, pretaj labori por Via Afero. Ebligu al mi esti unu el Viaj servantinoj, kiu atingis Vian bonfavoron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10769 in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/ab10769/it/</guid>
      <description>O mio Signore, mio Benamato, mio Desìo! Siimi Amico nella solitudine e Compagno nell’esilio. Allontana il mio dolore e fa’ ch’io sia devota alla Tua bellezza. Tienimi lontana da tutto fuorché da Te. Attirami con le Tue fragranze di santità. Fa’ ch’io sia unita, nel Tuo Regno, a coloro che sono distaccati da tutto fuorché da Te, che anelano a servire la Tua sacra soglia e che lavorano nella Tua Causa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
