<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB00044PRO on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00044pro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB00044PRO on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00044pro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00044PRO in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00044pro/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00044pro/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou Provider! Thou hast breathed over the friends in the West the sweet fragrance of the Holy Spirit, and with the light of divine guidance Thou hast lit up the western sky. Thou hast made those who were once remote to draw near unto Thyself; Thou hast turned strangers into loving friends; Thou hast awakened those who slept; Thou hast made the heedless mindful.
O Thou Provider! Assist Thou these noble friends to win Thy good pleasure, and make them well wishers of stranger and friend alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00044PRO in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00044pro/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/ab00044pro/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij Verzorger! Gij hebt de zoete geur van de Heilige Geest over de vrienden in het Westen geademd en met het licht van goddelijke leiding de westelijke hemel verlicht. Gij hebt hen die ooit veraf waren nader tot Uzelf gebracht; Gij hebt vreemden in liefdevolle vrienden veranderd; Gij hebt de slapenden doen ontwaken; Gij hebt de achtelozen opmerkzaam gemaakt. O Gij Verzorger! Sta deze nobele vrienden bij om Uw welbehagen te verwerven en laat hen mensen worden die het goed voor hebben met zowel vriend als vreemdeling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
