<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Teaching on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-teaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Teaching on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-teaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00156LOW in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/en/</guid>
      <description>Thou seest me, O my God, bowed down in lowliness, humbling myself before Thy commandments, submitting to Thy sovereignty, trembling at the might of Thy dominion, fleeing from Thy wrath, entreating Thy grace, relying upon Thy forgiveness, shaking with awe at Thy fury. I implore Thee with a throbbing heart, with streaming tears and a yearning soul, and in complete detachment from all things, to make Thy lovers as rays of light across Thy realms, and to aid Thy chosen servants to exalt Thy Word, that their faces may turn beauteous and bright with splendor, that their hearts may be filled with mysteries, and that every soul may lay down its burden of sin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00156LOW in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/nl/</guid>
      <description>Gij ziet mij nederig geknield, o mijn God, deemoedig voor Uw geboden, onderworpen aan Uw soevereiniteit, huiverend voor de macht van Uw heerschappij, vluchtend voor Uw gramschap, smekend om Uw genade, vertrouwend op Uw vergiffenis, bevend van ontzag voor Uw toorn. Ik smeek U met bonzend hart, stromende tranen en smachtende ziel, en in volledige onthechting van alle dingen, om Uw minnaars te maken als lichtstralen door al Uw rijken, en Uw uitverkoren dienaren te helpen Uw Woord te verheerlijken, opdat hun gelaat mag stralen van pracht en schoonheid, hun hart vervuld mag worden van mysteriën, en iedere ziel zijn zondenlast mag afleggen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00156LOW in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00156low/pt/</guid>
      <description>Vês-me, ó meu Deus, prostrado em submissão, humilde ante os Teus mandamentos, submisso ante a Tua soberania, estremecendo frente ao poder de Teu domínio, fugindo de Tua ira, suplicando Tua graça, confiando no Teu perdão e trémulo de temor ante a Tua fúria. Imploro-te, com o coração a palpitar, os olhos plenos de lágrimas, a alma anelante e com absoluto desprendimento de tudo, que faças daqueles que Te amam raios de luz através dos Teus reinos e que auxilies os Teus servos eleitos a exaltarem a Tua Palavra, para que suas frontes se façam formosas e resplandecentes, os seus corações fiquem repletos de mistérios, e toda a alma se livre do fardo dos seus pecados.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00189AID in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00189aid/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00189aid/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! Aid Thou Thy trusted servants to have loving and tender hearts. Help them to spread, amongst all the nations of the earth, the light of guidance that cometh from the Company on high. Verily, Thou art the Strong, the Powerful, the Mighty, the All-Subduing, the Ever-Giving. Verily, Thou art the Generous, the Gentle, the Tender, the Most Bountiful.
(Source category: Teaching) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 327)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00189AID in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00189aid/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab00189aid/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Deus, meu Deus! Ajuda os Teus servos fiéis a possuírem corações ternos e amorosos. Ajuda-os a difundir, dentre todas as nações da terra, a luz de guia que emana das Hostes celestiais. Verdadeiramente, Tu és o Forte, o Poderoso, o Potente, o Predominante, Aquele que sempre confere dádivas. Verdadeiramente, Tu és o Generoso, o Benigno, o Terno, a Suprema Bondade.
(Source category: Ensino) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 1109)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB05167 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab05167/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab05167/en/</guid>
      <description>Thou knowest, O God, and art my witness that I have no desire in my heart save to attain Thy good pleasure, to be confirmed in servitude unto Thee, to consecrate myself in Thy service, to labor in Thy great vineyard and to sacrifice all in Thy path. Thou art the All-Knowing and the All-Seeing. I have no wish save to turn my steps, in my love for Thee, towards the mountains and the deserts to loudly proclaim the advent of Thy Kingdom, and to raise Thy call amidst all men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB05805SER in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab05805ser/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab05805ser/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God, aid Thou Thy servant to raise up the Word, and to refute what is vain and false, to establish the truth, to spread the sacred verses abroad, reveal the splendors, and make the morning&amp;rsquo;s light to dawn in the hearts of the righteous. Thou art, verily, the Generous, the Forgiving.
(Source category: Teaching) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 326)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB05805SER in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab05805ser/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/ab05805ser/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Dio, helpu Vian servanton levi alten la Vorton kaj refuti, kio estas vana kaj falsa, kaj establi la veron, dissemi la sanktajn versojn, riveli la radiojn kaj briligi la matenan lumon en la koroj de la fidelaj. Vi estas vere la Donema, la Pardonanta.
(Source category: Instruado) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 4334)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00223MAG in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh00223mag/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh00223mag/en/</guid>
      <description>Say: Magnified be Thy Name, O Lord my God! I beseech Thee by Thy Name through which the splendor of the light of wisdom shone resplendent when the heavens of divine utterance were set in motion amidst mankind, to graciously aid me by Thy heavenly confirmations and enable me to extol Thy Name amongst Thy servants. O Lord! Unto Thee have I turned my face, detatched from all save Thee and holding fast to the hem of the robe of Thy manifold blessings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00308DES in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh00308des/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh00308des/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be unto Thee, O Lord of the world and Desire of the nations, O Thou Who hast become manifest in the Greatest Name, whereby the pearls of wisdom and utterance have appeared from the shells of the great sea of Thy knowledge, and the heavens of divine revelation have been adorned with the light of the appearance of the sun of Thy countenance. I beg of Thee, by that Word through which Thy proof was perfected among Thy creatures and Thy testimony was fulfilled amidst Thy servants, to strengthen Thy people in that whereby the face of the Cause will radiate in Thy dominion, the standards of Thy power will be planted among Thy servants, and the banners of Thy guidance will be raised throughout Thy dominions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00308DES in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh00308des/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh00308des/nl/</guid>
      <description>Glorie zij U, o Gij Heer van de wereld en het Verlangen der natiën, o Gij die openbaar geworden zijt in de Grootste Naam, waarbij de parelen van wijsheid en woorden uit de schelpen van de grote zee Uwer kennis te voorschijn zijn gekomen en de hemelen van goddelijke Openbaring werden getooid met het licht van de opkomst van de zon Uws aanschijns. Ik smeek U – bij dat Woord waardoor Uw bewijs onder Uw schepselen werd vervolmaakt en Uw getuigenis onder Uw dienaren werd voltooid – om Uw volk te sterken in hetgeen waardoor het aanzicht van de Zaak in Uw rijk zal stralen, en de vaandels van Uw macht onder Uw dienaren zullen worden geplant en de banieren van Uw leiding in al Uw rijken zullen worden geheven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08242 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08242/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08242/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise be to Thee, O Lord my God! I implore Thee, by Thy Name which none hath befittingly recognized, and whose import no soul hath fathomed; I beseech Thee, by Him Who is the Fountainhead of Thy Revelation and the Dayspring of Thy signs, to make my heart to be a receptacle of Thy love and of remembrance of Thee. Knit it, then, to Thy most great Ocean, that from it may flow out the living waters of Thy wisdom and the crystal streams of Thy glorification and praise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08242 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08242/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08242/pt/</guid>
      <description>Louvado sejas Tu, ó Senhor meu Deus! Imploro-Te, pelo Teu Nome, o qual jamais foi devidamente reconhecido, cuja significação nenhuma alma sondou, e suplico-Te, por Aquele que é o Manancial da Tua Revelação e o Alvorecer dos Teus sinais, que faças do meu coração um recetáculo do Teu amor e da Tua lembrança. Liga-o, pois, ao Teu mais grandioso Oceano para que assim por ele fluam as águas vivas da Tua sabedoria e as correntes cristalinas da Tua glorificação e do Teu louvor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08363 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08363/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08363/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, Who art the Author of all Manifestations, the Source of all Sources, the Fountainhead of all Revelations, and the Wellspring of all Lights! I testify that by Thy Name the heaven of understanding hath been adorned, and the ocean of utterance hath surged, and the dispensations of Thy providence have been promulgated unto the followers of all religions. I beseech Thee so to enrich me as to dispense with all save Thee, and be made independent of anyone except Thyself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08363 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08363/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08363/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh Dios, Quien eres el Autor de todas las Manifestaciones, el Origen de todos los Orígenes, la Fuente de todas las Revelaciones y el Manantial de todas las Luces! Atestiguo que, mediante Tu Nombre, el cielo de la comprensión ha sido adornado, y se ha encrespado el océano de la expresión, y las dispensaciones de Tu providencia han sido promulgadas a los seguidores de todas las religiones. Te imploro que me enriquezcas de tal modo que prescinda de todo salvo de Ti y me desligue de cualquiera que no seas Tú.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08433 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/en/</guid>
      <description>Magnified be Thy name, O my God, for that Thou hast manifested the Day which is the King of Days, the Day which Thou didst announce unto Thy chosen Ones and Thy Prophets in Thy most excellent Tablets, the Day whereon Thou didst shed the splendor of the glory of all Thy names upon all created things. Great is his blessedness whosoever hath set himself towards Thee, and entered Thy presence, and caught the accents of Thy voice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08433 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/eo/</guid>
      <description>Laŭdegata estu Via nomo, ho mia Dio, ĉar Vi manifestis tiun Tagon, kiu estas la Reĝo de la Tagoj, la Tagon, kiun Vi anoncis al Viaj Elektitoj kaj Viaj Profetoj en Viaj plej elstaraj Epistoloj, la Tagon, en kiu Vi elverŝis la lumon de la gloro de ĉiuj Viaj nomoj super la tuta kreitaro. Granda estas la beniteco de ĉiu ajn, kiu direktis sin al Vi kaj eniris Vian ĉeeston kaj kaptis la sonojn de Via voĉo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08433 in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/fr/</guid>
      <description>Magnifié soit ton nom, ô mon Dieu, car tu as révélé le jour qui est le roi des jours, le jour annoncé à tes élus et à tes prophètes dans tes épîtres les plus merveilleuses, le jour où tu as répandu la splendeur de la gloire de tous tes noms sur toutes choses créées. Béni celui qui avance vers toi, parvient en ta présence et perçoit les intonations de ta voix.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
