<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Firmness in the Covenant on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-firmness-in-the-covenant/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Firmness in the Covenant on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-firmness-in-the-covenant/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00065STE in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab00065ste/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab00065ste/en/</guid>
      <description>O my Lord and my Hope! Help Thou Thy loved ones to be steadfast in Thy mighty Covenant, to remain faithful to Thy manifest Cause, and to carry out the commandments Thou didst set down for them in Thy Book of Splendors; that they may become banners of guidance and lamps of the Company above, wellsprings of Thine infinite wisdom, and stars that lead aright, as they shine down from the supernal sky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00065STE in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab00065ste/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab00065ste/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Sinjoro kaj mia espero! Helpu Vi la amatojn Viajn persisti en Via potenca Interligo, resti fidela al Via evidenta Afero kaj efektivigi la ordonojn, kiujn Vi por ili dekretis en Via Libro de l’ Splendoroj; por ke ili fariĝu standardoj de l’ gvidado kaj lampoj de l’ Kompanio supra, fontoj de Via saĝo senlima kaj steloj ĝuste direktantaj brilante desur la ĉielaj altoj. Vere estas Vi la Nevenkebla, la Ĉiopova, la Ĉiopotenca.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02342AWA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/en/</guid>
      <description>O compassionate God! Thanks be to Thee for Thou hast awakened and made me conscious. Thou hast given me a seeing eye and favored me with a hearing ear, hast led me to Thy kingdom and guided me to Thy path. Thou hast shown me the right way and caused me to enter the ark of deliverance. O God! Keep me steadfast and make me firm and staunch. Protect me from violent tests and preserve and shelter me in the strongly fortified fortress of Thy Covenant and Testament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02342AWA in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Vi kompatema Dio! Dankoj estu al Vi por ke Vi vekis kaj konsciigis min. Vi donis al mi vidantajn okulojn kaj donacis al mi aŭdantajn orelojn. Vi kondukis min al Via regno kaj gvidis min sur Vian vojon. Vi montris al mi la ĝustan direkton kaj igis min eniri la Arkeon de Saviĝo. Ho Dio! Igu min konstanta, firma kaj fidela. Protektu min de teruraj provoj kaj gardu kaj ŝirmu min en la fortikaĵo de Via Sankta Interligo kaj Testamento.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02342AWA in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/nl/</guid>
      <description>O meedogende God! Dank zij U, daar Gij mij hebt gewekt en bewust hebt gemaakt. Gij hebt mij een waarnemend oog gegeven en mij begunstigd met een luisterend oor, mij naar Uw koninkrijk gevoerd en mij naar Uw pad geleid. Gij hebt mij het rechte pad getoond en mij de ark van verlossing doen binnengaan. O God! Laat mij standvastig blijven, en maak mij vastberaden en trouw. Bescherm mij tegen hevige beproevingen, bewaar en beschut mij in de zwaar versterkte vesting van Uw Verbond en Testament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB06211 in Deutsch</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab06211/de/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab06211/de/</guid>
      <description>Mache unsere Schritte fest auf Deinem Pfad, o Herr, und stärke unsere Herzen in Deinem Gehorsam. Wende unser Angesicht der Schönheit Deiner Einzigkeit zu und erfreue unser Herz mit den Zeichen Deiner göttlichen Einheit. Schmücke unseren Leib mit dem Gewande Deiner Großmut, nimm uns den Schleier der Sündhaftigkeit von den Augen und reiche uns den Kelch Deiner Gnade, damit das innerste Wesen aller Geschöpfe vor dem Anblick Deiner Größe Dein Lob singe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB06211 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab06211/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab06211/en/</guid>
      <description>Make firm our steps, O Lord, in Thy path and strengthen Thou our hearts in Thine obedience. Turn our faces toward the beauty of Thy oneness, and gladden our bosoms with the signs of Thy divine unity. Adorn our bodies with the robe of Thy bounty, and remove from our eyes the veil of sinfulness, and give us the chalice of Thy grace; that the essence of all beings may sing Thy praise before the vision of Thy grandeur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB06211 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab06211/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab06211/es/</guid>
      <description>Haz firmes nuestros pasos, oh Señor, en Tu sendero y fortalece nuestros corazones en Tu obediencia. Dirige nuestros rostros hacia la belleza de Tu unicidad y alegra nuestros pechos con las señales de Tu divina unidad. Adorna nuestros cuerpos con el manto de Tu generosidad, retira de nuestros ojos el velo de la transgresión y danos el cáliz de Tu gracia, para que la esencia de todos los seres cante Tu alabanza ante la visión de Tu grandeza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB06211 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab06211/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab06211/pt/</guid>
      <description>Faze firmes os nossos passos no Teu caminho, ó Senhor, e fortalece os nossos corações em obediência a Ti. Que as nossas faces se volvam para a beleza da Tua unidade e o íntimo das nossas almas se alegre com os sinais da Tua unicidade divina. Com as vestes da Tua bondade, adorna os nossos corpos; remove dos nossos olhos o véu do pecado e dá-nos o cálice da Tua graça, para que a essência de todos os seres cante louvores a Ti, ante a visão da Tua grandeza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07469 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/en/</guid>
      <description>He is the Mighty, the Pardoner, the Compassionate! O God, my God! Thou beholdest Thy servants in the abyss of perdition and error; where is Thy light of divine guidance, O Thou the Desire of the world? Thou knowest their helplessness and their feebleness; where is Thy power, O Thou in Whose grasp lie the powers of heaven and earth? I ask Thee, O Lord my God, by the splendor of the lights of Thy loving-kindness and the billows of the ocean of Thy knowledge and wisdom and by Thy Word wherewith Thou hast swayed the peoples of Thy dominion, to grant that I may be one of them that have observed Thy bidding in Thy Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07469 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/nl/</guid>
      <description>Hij is de Machtige, de Verontschuldiger, de Meedogende! O God, mijn God! Gij ziet Uw dienaren in de peilloze diepte van verderf en dwaling; waar is het licht van Uw goddelijke leiding, o Gij het Verlangen der wereld? Gij kent hun hulpeloosheid en hun zwakheid; waar is Uw kracht, o Gij in Wiens greep de krachten van hemel en aarde liggen? Ik vraag U, o Heer mijn God, bij de pracht van het licht van Uw goedertierenheid en de golven van de oceaan van Uw kennis en wijsheid en bij Uw Woord waarmee Gij de volkeren van Uw heerschappij overtuigt, te geven dat ik mag behoren tot hen die zich aan de geboden in Uw Boek hebben gehouden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07469 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07469/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ele é o Poderoso, o Supremo Perdão, o Compassivo! Ó Deus, meu Deus! Vês os Teus servos no abismo da perdição e do erro: onde está a luz da Tua divina orientação, ó Tu, Desejo do mundo? Conheces o seu desamparo e a sua fraqueza: onde está o Teu poder, ó Tu em cujas mãos estão os poderes do céu e da terra? Peço-Te, ó Senhor, meu Deus – pelo esplendor das luzes da Tua benevolência e pelas ondas do oceano do Teu conhecimento e da Tua sabedoria, e pela Tua Palavra, com a qual governaste os povos do Teu domínio – peço-Te que eu seja um dos que observaram o Teu mandamento no Teu Livro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07683 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O King of eternity, and the Maker of nations, and the Fashioner of every moldering bone! I pray Thee, by Thy Name through which Thou didst call all mankind unto the horizon of Thy majesty and glory, and didst guide Thy servants to the court of Thy grace and favors, to number me with such as have rid themselves from everything except Thyself, and have set themselves towards Thee, and have not been kept back by such misfortunes as were decreed by Thee, from turning in the direction of Thy gifts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07683 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Gloria a Ti, oh Rey de la eternidad, Hacedor de naciones y Modelador de todo hueso que se deshace! Te ruego, por Tu Nombre, mediante el cual llamaste a toda la humanidad hacia el horizonte de Tu majestad y gloria y guiaste a Tus siervos a la corte de Tu gracia y Tus favores, que me cuentes entre aquellos que se han librado de todo excepto de Ti y se han vuelto hacia Ti, y a quienes las desgracias que Tú has decretado no les han impedido volverse hacia Tus dádivas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07683 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/bh07683/nl/</guid>
      <description>Glorie zij U, o Koning der eeuwigheid en de Maker van natiën, en de Vormer van ieder vermolmd gebeente! Ik smeek U, bij Uw Naam waardoor Gij de gehele mensheid tot de horizon van Uw majesteit en glorie hebt geroepen, en Uw dienaren tot het hof van Uw genade en gaven hebt geleid, mij te rekenen tot hen die zich van alles buiten U ontdaan hebben, en zich tot U gericht hebben, en zich door de tegenspoed die Gij hebt beschikt niet hebben laten weerhouden zich in de richting van Uw gaven te wenden.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
