<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH09401 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09401/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH09401 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09401/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09401 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh09401/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh09401/en/</guid>
      <description>All praise, O my God, be to Thee Who art the Source of all glory and majesty, of greatness and honor, of sovereignty and dominion, of loftiness and grace, of awe and power. Whomsoever Thou willest Thou causest to draw nigh unto the Most Great Ocean, and on whomsoever Thou desirest Thou conferrest the honor of recognizing Thy Most Ancient Name. Of all who are in heaven and on earth, none can withstand the operation of Thy sovereign Will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09401 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh09401/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh09401/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ĉiuj laŭdoj, ho mia Dio, estu al Vi, Kiu estas la Fonto de ĉia gloro kaj majesto, de grandeco kaj honoro, de suvereneco kaj reĝeco, de alteco kaj favoro, de sankta timo kaj potenco. Kiun ajn Vi volas, Vi altiras al la Plej Sankta Oceano, kaj al kiu ajn Vi deziras, Vi donacas la honoron konfesi Vian Eternan Nomon. El ĉiuj, kiuj estas en la ĉielo kaj sur la tero, neniu povas rezisti la efikon de Via suverena volo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09401 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh09401/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/praise-and-gratitude/bh09401/nl/</guid>
      <description>Alle lof, o mijn God, zij U die de bron zijt van alle glorie en majesteit, van grootheid en eer, van soevereiniteit en heerschappij, van verhevenheid en genade, van ontzag en macht. Al wie Gij wilt doet Gij de Allergrootste Oceaan naderen, en al wie Gij verkiest verleent Gij de eer Uw Aloude Naam te erkennen. Van allen die in de hemel en op aarde zijn kan niemand de werking van Uw soevereine wil weerstaan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
