<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Triumph of the Cause on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-triumph-of-the-cause/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Triumph of the Cause on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-triumph-of-the-cause/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00065KIN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! Praise be unto Thee for kindling the fire of divine love in the Holy Tree on the summit of the loftiest mount: that Tree which is “neither of the East nor of the West,”¹ that fire which blazed out till the flame of it soared upward to the Concourse on high, and from it those realities caught the light of guidance, and cried out: “Verily have we perceived a fire on the slope of Mount Sinai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00065KIN in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/nl/</guid>
      <description>O God, mijn God! Geprezen zijt Gij dat Gij het vuur van goddelijke liefde in de Heilige Boom op de top van de verhevenste berg hebt ontstoken; die Boom die “noch van het Oosten, noch van het Westen” is, dat vuur dat oplaaide tot de vlam ervan tot de hemelse Scharen omhoog steeg, en deze werkelijkheden daaruit het licht van leiding opvingen, waarna zij uitriepen: “Waarlijk hebben wij een vuur op de helling van de berg Sinaï ontwaard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00065KIN in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00065kin/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Deus, meu Deus! Louvores a Ti por haveres ateado o fogo do amor divino na Árvore Sagrada - a qual “não é nem do Oriente nem do Ocidente”, sita no cume da mais elevada montanha; fogo esse que se abrasou até a sua flama se elevar e atingir a Assembleia do alto, cujas realidades dela colheram a luz da guia e bradaram: “Percebemos, verdadeiramente, um fogo na encosta do Monte Sinai”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00527 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00527/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00527/en/</guid>
      <description>He is God! O Lord, my God, my Well-Beloved! These are servants of Thine that have heard Thy Voice, given ear to Thy Word and hearkened to Thy Call. They have believed in Thee, witnessed Thy Wonders, acknowledged Thy proof and testified to Thine evidence. They have walked in Thy ways, followed Thy guidance, discovered Thy mysteries, comprehended the secrets of Thy Book, the verses of Thy Scrolls, and the tidings of Thy Epistles and Tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00527 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00527/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/ab00527/nl/</guid>
      <description>Hij is God! O Heer, mijn God, mijn Inniggeliefde! Dit zijn Uw dienaren die Uw stem hebben gehoord, die Uw woord hebben beluisterd en gehoor hebben gegeven aan Uw roep. Zij geloven in U, hebben Uw wondere daden aanschouwd, Uw bewijs erkend en getuigenis van U afgelegd. Zij hebben Uw wegen bewandeld, Uw leiding gevolgd, Uw mysteriën ontdekt en de geheimen van Uw boek, de verzen van Uw geschriften en de boodschappen van Uw brieven en tafelen begrepen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00002ENA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00002ena/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00002ena/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Enable all the peoples of the earth to gain admittance into the Paradise of Thy Faith, so that no created being may remain beyond the bounds of Thy good-pleasure. From time immemorial Thou hast been potent to do what pleaseth Thee and transcendent above whatsoever Thou desirest.
(Source category: Triumph of the Cause) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 351)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00002ENA in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00002ena/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00002ena/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Eternulo! Ebligu al ĉiuj popoloj de la mondo akiri enlason en la Paradizon de Via Kredo, por ke neniu kreito restu ekster la limoj de Via bonŝato. De pratempoj Vi estas potenca fari kio ajn plaĉas al Vi kaj transcendanta ĉion ajn, kion Vi deziras.
(Source category: Triumfo de la Afero) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 4358)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00004REN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be unto Thee, O Lord, Thou Who hast brought into being all created things, through the power of Thy behest. O Lord! Assist those who have renounced all else but Thee, and grant them a mighty victory. Send down upon them, O Lord, the concourse of the angels in heaven and earth and all that is between, to aid Thy servants, to succor and strengthen them, to enable them to achieve success, to sustain them, to invest them with glory, to confer upon them honor and exaltation, to enrich them and to make them triumphant with a wondrous triumph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00004REN in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/es/</guid>
      <description>Gloria sea a Ti, oh Señor, Tú que has traído a la existencia todas las cosas creadas, mediante el poder de Tu mandato. ¡Oh Señor! Ayuda a aquellos que han renunciado a todo cuanto no seas Tú, y confiéreles una gran victoria. ¡Oh Señor! Haz descender sobre ellos el concurso de los ángeles del cielo y de la tierra y de todo cuanto hay entre ellos, para que asistan a Tus siervos, los socorran y los fortalezcan, les faciliten el éxito, los apoyen, los invistan de gloria, les confieran honor y exaltación, los enriquezcan y les hagan triunfar con una maravillosa victoria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00004REN in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/eo/</guid>
      <description>Gloro estu al Vi, ho Eternulo, Vi Kiu ekzistigis ĉion kreitan per la potenco de Via ordono. Ho Eternulo! Asistu tiujn, kiuj abnegaciis ĉion alian krom Vi, kaj donu al ili grandan venkon. Sendu sur ilin, ho Eternulo, la tutan aron da anĝeloj en la ĉielo kaj sur la tero kaj ĉie inter tiuj, por helpi Viajn servantojn, por asisti kaj fortigi ilin, por igi ilin kapablaj atingi sukceson, por subteni ilin, por kroni ilin per gloro, por doni al ili honoron kaj altecon, por riĉigi ilin kaj por igi ilin triumfantaj en brila venko.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00147GRO in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00147gro/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00147gro/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Provide for the speedy growth of the Tree of Thy divine Unity; water it then, O Lord, with the flowing waters of Thy good-pleasure, and cause it, before the revelations of Thy divine assurance, to yield such fruits as Thou desirest for Thy glorification and exaltation, Thy praise and thanksgiving, and to magnify Thy Name, to laud the oneness of Thine Essence and to offer adoration unto Thee, inasmuch as all this lieth within Thy grasp and in that of none other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00147GRO in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00147gro/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00147gro/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Heer! Maak de snelle groei van de boom van Uw goddelijke Eenheid mogelijk; begiet hem daartoe, o Heer, met het stromend water van Uw welbehagen, en laat hem, ten overstaan van de openbaringen van Uw goddelijke bevestiging, de vruchten voortbrengen die Gij wenst voor Uw glorie en verheffing, voor Uw lof en dankzegging, en om Uw Naam te verheerlijken, om het één-zijn van Uw Essentie te vereren en om U te aanbidden, aangezien dit alles in Uw macht ligt en niet in die van iemand anders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00543VIC in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Render victorious Thy forbearing servants in Thy days by granting them a befitting victory, inasmuch as they have sought martyrdom in Thy path. Send down upon them that which will bring comfort to their minds, will rejoice their inner beings, will impart assurance to their hearts and tranquillity to their bodies and will enable their souls to ascend to the presence of God, the Most Exalted, and to attain the supreme Paradise and such retreats of glory as Thou hast destined for men of true knowledge and virtue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00543VIC in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh Señor! Haz victoriosos en Tus días a Tus sufridos siervos y concédeles un merecido triunfo, por cuanto han anhelado el martirio en Tu camino. Haz descender sobre ellos lo que alivie su mente, alegre su ser interior, dé seguridad a sus corazones y tranquilidad a sus cuerpos, y permita que sus almas asciendan a la presencia de Dios, el Exaltadísimo, y alcancen el supremo Paraíso y los retiros de gloria que Tú has destinado para las personas de virtud y verdadero conocimiento.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00543VIC in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Heer! Laat Uw verdraagzame dienaren overwinnen in Uw dagen door hun een passende zege te schenken, daar zij naar het martelaarschap op Uw pad verlangen. Zend tot hen neer hetgeen hun gemoed zal vertroosten, hun innerlijk zal verblijden, hun hart gerust zal stellen, hun lichaam tot kalmte zal brengen en hun ziel in staat zal stellen op te stijgen tot de tegenwoordigheid van God, de Verhevenste, en het allerhoogste paradijs en die glorieuze toevluchtsoorden te bereiken die Gij hebt bestemd voor de mensen met ware kennis en deugd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH05703KEP in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh05703kep/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh05703kep/en/</guid>
      <description>Suffer me not, O God, my God, to be kept back from the heaven of Thy bounties and the daystar of Thy favors. I beseech Thee by that Word through which Thou hast subdued all things visible and invisible to assist me and to assist Thy chosen ones to accomplish that which shall exalt Thy Cause amidst Thy servants and throughout Thy regions. Do Thou ordain for me, then, every good thing which Thou hast sent down in Thy Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09809 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh09809/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh09809/en/</guid>
      <description>Thou seest, O my God, how Thy loved ones have been encompassed by the rebellious amongst Thy creatures and the wicked amidst Thy people. No land remaineth but the lamentation of Thy lovers and the wailing of Thy chosen ones were lifted up therein. I beseech Thee by Thy Most Great Name to draw forth the hand of power from the bosom of Thy might and to assist therewith all them that love Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09809 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh09809/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh09809/nl/</guid>
      <description>Gij ziet, o mijn God, hoe Uw geliefden omringd zijn door de opstandigen onder Uw schepselen en de verdorvenen onder Uw volk. Er is geen land waar het weeklagen van Uw minnaars en de jammerklachten van Uw uitverkorenen niet weerklinken. Ik smeek U bij Uw Allergrootste Naam de hand van kracht uit de boezem van Uw macht tevoorschijn te halen en daarmee allen die U liefhebben bij te staan. Gij aanschouwt hen, o mijn God, met hun ogen naar U geheven, hun blik op de Dageraad van Uw macht en Uw liefdevolle voorzienigheid gericht.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH11278RIV in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh11278riv/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh11278riv/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O Lord my God! Make manifest the rivers of Thy sovereign might, that the waters of Thy Unity may flow through the inmost realities of all things, in such wise that the banner of Thine unfailing guidance may be raised aloft in the kingdom of Thy command and the stars of Thy divine splendor may shine brightly in the heaven of Thy majesty. Potent art Thou to do what pleaseth Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH11278RIV in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh11278riv/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bh11278riv/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Gloria sea a Ti, oh Señor mi Dios! Haz manifiestos los torrentes de Tu poder soberano para que las aguas de Tu Unidad fluyan a través de las realidades íntimas de todas las cosas, de tal modo que el estandarte de Tu infalible guía se alce en el reino de Tu mandato, y las estrellas de Tu divino esplendor brillen intensamente en el cielo de Tu majestad. Potente eres Tú para hacer lo que Te place.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
