<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BB00374 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bb00374/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BB00374 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bb00374/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00374 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bb00374/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bb00374/en/</guid>
      <description>Vouchsafe unto me, O my God, the full measure of Thy love and Thy good-pleasure, and through the attractions of Thy resplendent light enrapture our hearts, O Thou Who art the Supreme Evidence and the All-Glorified. Send down upon me, as a token of Thy grace, Thy vitalizing breezes, throughout the daytime and in the night season, O Lord of bounty. No deed have I done, O my God, to merit beholding Thy face, and I know of a certainty that were I to live as long as the world lasts I would fail to accomplish any deed such as to deserve this favor, inasmuch as the station of a servant shall ever fall short of access to Thy holy precincts, unless Thy bounty should reach me and Thy tender mercy pervade me and Thy loving-kindness encompass me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00374 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bb00374/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bb00374/es/</guid>
      <description>Concédeme, oh mi Dios, la plenitud de Tu amor y Tu complacencia, y, con la atracción de Tu luz resplandeciente, extasía nuestros corazones, oh Tú que eres la Evidencia Suprema y el Todoglorificado. Como señal de Tu gracia, sopla sobre mí Tus brisas vivificadoras durante el día y por la noche, oh Señor de munificencia. Ninguna acción he realizado, oh mi Dios, que me haga merecedor de contemplar Tu rostro, y sé de cierto que, aunque viviera tanto tiempo como dure el mundo, no lograría realizar acción alguna que mereciera este favor, pues la condición de un siervo jamás le permitirá acceder a Tus sagrados recintos, a no ser que Tu generosidad me alcance y Tu tierna misericordia me inunde, y Tu bondad me circunde.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
