<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Common Tablets on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-common-tablets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Common Tablets on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-common-tablets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fire Tablet  in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/bh00687/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/bh00687/en/</guid>
      <description>##Fire Tablet
In the Name of God, the Most Ancient, the Most Great.
Indeed the hearts of the sincere are consumed in the fire of separation: Where is the gleaming of the light of Thy Countenance, O Beloved of the worlds?
Those who are near unto Thee have been abandoned in the darkness of desolation: Where is the shining of the morn of Thy reunion, O Desire of the worlds?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fire Tablet  in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/bh00687/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/bh00687/nl/</guid>
      <description>In Naam van God, de Aloude, de Allergrootste. De harten van de oprechten worden voorwaar verteerd in het vuur van scheiding: waar is de glans van het licht van Uw aangezicht, o Geliefde der werelden? Degenen die U nabij zijn, zijn achtergelaten in het duister van troosteloosheid: waar is de luister van de dageraad van Uw hereniging, o Verlangen der werelden? De lichamen van Uw uitverkorenen liggen sidderend terneer op verre kusten: waar is de oceaan van Uw aanwezigheid, o Betoveraar der werelden?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tablet of Ahmad in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/bh02022/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/bh02022/en/</guid>
      <description>**Tablet of Aḥmad
*“These daily obligatory prayers, together with a few other specific ones, such as the Healing Prayer, the Tablet of Aḥmad, have been invested by Bahá’u’lláh with a special potency and significance, and should therefore be accepted as such and be recited by the believers with unquestioning faith and confidence, that through them they may enter into a much closer communion with God, and identify themselves more fully with His laws and precepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tablet of Ahmad in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/bh02022/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/bh02022/eo/</guid>
      <description>##Epistolo al Aĥmad Li estas la Reĝo, la Ĉio-scia, la Saĝa! Jen, la Najtingalo de l&amp;rsquo; Paradizo kantas sur la branĉoj de la Arbo de Eterneco, proklamante per melodioj sanktaj kaj dolĉaj al la sinceruloj la ĝojan sciigon pri la proksimeco de Dio, vokante la kredantojn je la Dia Unueco al la kortego de la Ĉeesto de la Grandanima, konigante al la purkoraj la mesaĝon revelaciitan de Dio, la Reĝo, la Glora, la Senkompara, gvidante la amantojn al la trono de sankteco kaj al tiu ĉi majesta Belo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tablet of Ahmad in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/bh02022/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/bh02022/fy/</guid>
      <description>##Tafel Fan Ahmad
&amp;ldquo;Dizze deistige ferplichte gebedens mei inkelde spesjale, lykas it Genêzingsgebed en de Tafel van Ahmad hat Bahá&amp;rsquo;u&amp;rsquo;lláh in bysûndere krêft en betsjutting jûn en dy moatte dêrom sa oannommen wurde. De leauwenden moatte dy gebedens sizze mei folslein leauwe en betrouwen, dat hja hjirtroch komme meie ta in neiere omgong mei God en harren hieltyd mear indentifisearje sille mei Syn wetten en foarskriften.&amp;rdquo;
Út in brief, dy&amp;rsquo;t skreaun is út namme fan Shogi Effendi, sjoch: Bahá&amp;rsquo;í News, septimber 1951.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tablet of the Holy Mariner in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/ab00204mar/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/ab00204mar/en/</guid>
      <description>##Tablet of the Holy Mariner *“Study the Tablet of the Holy Mariner that ye may know the truth, and consider that the Blessed Beauty hath fully foretold future events. Let them who perceive, take warning!” —‘Abdu’l-Bahá
He is the Gracious, the Well-Beloved! O Holy Mariner!
Bid thine ark of eternity appear before the Celestial Concourse,
Glorified be my Lord, the All-Glorious!
Launch it upon the ancient sea, in His Name, the Most Wondrous,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tablet of the Holy Mariner in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/ab00204mar/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/common-tablets/ab00204mar/nl/</guid>
      <description>*“Bestudeer de Tafel van de Heilige Zeevaarder, opdat u de waarheid leert kennen, en beseft dat de Gezegende Schoonheid toekomstige gebeurtenissen volledig heeft voorzegd. Laat hen die waarnemen gewaarschuwd zijn” - Abdu’l-Baha
Hij is de Genadige, de Inniggeliefde! O Heilige Zeevaarder! Gelast uw ark van eeuwigheid voor de Hemelse Schare te verschijnen, Geprezen zij mijn Heer, de Alglorierijke! laat haar te water op de aloude zee, in Zijn Naam, de Wonderbaarlijkste, Geprezen zij mijn Heer, de Alglorierijke!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
