<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH03908 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh03908/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH03908 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh03908/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03908 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/naw-r%C3%BAz/bh03908/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/naw-r%C3%BAz/bh03908/en/</guid>
      <description>##Naw-Rúz *(Naw-Rúz, March 21, is the first day of the Bahá&amp;rsquo;í year.)
Praised be Thou, O my God, that Thou hast ordained Naw-Rúz as a festival unto those who have observed the Fast for love of Thee and abstained from all that is abhorrent unto thee. Grant, O my Lord, that the fire of Thy love and the heat produced by the Fast enjoined by Thee may inflame them in Thy Cause, and make them to be occupied with Thy praise and with remembrance of Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03908 in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/naw-r%C3%BAz/bh03908/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/naw-r%C3%BAz/bh03908/fy/</guid>
      <description>##Naw-Ruz
*(Naw-Rúz, 21 maart, de earste dei fan it Bahá&amp;rsquo;í jier, is in dei fan freugde)
Priizge binne Jo, o myn God, dat Jo Naw-Rúz ynsteld hawwe as in feestdei foar harren dy&amp;rsquo;t de fêste neikommen binne út leafde foar Jo en harren ûnthâlden hawwe fan al wat Jo wearzget. Stean ta, o myn Hear, dat it fjoer fan Jo leafde en de gloede, feroarsake troch de fan Jo opleine fêste, harren foar Jo Saak ûntflamje litte mei en lit harren dwaande wêze Jo te earjen en te betinken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH03908 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/naw-r%C3%BAz/bh03908/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/naw-r%C3%BAz/bh03908/pt/</guid>
      <description>##Epístola De Naw-Rúz Louvado seja tu, ó meu Deus, por haveres ordenado o Naw-Rúz como um festival para aqueles que observaram o jejum por amor a Ti e se abstiveram de tudo o que Tu desaprovas. Permite, ó meu Senhor, que o fogo do Teu amor e o ardor causado pelo jejum por Ti prescrito, os inflamem em Tua Causa e os façam ocuparem-se com o Teu louvor e a Tua menção.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
