<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BB00522 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bb00522/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BB00522 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bb00522/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00522 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00522/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00522/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Unto Thee I repair for refuge, and toward all Thy signs I set my heart. O Lord! Whether traveling or at home, and in my occupation or in my work, I place my whole trust in Thee. Grant me then Thy sufficing help so as to make me independent of all things, O Thou Who art unsurpassed in Thy mercy! Bestow upon me my portion, O Lord, as Thou pleasest, and cause me to be satisfied with whatsoever Thou hast ordained for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00522 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00522/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00522/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh Señor! A Ti acudo en busca de amparo, y hacia todos Tus signos oriento el corazón. ¡Oh Señor! Ya sea de viaje o en mi hogar, en mis ocupaciones o en mi trabajo, en Ti deposito toda mi confianza. Concédeme, pues, Tu ayuda suficiente para hacerme independiente de todas las cosas, oh Tú a Quien nadie supera en misericordia. Otórgame mi parte, oh Señor, como sea de Tu agrado, y haz que me sienta satisfecho con lo que hayas decretado para mí.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00522 in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00522/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00522/it/</guid>
      <description>O Signore! Presso Te cerco riparo e verso tutti i Tuoi segni volgo il mio cuore. O Signore! In viaggio o in casa, nelle occupazioni o nel lavoro, ripongo ogni fiducia in Te. Concedimi dunque il Tuo bastevole aiuto sì da affrancarmi da ogni cosa, o Tu Che sei insorpassato nella Tua misericordia! Accordami la mia parte, o Signore, come Ti aggrada e fa’ ch’io sia pago di quanto hai disposto per me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
