<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH03447 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh03447/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH03447 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh03447/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Medium Obligatory Prayer in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh03447/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh03447/en/</guid>
      <description>#Medium Obligatory Prayer ##To be recited daily, in the morning, at noon, and in the evening
*Whoso wisheth to pray, let him wash his hands, and while he washeth, let him say:
Strengthen my hand, O my God, that it may take hold of Thy Book with such steadfastness that the hosts of the world shall have no power over it. Guard it, then, from meddling with whatsoever doth not belong unto it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medium Obligatory Prayer in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh03447/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh03447/eo/</guid>
      <description>##La mezlonga deviga preĝo *(Citenda kaj matene, kaj tagmeze kaj vespere. “Matene”, “tagmeze” kaj “vespere”, menciitaj je la Devigaj Preĝoj, signifas respektive la intervalojn inter sunleviĝo kaj tagmezo, inter tagmezo kaj sunsubiro, kaj de sunsubiro ĝis du horojn poste.)
*Kiu deziras preĝi, tiu lavu siajn manojn, kaj dum la lavado li diru: Fortigu mian manon, ho Dio, ke firme ĝi tenu Vian Libron per tia fideleco, ke la mondularo havu nenian potencon super ĝi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medium Obligatory Prayer in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh03447/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh03447/nl/</guid>
      <description>*Dagelijks te reciteren, ’s ochtends, ‘s middags en ’s avonds.
*Laat al wie wenst te bidden, zijn handen wassen en onder het wassen zeggen:
Sterk mijn hand, o mijn God, dat zij Uw Boek zo onwrikbaar mag vasthouden dat de wereldse scharen er geen macht over zullen hebben. Behoed haar dan voor bemoeienis met al hetgeen haar niet toebehoort. Gij zijt waarlijk de Almachtige, de Almogende.
*Laat hij terwijl hij zijn gezicht wast, zeggen:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medium Obligatory Prayer in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh03447/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh03447/pt/</guid>
      <description>#A SER RECITADA DIARIAMENTE, PELA MANHÃ, AO MEIO-DIA E AO ANOITECER *Aquele que deseja rezar deverá lavar as mãos e, ao lavá-las, dizer:Fortalece a minha mão, ó meu Deus, para que possa segurar o Teu Livro com tal firmeza que as hostes do mundo não tenham sobre ela poder algum. Guarda-a, pois, de tocar o que não lhe pertence. Tu és, em verdade, o Omnipotente, o Mais Poderoso. *E enquanto lavar o rosto, diga: Volvi a face para Ti, ó meu Senhor!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
