<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB02024 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab02024/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB02024 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab02024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02024 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/martyrs-and-their-families/ab02024/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/martyrs-and-their-families/ab02024/en/</guid>
      <description>He is God! O Lord my God! O Thou Helper of the feeble, Succorer of the poor and Deliverer of the helpless who turn unto Thee. With utmost lowliness I raise my suppliant hands to Thy kingdom of beauty and fervently call upon Thee with my inner tongue, saying: O God, my God! Aid me to adore Thee, strengthen my loins to serve Thee; assist me by Thy grace in my servitude to Thee; suffer me to remain steadfast in my obedience to Thee; pour forth upon me the liberal effusions of Thy bounty, let the glances of the eye of Thy loving-kindness be directed towards me, and immerse me in the ocean of Thy forgiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02024 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/martyrs-and-their-families/ab02024/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/martyrs-and-their-families/ab02024/nl/</guid>
      <description>Hij is God! O Heer mijn God! O Gij Helper van de zwakken, Steun van de armen en Verlosser van de hulpelozen die zich tot U keren. In uiterste deemoed hef ik mijn smekende handen tot Uw koninkrijk van schoonheid en roep ik U innerlijk vurig aan, zeggende: o God, mijn God! Help mij U te aanbidden, sterk mijn lendenen om U te dienen, sta mij met Uw genade bij in mijn dienstbaarheid aan U, vergun mij standvastig te blijven in mijn gehoorzaamheid aan U, stort de overvloedige stromen van Uw milddadigheid over mij uit, laat de blik van het oog van Uw goedertierenheid op mij rusten en dompel mij in de oceaan van Uw vergeving.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
