<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-ABU0137ALL on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-abu0137all/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-ABU0137ALL on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-abu0137all/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0137ALL in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/humanity/abu0137all/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/humanity/abu0137all/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! Thou hast created all humanity from the same stock. Thou hast decreed that all shall belong to the same household. In Thy Holy Presence they are all Thy servants, and all mankind are sheltered beneath Thy Tabernacle; all have gathered together at Thy Table of Bounty; all are illumined through the light of Thy Providence.
O God! Thou art kind to all, Thou hast provided for all, dost shelter all, conferrest life upon all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0137ALL in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/humanity/abu0137all/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/humanity/abu0137all/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Vi bonkora Sinjoro! Vi kreis la tutan homaron el la sama radiko. Vi decidis, ke ĉiuj apartenu al la sama familio. En Via Sankta Ĉeesto ili ĉiuj estas Viaj servantoj, kaj la tuta homaro trovas protekton en Via Sanktejo. Ĉiuj kolektiĝis ĉirkaŭ Via Festena Tablo. Ĉiuj estas lumigataj de la lumo de Via Providenco. Ho Dio! Vi estas bonkora al ĉiuj. Vi zorgas pri ĉiuj, protektas ĉiujn, donas vivon al ĉiuj.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0137ALL in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/humanity/abu0137all/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/humanity/abu0137all/fy/</guid>
      <description>O Jo, leafderyk Hear! Jo hawwe it hiele minskdom út deselde stam skepen. Jo hawwe foarbeskikt dat wy allegearre ta deselde famylje hearre. Foar Jo hillich Antlit binne allegearre Jo tsjinners en it hiele minskdom wurdt fan Jo Tabernakel beskerme. Wy allegearre binne gearkommen om Jo Tafel fan Oerfloed en wurde ferljochte troch it ljocht fan Jo foarsjennichheid. O God! Jo binne freonlik foar ús allegearre, Jo soargje foar ús allegearre, Jo beskermje ús allegearre, Jo skinke libben oan ús allegearre.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
