<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH10973 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh10973/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH10973 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh10973/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10973 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh10973/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh10973/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou Whose face is the object of my adoration, Whose beauty is my sanctuary, Whose habitation is my goal, Whose praise is my hope, Whose providence is my companion, Whose love is the cause of my being, Whose mention is my solace, Whose nearness is my desire, Whose presence is my dearest wish and highest aspiration, I entreat Thee not to withhold from me the things Thou didst ordain for the chosen ones among Thy servants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10973 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh10973/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh10973/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Vi, Kies vizaĝo estas la objekto de mia adoro, Kies beleco estas mia sanktejo, Kies restadejo estas mia celo, Kies laŭdo estas mia espero, Kies providenco estas mia akompananto, Kies amo estas la kaŭzo de mia estado, Kies mencio estas mia konsolo, Kies proksimeco estas mia deziro, Kies ĉeesto estas mia plej kara strebo kaj plej alta aspiro, mi petegas Vin ne deteni de mi, kion Vi ordonis por la elektitoj el inter Viaj sekvantoj.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10973 in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh10973/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh10973/fy/</guid>
      <description>O Jo, waans antlit it doel is fan myn oanbidding, Waans skientme myn hillichdom, Waans wente myn doel, Waans lofspraak myn hope, Waans foarsjennichheid myn selskipsman, Waans leafde de reden fan myn bestean, Waans neamd-wurden myn treast, Waans neite myn langstme, Waans tsjinwurdichheid myn dierberste winsk en heechste stribjen is. Ik smeekje Jo my net te ûnthâlden wat Jo foar de útkarden fan Jo tsjinners ornearre hawwe. Ferlien my dan it goede fan dizze wrâld en fan de neikommende.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10973 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh10973/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/aid-and-assistance/bh10973/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij, Wiens gelaat het voorwerp is van mijn aanbidding, Wiens schoonheid mijn heiligdom, Wiens woning mijn doel, Wiens lof mijn hoop, Wiens voorzienigheid mijn metgezel, Wiens liefde de reden van mijn bestaan, Wiens noemen mijn troost, Wiens nabijheid mijn verlangen, Wiens tegenwoordigheid mijn dierbaarste wens en hoogste streven is, ik smeek U mij niet te onthouden hetgeen Gij voor de uitverkorenen onder Uw dienaren hebt bestemd. Verleen mij dan het goede van deze wereld en van de volgende.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
