<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Families on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-families/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Families on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-families/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02000DIS in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab02000dis/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab02000dis/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! In this Most Great Dispensation Thou dost accept the intercession of children in behalf of their parents. This is one of the special infinite bestowals of this Dispensation. Therefore, O Thou kind Lord, accept the request of this Thy servant at the threshold of Thy singleness and submerge his father in the ocean of Thy grace, because this son hath arisen to render Thee service and is exerting effort at all times in the pathway of Thy love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02000DIS in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab02000dis/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab02000dis/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Eternulo! En tiu ĉi Plej Granda Misio Vi akceptas la propeton de infanoj por siaj gepatroj. Tio estas unu el la apartaj senlimaj donacoj de tiu ĉi Misio. Tial, ho Vi bona Sinjoro, akceptu la peton de tiu ĉi servanto Via ĉe la sojlo de Via ununureco kaj mergu lian patron en la oceanon de Via graco, ĉar ĉi tiu filo leviĝis por plenurni al Vi servojn kaj ĉiutempe penadas sur la vojo de Via amo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02000DIS in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab02000dis/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab02000dis/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Heer! Gij aanvaardt in deze Allergrootste Beschikking de voorspraak van kinderen in naam van hun ouders. Dit is één van de speciale, oneindige gunsten van deze Beschikking. O Gij vriendelijk Heer, aanvaard daarom het verzoek van deze dienaar van U aan de drempel van Uw enig-zijn en dompel zijn vader in de oceaan van Uw genade, want zijn zoon is opgestaan om U te dienen en spant zich te allen tijde in op het pad van Uw liefde.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB03017CAL in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab03017cal/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/ab03017cal/en/</guid>
      <description>#Husbands
O God, my God! This Thy handmaid is calling upon Thee, trusting in Thee, turning her face unto Thee, imploring Thee to shed thy heavenly bounties upon her, and to disclose unto her Thy spiritual mysteries, and to cast upon her the lights of Thy Godhead. O my Lord! Make the eyes of my husband to see. Rejoice Thou his heart with the light of the knowledge of Thee, draw Thou his mind unto Thy luminous beauty, cheer Thou his spirit by revealing unto him Thy manifest splendors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00018FOR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/en/</guid>
      <description>#Parents
I beg Thy forgiveness, O my God, and implore pardon after the manner Thou wishest Thy servants to direct themselves to Thee. I beg of Thee to wash away our sins as befitteth Thy Lordship, and to forgive me, my parents, and those who in Thy estimation have entered the abode of Thy love in a manner which is worthy of Thy transcendent sovereignty and well beseemeth the glory of Thy celestial power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00018FOR in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/fr/</guid>
      <description>Ô mon Dieu, je sollicite ta clémence et j’implore ton pardon ainsi que tu souhaites entendre tes serviteurs s’adresser à toi. Lave-nous de nos péchés, je t’en supplie, comme il sied à ton empire et accorde-moi ton pardon, ainsi qu’à mes parents et à ceux qui, à tes yeux, se sont réfugiés en ton amour, comme il convient à ta souveraineté transcendante et à la gloire de ton pouvoir céleste. Ô mon Dieu, tu as inspiré mon âme pour qu’elle t’adresse cette supplique, et sans toi, je ne pourrai faire appel à toi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00018FOR in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00018for/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik smeek om Uw vergeving, o mijn God, en bid om vergiffenis zoals Gij wenst dat Uw dienaren zich tot U wenden. Ik smeek U onze zonden weg te nemen zoals het U, Heer, past en vergeving te schenken aan mij, mijn ouders, en degenen die naar Uw oordeel de verblijfplaats van Uw liefde hebben betreden op een wijze die Uw alles te boven gaande soevereiniteit waardig is en de heerlijkheid van Uw hemelse macht betaamt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00583 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00583/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00583/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be unto Thee, O Lord my God! I beg Thee to forgive me and those who support Thy Faith. Verily, Thou art the sovereign Lord, the Forgiver, the Most Generous. O my God! Enable such servants of Thine as are deprived of knowledge to be admitted into Thy Cause; for once they learn of Thee, they bear witness to the truth of the Day of Judgment and do not dispute the revelations of Thy bounty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00583 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00583/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/families/bb00583/pt/</guid>
      <description>Glória a Ti, ó Senhor meu Deus! Peço-Te que me perdoes e àqueles que apoiam a Tua Fé. Em verdade Tu és o Senhor soberano, o Clemente, o Mais Generoso. Ó meu Deus! Permite que sejam admitidos à Tua Causa os servos Teus que estão privados de conhecimentos, pois, uma vez sabendo de Ti, eles dão testemunho da verdade do Dia do Juízo e não disputam as revelações da Tua generosidade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
