<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Blackfoot / Siksika on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-blackfoot-/-siksika/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Blackfoot / Siksika on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-blackfoot-/-siksika/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn4148 in Canadian Indigenous</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-ca/bpn4148/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-ca/bpn4148/</guid>
      <description>Apistotokeewa keeták-oXkotspómok-owa, kútat-sits-eéh’pa keeták-oXkot-spomókee? Ah-yoh Apistotokee! UnúX-kiy Apistotokee! Kunáy-tapee otés-pomok ki óXkunoX-pokee-woh-yah.
*Is there any Remover of difficulties save God? Say: Praised be God! He is God! All are His servants, and all abide by His bidding!.
(Source category: Blackfoot / Siksika) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 4148)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn4149 in Canadian Indigenous</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-ca/bpn4149/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-ca/bpn4149/</guid>
      <description>Atsée-moyeh’kapee un-óm, ki kokónahn, keetáw-pop, ki akápeeyoyis, kyoos-kee-tsée-paXpee, ki mee-stúkee, keetáyk-sasohp, ki ata-níksin, ki ist-sikúm, ki isksáXko, ki mo-tíy-oXkee, ki mée-nee, ki ápoX-keepee kyám-ost-skiy; Apistotokee eeh-tsee-tésk-sinowa kyot-sokáp-sinee áXkeetso-keetseesinee.
*Blessed is the spot, and the house, and the place, and the city, and the heart, and the mountain, and the refuge, and the cave, and the valley, and the land, and the sea, and the island, and the meadow where mention of God hath been made, and His praise glorified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn4150 in Canadian Indigenous</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-ca/bpn4150/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-ca/bpn4150/</guid>
      <description>Kitsíneh’ka-seemee tóXta-sókimoX-see, áh-yoh Apistotokee, ki ikúmoks-tay-ksím-stay-neekee tákoXt-seets. Keetóta-powáX-kaX-see noXtóh-tamee-túkee ki eh’tóX-pokow-op keeta-wákomin-oX-sinee. Kitsee-kím-oX-sinee nitoX- táh-sokaps ki nitóX-tah-spom-ókoh unoyee isk-sáX-koy ki iy-yá-keeta-popay-nyókee. Gee-stóa keetsee-kím-apee, keetóX-kunes-ksineéh’p éehpóX-sinee kitsee-kók-akee.
*Thy name is my healing, O my God, and remembrance of Thee is my remedy. Nearness to Thee is my hope, and love for Thee is my companion. Thy mercy to me is my healing and my succour in both this world and the world to come.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
