<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Detachment on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-detachment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Detachment on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-detachment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00553 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/ab00553/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/ab00553/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! Fill up for me the cup of detachment from all things, and in the assembly of Thy splendors and bestowals, rejoice me with the wine of loving Thee. Free me from the assaults of passion and desire, break off from me the shackles of this nether world, draw me with rapture unto Thy supernal realm, and refresh me amongst the handmaids with the breathing of Thy holiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB04980HOP in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ab04980hop/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ab04980hop/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! Thou art my Hope and my Beloved, my highest Aim and Desire! With great humbleness and entire devotion I pray to Thee to make me a minaret of Thy love in Thy land, a lamp of Thy knowledge among Thy creatures, and a banner of divine bounty in Thy dominion. Number me with such of Thy servants as have detached themselves from everything but Thee, have sanctified themselves from the transitory things of this world, and have freed themselves from the promptings of the voicers of idle fancies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00015SUF in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00015suf/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00015suf/en/</guid>
      <description>Say: God sufficeth all things above all things, and nothing in the heavens or in the earth but God sufficeth. Verily, He is in Himself the Knower, the Sustainer, the Omnipotent.
(Source category: Detachment) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 219)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00015SUF in Papiamentu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00015suf/pap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00015suf/pap/</guid>
      <description>*Say: God sufficeth all things above all things…
Bisá: Dios ta sufisiente riba tur kos i nada den shelunan o riba tera ta sufisiente sino Dios. En berdat, E ta den Su mes e konosedor, e sostenedor, e omnipotente.
(Source category: Detachment) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 6868)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00522 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00522/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00522/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Unto Thee I repair for refuge, and toward all Thy signs I set my heart. O Lord! Whether traveling or at home, and in my occupation or in my work, I place my whole trust in Thee. Grant me then Thy sufficing help so as to make me independent of all things, O Thou Who art unsurpassed in Thy mercy! Bestow upon me my portion, O Lord, as Thou pleasest, and cause me to be satisfied with whatsoever Thou hast ordained for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00560 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00560/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bb00560/en/</guid>
      <description>In the Name of Thy Lord, the Creator, the Sovereign, the All-Sufficing, the Most Exalted, He Whose help is implored by all men.
Say: O my God! O Thou Who art the Maker of the heavens and of the earth, O Lord of the Kingdom! Thou well knowest the secrets of my heart, while Thy being is inscrutable to all save Thyself. Thou seest whatsoever is of me, while no one else can do this save Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH05771 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh05771/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh05771/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise be unto Thee, O my God! I am one of Thy servants, who hath believed on Thee and on Thy signs. Thou seest how I have set myself towards the door of Thy mercy, and turned my face in the direction of Thy loving-kindness. I beseech Thee, by Thy most excellent titles and Thy most exalted attributes, to open to my face the portals of Thy bestowals. Aid me, then, to do that which is good, O Thou Who art the Posessor of all names and attributes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH05894 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh05894/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh05894/en/</guid>
      <description>I know not, O my God, what the Fire is which Thou didst kindle in Thy land. Earth can never cloud its splendor, nor water quench its flame. All the peoples of the world are powerless to resist its force. Great is the blessedness of him that hath drawn nigh unto it, and heard its roaring. Some, O my God, Thou didst, through Thy strengthening grace, enable to approach it, while others Thou didst keep back by reason of what their hands have wrought in Thy days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09024 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09024/en/</guid>
      <description>Many a chilled heart, O my God, hath been set ablaze by the fire of Thy Cause, and many a slumberer hath been wakened by the sweetness of Thy voice. How many are the strangers who have sought shelter beneath the shadow of the tree of Thy oneness, and how numerous the thirsty ones who have panted after the fountain of Thy living waters in Thy days! Blessed is he that hath set himself towards Thee, and hasted to attain the Dayspring of the lights of Thy face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09289 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09289/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09289/en/</guid>
      <description>Suffer me, O my God, to draw nigh unto Thee, and to abide within the precincts of Thy court, for remoteness from Thee hath well-nigh consumed me. Cause me to rest under the shadow of the wings of Thy grace, for the flame of my separation from Thee hath melted my heart within me. Draw me nearer unto the river that is life indeed, for my soul burneth with thirst in its ceaseless search after Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09508 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09508/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09508/en/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O my God! I yield Thee thanks that Thou hast made known unto me Him who is the Dayspring of Thy mercy, and the Dawning-Place of Thy grace, and the Repository of Thy Cause. I beseech Thee by Thy Name, through which the faces of them that are nigh unto Thee have turned white, and the hearts of such as are devoted to Thee have winged their flight towards Thee, to grant that I may, at all times and under all conditions, lay hold on Thy cord, and be rid of all attachment to anyone except Thee, and may keep mine eyes directed towards the horizon of Thy Revelation, and may carry out what Thou hast prescribed unto me in Thy Tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09864 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09864/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/detachment/bh09864/en/</guid>
      <description>Lauded be Thy name, O my God! I entreat Thee by the fragrances of the Raiment of Thy grace which at Thy bidding and in conformity with Thy desire were diffused throughout the entire creation, and by the Daystar of Thy will that hath shone brightly, through the power of Thy might and of Thy sovereignty, above the horizon of Thy mercy, to blot out from my heart all idle fancies and vain imaginings, that with all my affections I may turn unto Thee, O Thou Lord of all mankind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12374 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12374/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12374/</guid>
      <description>Suffer me, O my God, to draw nigh unto Thee,….
 Lo’u Atua e, faapologaina a’u ia avatua faalatalata ia te Oe, ma ia nofo mau ai i totonu o lotoa o Lou maota, aua o le taumamao ma Oe ua latalata mai ai le faaumatia o a’u. Faia ia ou malolo i lalo ifo o le paolo o apaau o Lou alofa tunoa, ona o le mamao o lo’u vavaeesea mai ia te Oe, ua liu suavai ai lo’u loto i totonu ia te a’u.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12375 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12375/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12375/</guid>
      <description>Many a chilled heart, Om my God, hath been set ablaze with the fire……
 Lo’u Atua e, e tele ni loto maalilili ua faamumuina e le afi o Lau Fuataiga, ma e to’atele tagata moegagase ua fafaguina e le leomalie o Lou Si’ufofoga. E fia tagata ese ua saili lafitaga atu i lalo o le paolo o le laau o Lou tafatasi, ma e matua manomano tagata galala sa tofao atu i le puna o Au vai ola i Ou aso!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6343 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6343/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6343/</guid>
      <description>Say: O God, my God! Thou beholdest me circling round Thy Will with mine eyes turned towards the horizon of Thy bounty, eagerly awaiting the revelation of the effulgent splendours of the sun of Thy favours. I beg of Thee, O Beloved of every understanding heart and the Desire of such as have near access unto Thee, to grant that Thy loved ones may become wholly detached from their own inclinations, holding fast unto that which pleaseth Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
