<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB00001FIR on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00001fir/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB00001FIR on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00001fir/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001FIR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord my God! Assist Thy loved ones to be firm in Thy Faith, to walk in Thy ways, to be steadfast in Thy Cause. Give them Thy grace to withstand the onslaught of self and passion, to follow the light of divine guidance. Thou art the Powerful, the Gracious, the Self-Subsisting, the Bestower, the Compassionate, the Almighty, the All-Bountiful.
(Source category: Steadfastness) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 319)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001FIR in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Eternulo, mia Dio! Asistu Viajn amatojn, por ke ili estu firmaj en Via Kredo, iru Viajn vojojn kaj estu persistemaj en Via Afero. Donu al ili Vian gracon por kontraŭstari la atakojn de egoismo kaj pasio kaj por sekvi la lumon de la ĉiela gvidado. Vi estas la Potenca, la Graca, la Mem-Ekzistanta, la Donacanto, la Kompatema, la Ĉio-pova, la Plej Malavara.
(Source category: Firmeco en la Interligo) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 4333)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001FIR in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/it/</guid>
      <description>O Signore mio Dio! Assisti i Tuoi amati ad essere saldi nella Tua Fede, a camminare sulle Tue vie, ad essere costanti nella Tua Causa. Da’ loro la Tua grazia onde sopportino i furiosi assalti dell’egoismo e della passione, e seguano la luce della guida divina. Tu sei il Potente, il Benevolo, Colui Che Esiste da Sé, il Donatore, il Compassionevole, l’Onnipotente, il Generosissimo.
(Source category: Saldezza) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 7913)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001FIR in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Heer, mijn God! Help Uw geliefden sterk te staan in Uw Geloof, Uw wegen te bewandelen en standvastig te zijn in Uw Zaak. Geef hun Uw genade om de aanvallen van zelfzucht en hartstocht te weerstaan en het licht van goddelijke leiding te volgen. Gij zijt de Krachtige, de Genadige, de Bij-zich-bestaande, de Schenker, de Meedogende, de Almachtige, de Almilddadige.
(Source category: Standvastigheid) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9713)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001FIR in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Senhor, meu Deus! Ajuda aqueles que Te amam a permanecerem firmes na Tua Fé, a prosseguirem nos Teus caminhos e serem constantes na Tua Causa. Dispensa-lhes a Tua graça, para que resistam às investidas do ego e da paixão e se guiem pela luz da guia divina. Tu és o Poderoso, o Benévolo, O que subsiste por Si próprio, o Magnânimo, o Compassivo, o Omnipotente, a Suprema Bondade.
(Source category: Firmeza e Constância) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
