<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Sacrifice on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-sacrifice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Sacrifice on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-sacrifice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6305 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6305/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6305/</guid>
      <description>O Divine Providence! Lift to Thy lovers&amp;rsquo; lips a cup brimful of anguish. To the yearners on Thy pathway, make sweetness but a sting, and poison honey-sweet. Set Thou our heads for ornaments on the points of spears. Make Thou our hearts the targets for pitiless arrows and darts. Raise Thou this withered soul to life on the martyr&amp;rsquo;s field, make Thou his faded heart to drink the draft of tyranny, and thus grow fresh and fair once more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6835 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6835/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6835/</guid>
      <description>Magnified be Thy name, O God, the Lord of heaven! Attire my head with the crown of martyrdom, even as Thou didst attire my body with the ornament of tribulation before all that dwell in Thy land. Grant, moreover, that they whose hearts yearn over Thee may draw nigh unto the horizon of Thy grace, above which the Day-Star of Thy beauty sheddeth its radiance. Ordain, also, for them what will make them rich enough to dispense with aught else except Thee, and rid them of all attachment to such as have repudiated Thy signs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6836 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6836/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6836/</guid>
      <description>Praise be to Thee, O Lord my God! I am the one who hath sought the good pleasure of Thy will, and directed his steps towards the seat of Thy gracious favors. I am he who hath forsaken his all, who hath fled to Thee for shelter, who hath set his face towards the tabernacle of Thy revelation and the adored sanctuary of Thy glory. I beseech Thee, O my Lord, by Thy call whereby they who recognized Thy unity have sought the shadow of Thy most gracious providence, and the sincere have fled far from themselves unto Thy name, the Most Exalted, the All-Glorious, through which Thy verses were sent down, and Thy word fulfilled, and Thy proof manifested, and the sun of Thy beauty risen, and Thy testimony established, and Thy signs uncovered,—I beseech Thee to grant that I may be numbered with them that have quaffed the wine that is life indeed from the hands of Thy gracious providence, and have rid themselves, in Thy path, of all attachment to Thy creatures, and been so inebriated with Thy manifold wisdom that they hastened to the field of sacrifice with Thy praise on their lips and Thy remembrance in their hearts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6837 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6837/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6837/</guid>
      <description>How numerous the souls raised to life who were exposed to dire humiliation in Thy Path for exalting Thy Word and for glorifying Thy divine Unity! How profuse the blood that hath been shed for the sake of Thy Faith to vindicate the authenticity of Thy divine Mission and to celebrate Thy praise! How vast the possessions that were wrongfully seized in the Path of Thy love in order to affirm the loftiness of Thy sanctity and to extol Thy glorious Name!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6838 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6838/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6838/</guid>
      <description>Glory be unto Thee, O Lord! Although Thou mayest cause a person to be destitute of all earthly possessions, and from the beginning of his life until his ascension unto Thee he may be reduced to poverty through the operation of Thy decree, yet wert Thou to have brought him forth from the Tree of Thy love, such a bounty would indeed be far better for him than all the things Thou hast created in heaven and earth and whatsoever lieth between them; inasmuch as he will inherit the heavenly home, through the revelation of Thy favours, and will partake of the goodly gifts Thou hast provided therein; for the things which are with Thee are inexhaustible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6839 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6839/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6839/</guid>
      <description>Glorified be Thou, O my God! Behold Thou my head ready to fall before the sword of Thy Will, my neck prepared to bear the chains of Thy Desire, my heart yearning to be made a target for the darts of Thy Decree, mine eyes expectant to gaze on the tokens and signs of Thy wondrous Mercy. For whatsoever may befall me from Thee is the cherished desire of them who thirst to meet Thee, and the supreme aspiration of such as have drawn nigh unto Thy court.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
