<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Short Obligatory Prayer on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-short-obligatory-prayer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Short Obligatory Prayer on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-short-obligatory-prayer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12476 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12476/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12476/</guid>
      <description>##SHORT OBLIGATORY PRAYER
*TO BE RECITED ONCE IN TWENTY-FOUR HOURS, AT NOON
TATALO PU’UPU’U FA’APOLOA’IGA E TASI LE FAIGA I LE LUASEFULU-FA ITULA, I LE AOAULI.
Lo’u Atua e, ou te molimau atu, na faia e Lau Afio a’u ina ia iloa Oe ma tapua’i atu ia te Oe. Ou te tautino atu i lenei itula, lo’u augavale ma Lou malosi, o lo’u mativa i le ma Lou tamaoaiga.
E leai lava se tasi Atua na o Oe, o le Fesoasoani i Puapugā, o le Puna– o– le–Ola.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12930 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12930/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12930/</guid>
      <description>##SOTPELA PREA BILONG KOLIM LONG OLGETA WAN WAN DE
Wan wan Baha&amp;rsquo;i i mas kolim dispela prea wanpela taim long olgeta wan wan de namel long taim bilong belo i go inap long taim san i go daun. Pastaim em i mas wasim han na pes bilong en, na bihain em i mas sanap na tanim pes bilong en i go long Ples Matmat bilong Baha&amp;rsquo;u&amp;rsquo;llah long Ples Tambu (Israel). Olsem na long PNG man i mas sanap na tanim pes bilong en i go long ples we san i go daun na tanim long hansut liklik na kolim dispela prea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13321 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13321/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13321/</guid>
      <description>*(I&amp;rsquo;w hadrodd unwaith bob dydd rhwng hanner dydd a machlud haul)
Tystiaf, O fy Nuw, i Ti fy nghreu i i&amp;rsquo;th adnabod Di ac i&amp;rsquo;th addoli Di. Tystiaf, ar y funud hon, i&amp;rsquo;m diymadferthedd ac i&amp;rsquo;th allu Di, i&amp;rsquo;m tlodi ac i&amp;rsquo;th gyfoeth Di. Nid oes Duw arall ond Ti, y Cymorth mewn Perygl, yr Hunangynhaliol.
*(to be recited once a day between midday and sunset)
I bear witness, O my God, that Thou hast created me to know Thee and to worship Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9110 in ភាសាខ្មែរ</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/km/bpn9110/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/km/bpn9110/</guid>
      <description>*ធម’អធិដ្ឋានប្រចាំថ្ងៃ
¬សូត្រមួយថ្ងៃម្ដងចន្លេាះពេលថ្ងៃត្រង់ និងពេលល្ងាច¦ បពិត្រព្រះជាម្ចាស់¡ ទូលបង្គំសូមធ្វេីជាសក្ខីភាពថា ព្រះអង្គបានបង្កេីតទូលព្រះបង្គំមក ដេីម្បីអេាយទូលព្រះបង្គំ បានស្គាល់និងបូជាសក្ការៈចំពេាះព្រះអង្គ ។ ក្នុងខណៈនេះទូលព្រះបង្គំបានជ្រាបហេីយនូវភាពទន់ខ្សេាយរបស់ទូល ព្រះបង្គំ ទៅនឹងបារមីដ៏បវររបស់ព្រះអង្គ និងភាពទន់ខ្សេាយរបស់ទូលព្រះបង្គំ ទៅនឹងទ្រព្យសម្បត្ដិដ៏ធំធេង របស់ព្រអង្គ ។ ពុំមានព្រះជាម្ចាស់ដទៃណាទៀតឡេីយក្រេៅពីព្រះអង្គ ព្រះអង្គទ្រង់ជួយរំដេាះទុក្ខភ័យនៃសត្វលេាក ព្រះអង្គគង់នៅជានិច្ចដេាយបារមីនៃព្រះអង្គឯង ។
(Source category: Short Obligatory Prayer) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9110)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short Obligatory Prayer in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh11209/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh11209/en/</guid>
      <description>#Short obligatory prayer ##To be recited once in twenty-four hours, at noon
I bear witness, O my God, that Thou hast created me to know Thee and to worship Thee. I testify, at this moment, to my powerlessness and to Thy might, to my poverty and to Thy wealth. There is none other God but Thee, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting.
 &amp;ldquo;The daily obligatory prayers are three in number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short Obligatory Prayer in Papiamentu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh11209/pap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/obligatory-prayers/bh11209/pap/</guid>
      <description>##Short Obligatory Prayer
Mi ta duna testimonio, o mi Dios, ku Bo a kriami pa mi konosé Bo i adorá Bo. Mi ta testigo na e momento aki di mi flakesa i di Bo poder, di mi pobresa i di Bo rikesa. No tin ningun otro Dios sino Bo, e auxilio den peliger, esun ku ta subsistí di Su mes.
(Source category: Short Obligatory Prayer) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 6865)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
