<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Nearness to God on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-nearness-to-god/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Nearness to God on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-nearness-to-god/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02866 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab02866/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab02866/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord, my God and my Haven in my distress! My Shield and my Shelter in my woes! My Asylum and Refuge in time of need and in my loneliness my Companion! In my anguish my Solace, and in my solitude a loving Friend! The Remover of the pangs of my sorrows and the Pardoner of my sins! Wholly unto Thee do I turn, fervently imploring Thee with all my heart, my mind and my tongue, to shield me from all that runs counter to Thy will in this, the cycle of Thy divine unity, and to cleanse me of all defilement that will hinder me from seeking, stainless and unsullied, the shade of the tree of Thy grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02866 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab02866/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab02866/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Eternulo, mia Dio kaj mia Haveno en mia aflikto! Mia Ŝildo kaj mia Ŝirmo en miaj turmentoj! Mia Azilo kaj mia Rifuĝejo en horo de bezono, kaj en mia izoleco mia Kunulo! En mia angoro mia Konsolo, kaj en mia soleco amema Amiko! La Foriganto de la doloregoj de miaj ĉagrenoj, kaj la Pardonanto de miaj pekoj! Nur al Vi mi turnas min, fervore petegante Vin per mia tuta koro, mia menso kaj mia lango, ke Vi protektu min de ĉio, kio kontraŭas Vian volon en ĉi tiu ciklo de Via dia unueco, kaj ke Vi purigu min de ĉiu malpuro, kiu malebligas al mi celadi senmakula kaj pura al la ombro de la arbo de Via graco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB06012 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab06012/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab06012/en/</guid>
      <description>He is the Compassionate, the All-Bountiful! O God, my God! Thou seest me, Thou knowest me; Thou art my Haven and my Refuge. None have I sought nor any will I seek save Thee; no path have I trodden nor any will I tread but the path of Thy love. In the darksome night of despair, my eye turneth expectant and full of hope to the morn of Thy boundless favor and at the hour of dawn my drooping soul is refreshed and strengthened in remembrance of Thy beauty and perfection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB06012 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab06012/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab06012/eo/</guid>
      <description>Li estas la Kompatema, la Ĉion-Donacanta! Ho Dio, mia Dio! Vi vidas min, Vi konas min; Vi estas mia Haveno kaj mia Rifuĝejo. Neniun mi serĉis nek celos krom Vi; neniun vojon mi paŝis nek paŝos krom tiun de Via amo. En la senluma nokto de malespero mia okulo turnas sin atendema kaj esperplena al la tagiĝo de Via senlima korfavoro, kaj en la tagiĝa horo mia velkanta animo refresiĝas kaj fortikiĝas je rememoro pri Viaj beleco kaj perfekteco.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB06012 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab06012/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab06012/nl/</guid>
      <description>Hij is de Meedogende, de Almilddadige! O God, mijn God! Gij ziet mij, Gij kent mij; Gij zijt mijn schuilplaats en mijn toevlucht. Niemand heb ik gezocht noch zal ik zoeken buiten U; geen pad heb ik begaan noch zal ik begaan dan het pad van Uw liefde. In de duistere nacht van wanhoop richt ik mijn blik vol verwachting en hoop op de morgen van Uw grenzeloze gunst, en bij het aanbreken van de dag wordt mijn kwijnende ziel verkwikt en gesterkt door het gedenken van Uw schoonheid en volmaaktheid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00018ANG in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bb00018ang/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bb00018ang/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! There is no one but Thee to allay the anguish of my soul, and Thou art my highest aspiration, O my God. My heart is wedded to none save Thee and such as Thou dost love. I solemnly declare that my life and death are both for Thee. Verily Thou art incomparable and hast no partner. O my Lord! I beg Thee to forgive me for shutting myself out from Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00556 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bb00556/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bb00556/en/</guid>
      <description>Verily I am Thy servant, O my God, and Thy poor one and Thy suppliant and Thy wretched creature. I have arrived at Thy gate, seeking Thy shelter. I have found no contentment save in Thy love, no exultation except in Thy remembrance, no eagerness but in obedience to Thee, no joy save in Thy nearness, and no tranquillity except in reunion with Thee, notwithstanding that I am conscious that all created things are debarred from Thy sublime Essence and the entire creation is denied access to Thine inmost Being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08264 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bh08264/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bh08264/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O my God! Thou hearest Thine ardent lovers lamenting in their separation from Thee, and such as have recognized Thee wailing because of their remoteness from Thy presence. Open Thou outwardly to their faces, O my Lord, the gates of Thy grace, that they may enter them by Thy leave and in conformity with Thy will, and may stand before the throne of Thy majesty, and catch the accents of Thy voice, and be illumined with the splendors of the light of Thy face.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
