<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BB00543VIC on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bb00543vic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BB00543VIC on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bb00543vic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00543VIC in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord! Render victorious Thy forbearing servants in Thy days by granting them a befitting victory, inasmuch as they have sought martyrdom in Thy path. Send down upon them that which will bring comfort to their minds, will rejoice their inner beings, will impart assurance to their hearts and tranquillity to their bodies and will enable their souls to ascend to the presence of God, the Most Exalted, and to attain the supreme Paradise and such retreats of glory as Thou hast destined for men of true knowledge and virtue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00543VIC in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh Señor! Haz victoriosos en Tus días a Tus sufridos siervos y concédeles un merecido triunfo, por cuanto han anhelado el martirio en Tu camino. Haz descender sobre ellos lo que alivie su mente, alegre su ser interior, dé seguridad a sus corazones y tranquilidad a sus cuerpos, y permita que sus almas asciendan a la presencia de Dios, el Exaltadísimo, y alcancen el supremo Paraíso y los retiros de gloria que Tú has destinado para las personas de virtud y verdadero conocimiento.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00543VIC in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00543vic/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Heer! Laat Uw verdraagzame dienaren overwinnen in Uw dagen door hun een passende zege te schenken, daar zij naar het martelaarschap op Uw pad verlangen. Zend tot hen neer hetgeen hun gemoed zal vertroosten, hun innerlijk zal verblijden, hun hart gerust zal stellen, hun lichaam tot kalmte zal brengen en hun ziel in staat zal stellen op te stijgen tot de tegenwoordigheid van God, de Verhevenste, en het allerhoogste paradijs en die glorieuze toevluchtsoorden te bereiken die Gij hebt bestemd voor de mensen met ware kennis en deugd.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
