<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB02866 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab02866/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB02866 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab02866/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02866 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab02866/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab02866/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord, my God and my Haven in my distress! My Shield and my Shelter in my woes! My Asylum and Refuge in time of need and in my loneliness my Companion! In my anguish my Solace, and in my solitude a loving Friend! The Remover of the pangs of my sorrows and the Pardoner of my sins! Wholly unto Thee do I turn, fervently imploring Thee with all my heart, my mind and my tongue, to shield me from all that runs counter to Thy will in this, the cycle of Thy divine unity, and to cleanse me of all defilement that will hinder me from seeking, stainless and unsullied, the shade of the tree of Thy grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02866 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab02866/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab02866/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Eternulo, mia Dio kaj mia Haveno en mia aflikto! Mia Ŝildo kaj mia Ŝirmo en miaj turmentoj! Mia Azilo kaj mia Rifuĝejo en horo de bezono, kaj en mia izoleco mia Kunulo! En mia angoro mia Konsolo, kaj en mia soleco amema Amiko! La Foriganto de la doloregoj de miaj ĉagrenoj, kaj la Pardonanto de miaj pekoj! Nur al Vi mi turnas min, fervore petegante Vin per mia tuta koro, mia menso kaj mia lango, ke Vi protektu min de ĉio, kio kontraŭas Vian volon en ĉi tiu ciklo de Via dia unueco, kaj ke Vi purigu min de ĉiu malpuro, kiu malebligas al mi celadi senmakula kaj pura al la ombro de la arbo de Via graco.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
