<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB02342AWA on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab02342awa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB02342AWA on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab02342awa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02342AWA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/en/</guid>
      <description>O compassionate God! Thanks be to Thee for Thou hast awakened and made me conscious. Thou hast given me a seeing eye and favored me with a hearing ear, hast led me to Thy kingdom and guided me to Thy path. Thou hast shown me the right way and caused me to enter the ark of deliverance. O God! Keep me steadfast and make me firm and staunch. Protect me from violent tests and preserve and shelter me in the strongly fortified fortress of Thy Covenant and Testament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02342AWA in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Vi kompatema Dio! Dankoj estu al Vi por ke Vi vekis kaj konsciigis min. Vi donis al mi vidantajn okulojn kaj donacis al mi aŭdantajn orelojn. Vi kondukis min al Via regno kaj gvidis min sur Vian vojon. Vi montris al mi la ĝustan direkton kaj igis min eniri la Arkeon de Saviĝo. Ho Dio! Igu min konstanta, firma kaj fidela. Protektu min de teruraj provoj kaj gardu kaj ŝirmu min en la fortikaĵo de Via Sankta Interligo kaj Testamento.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02342AWA in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/firmness-in-the-covenant/ab02342awa/nl/</guid>
      <description>O meedogende God! Dank zij U, daar Gij mij hebt gewekt en bewust hebt gemaakt. Gij hebt mij een waarnemend oog gegeven en mij begunstigd met een luisterend oor, mij naar Uw koninkrijk gevoerd en mij naar Uw pad geleid. Gij hebt mij het rechte pad getoond en mij de ark van verlossing doen binnengaan. O God! Laat mij standvastig blijven, en maak mij vastberaden en trouw. Bescherm mij tegen hevige beproevingen, bewaar en beschut mij in de zwaar versterkte vesting van Uw Verbond en Testament.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
