<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Guidance on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-guidance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Guidance on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-guidance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13346 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13346/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13346/</guid>
      <description>O fy Nuw! Na fydded i mi unrhyw ddrwg mewn cyfnodau o dreialon, ac mewn munudau diofal arwain fy nghamau yn gywir trwy Dy ysbrydoliaeth.
O my God! Let no harm beset me in times of tests, and in moments of heedlessness guide my steps aright through Thine inspiration.
(Source category: Guidance) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 13346)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13347 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13347/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13347/</guid>
      <description>Rho i mi fy nghyfran, O Arglwydd, yn ôl dy ddymuniad,a gwna fi&amp;rsquo;n fodlon ar beth bynnagyr Wyt wedi ei ordeinio ar fy nghyfer.Tydi sydd â&amp;rsquo;r awdurdod terfynol i orchymyn.
Bestow upon me my portion, O Lord, as Thou pleasest, and cause me to be satisfied with whatsoever thou hast ordained for me. Thine is the absolute authority to command.
(Source category: Guidance) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 13347)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13348 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13348/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13348/</guid>
      <description>O Dydi Drugarog Arglwydd! Ti yr Hwn sydd Haelionus a Galluog! Dy weision ydym, a gysgodwyd dan Dy ragluniaeth. Bwrw olwg dy ffafr arnom. Rho oleuni i&amp;rsquo;n llygaid, clyw i&amp;rsquo;n clustiau, a dealltwriaeth a chariad i&amp;rsquo;n calonnau. Gwna&amp;rsquo;n heneidiau yn llawen a dedwydd drwy Dy newyddion da. O Arglwydd! Dango i ni lwybr Dy deyrnas, ac adfywhâ ni drwy anadl yr Ysbryd Glân. Dyro i ni fywyd tragwyddol a chyflwyna arnom anrhydedd di-baid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6788 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6788/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6788/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! Rain down, I beseech Thee, from the clouds of Thine overflowing grace, that which shall cleanse the hearts of Thy servants from whatever may prevent their beholding Thy face, or may prevent them from turning unto Thee, that they may all recognize Him Who is their Fashioner and Creator. Help them, then, O God, to reach forth, through the power of Thy sovereign might, towards such a station that they can readily distinguish every foul smell from the fragrance of the raiment of Him Who is the Bearer of Thy most lofty and exalted name, that they may turn with all their affections toward Thee, and may enjoy such intimate communion with Thee that if all that is in heaven and on earth were given them they would regard it as unworthy of their notice, and would refuse to cease from remembering Thee and from extolling Thy virtues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6789 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6789/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6789/</guid>
      <description>We pray to God to graciously assist them that have been led astray to be just and fair-minded, and to make them aware of that whereof they have been heedless. He, in truth, is the All-Bounteous, the Most Generous. Debar not Thy servants, O my Lord, from the door of Thy grace, and drive them not away from the court of Thy presence. Assist them to dispel the mists of idle fancy, and to tear away the veils of vain imaginings and hopes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6801 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6801/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6801/</guid>
      <description>My God, the Object of my adoration, the Goal of my desire, the All-Bountiful, the Most Compassionate! All life is of Thee and all power lieth within the grasp of Thine omnipotence. Whosoever Thou exaltest is raised above the angels, and attaineth the station: “Verily, We uplifted him to a place on high!”; and whosoever Thou dost abase is made lower than dust, nay, less than nothing.
O Divine Providence! Though wicked, sinful, and intemperate, we still seek from Thee a “seat of truth,” and long to behold the countenance of the Omnipotent King.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
