<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Tablets of the Divine Plan on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-tablets-of-the-divine-plan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Tablets of the Divine Plan on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-tablets-of-the-divine-plan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00049RAP in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00049rap/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00049rap/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá’ís of the United States and Canada
*Whoever sets out on a teaching journey to any place, let him recite this prayer day and night during his travels in foreign lands.
O God, my God! Thou seest me enraptured and attracted toward Thy glorious kingdom, enkindled with the fire of Thy love amongst mankind, a herald of Thy kingdom in these vast and spacious lands, severed from aught else save Thee, relying on Thee, abandoning rest and comfort, remote from my native home, a wanderer in these regions, a stranger fallen upon the ground, humble before Thine exalted Threshold, submissive toward the heaven of Thine omnipotent glory, supplicating Thee in the dead of night and at the break of dawn, entreating and invoking Thee at morn and at eventide to graciously aid me to serve Thy Cause, to spread abroad Thy Teachings and to exalt Thy Word throughout the East and the West.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00094WEA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00094wea/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00094wea/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá&amp;rsquo;ís of the United States and Canada
*Let whosoever travels to different parts to teach, peruse over mountain, desert, land and sea this supplication.
O God! O God! Thou seest my weakness, lowliness and humility before Thy creatures; nevertheless, I have trusted in Thee and have arisen in the promotion of Thy teachings among Thy strong servants, relying on Thy power and might.
O Lord! I am a broken-winged bird and desire to soar in Thy limitless space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00169BEH in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00169beh/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00169beh/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá’ís of Canada
*The spreaders of the fragrances of God should recite this prayer every morning:
O God, my God! Thou beholdest this weak one begging for celestial strength, this poor one craving Thy heavenly treasures, this thirsty one longing for the fountain of eternal life, this afflicted one yearning for Thy promised healing through Thy boundless mercy which Thou hast destined for Thy chosen servants in Thy kingdom on high.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00169FRA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00169fra/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00169fra/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá&amp;rsquo;ís of Canada and Greenland Praise be to Thee, O my God! These are Thy servants who are attracted by the fragrances of Thy mercifulness, are enkindled by the fire burning in the tree of Thy singleness, and whose eyes are brightened by beholding the splendors of the light shining in the Sinai of Thy oneness.
O Lord! Loose their tongues to make mention of Thee amongst Thy people, suffer them to speak forth Thy praise through Thy grace and loving-kindness, assist them with the cohorts of Thine angels, strengthen their loins in Thy service, and make them the signs of Thy guidance amongst Thy creatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00184KIN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00184kin/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00184kin/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá&amp;rsquo;ís of the Central States *Let the spreaders of the fragrances of God recite this prayer every morning:
O Lord, my God! Praise and thanksgiving be unto Thee for Thou hast guided me to the highway of the kingdom, suffered me to walk in this straight and far-stretching path, illumined my eye by beholding the splendors of Thy light, inclined my ear to the melodies of the birds of holiness from the kingdom of mysteries and attracted my heart with Thy love among the righteous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00209UND in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00209und/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00209und/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá&amp;rsquo;ís of the Southern States
*Every soul who travels through the cities, villages and hamlets of these States and is engaged in the diffusion of the fragrances of God, should peruse this commune every morning:
O my God! O my God! Thou seest me in my lowliness and weakness, occupied with the greatest undertaking, determined to raise Thy word among the masses and to spread Thy teachings among Thy peoples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00210BIR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00210bir/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00210bir/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá&amp;rsquo;ís of the Western States *The following commune is to be read &amp;hellip; every day:
O God! O God! This is a broken-winged bird and his flight is very slow - assist him so that he may fly toward the apex of prosperity and salvation, wing his way with the utmost joy and happiness throughout the illimitable space, raise his melody in Thy Supreme Name in all the regions, exhilarate the ears with this call, and brighten the eyes by beholding the signs of guidance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00218SOU in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00218sou/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00218sou/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá’ís of the United States and Canada
O Thou incomparable God! O Thou Lord of the Kingdom! These souls are Thy heavenly army. Assist them and, with the cohorts of the Supreme Concourse, make them victorious, so that each one of them may become like unto a regiment and conquer these countries through the love of God and the illumination of divine teachings. O God! Be Thou their supporter and their helper, and in the wilderness, the mountain, the valley, the forests, the prairies and the seas, be Thou their confidant—so that they may cry out through the power of the Kingdom and the breath of the Holy Spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00241HIG in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00241hig/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/tablets-of-the-divine-plan/ab00241hig/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá&amp;rsquo;ís of the Northeastern States
*The following supplication is to be read by the teachers and friends daily:
O Thou kind Lord! Praise be unto Thee that Thou hast shown us the highway of guidance, opened the doors of the kingdom and manifested Thyself through the Sun of Reality. To the blind Thou hast given sight; to the deaf Thou hast granted hearing; Thou hast resuscitated the dead; Thou hast enriched the poor; Thou hast shown the way to those who have gone astray; Thou hast led those with parched lips to the fountain of guidance; Thou hast suffered the thirsty fish to reach the ocean of reality; and Thou hast invited the wandering birds to the rose garden of grace.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
