<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-The Fast on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-the-fast/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-The Fast on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-the-fast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00154FIR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00154fir/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00154fir/en/</guid>
      <description>*The Kitáb-i-Aqdas states: “We have commanded you to pray and fast from the beginning of maturity [15 years]; this is ordained by God, your Lord and the Lord of your forefathers&amp;hellip; The traveler, the ailing, those who are with child or giving suck, are not bound by the fast&amp;hellip; Abstain from food and drink from sunrise to sundown, and beware lest desire deprive you of this grace that is appointed in the Book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00778 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh00778/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O Lord my God! These are the days whereon Thou hast bidden all men to observe the Fast, that through it they may purify their souls and rid themselves of all attachment to anyone but Thee, and that out of their hearts may ascend that which will be worthy of the court of Thy majesty and may well beseem the seat of the revelation of Thy oneness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01125 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01125/en/</guid>
      <description>I beseech Thee, O my God, by Thy mighty Sign, and by the revelation of Thy grace amongst men, to cast me not away from the gate of the city of Thy presence, and to disappoint not the hopes I have set on the manifestations of Thy grace amidst Thy creatures. Thou seest me, O my God, holding to Thy Name, the Most Holy, the Most Luminous, the Most Mighty, the Most Great, the Most Exalted, the Most Glorious, and clinging to the hem of the robe to which have clung all in this world and in the world to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01503ENJ in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01503enj/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01503enj/en/</guid>
      <description>Praised be Thou, O God, my God! These are the days whereon Thou hast enjoined Thy chosen ones, Thy loved ones and Thy servants to observe the Fast, which Thou hast made a light unto the people of Thy kingdom, even as Thou didst make obligatory prayer a ladder of ascent unto those who acknowledge Thy unity. I beg of Thee, O my God, by these two mighty pillars, which Thou hast ordained as a glory and honor for all mankind, to keep Thy religion safe from the mischief of the ungodly and the plotting of every wicked doer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01888 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01888/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh01888/en/</guid>
      <description>These are, O my God, the days whereon Thou didst enjoin Thy servants to observe the Fast. With it Thou didst adorn the preamble of the Book of Thy Laws revealed unto Thy creatures, and didst deck forth the Repositories of Thy commandments in the sight of all who are in Thy heaven and all who are on Thy earth. Thou hast endowed every hour of these days with a special virtue, inscrutable to all except Thee, Whose knowledge embraceth all created things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07657 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh07657/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh07657/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise be to Thee, O Lord my God! I beseech Thee by this Revelation whereby darkness hath been turned into light, through which the Frequented Fane hath been built, and the Written Tablet revealed, and the Outspread Roll uncovered, to send down upon me and upon them who are in my company that which will enable us to soar into the heavens of Thy transcendent glory, and will wash us from the stain of such doubts as have hindered the suspicious from entering into the tabernacle of Thy unity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10127 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10127/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10127/en/</guid>
      <description>In the Name of Him Who hath been promised in the Books of God, the All-Knowing, the All-Informed! The days of fasting have arrived wherein those servants who circle round Thy throne and have attained Thy presence have fasted. Say: O God of names and creator of heaven and earth! I beg of Thee by Thy Name, the All-Glorious, to accept the fast of those who have fasted for love of Thee and for the sake of Thy good-pleasure and have carried out what Thou hast bidden them in Thy Books and Tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10581 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/the-fast/bh10581/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise be unto Thee, O Lord my God! We have observed the Fast in conformity with Thy bidding and break it now through Thy love and Thy good-pleasure. Deign to accept, O my God, the deeds that we have performed in Thy path wholly for the sake of Thy beauty with our faces set towards Thy Cause, free from aught else but Thee. Bestow, then, Thy forgiveness upon us, upon our forefathers, and upon all such as have believed in Thee and in Thy mighty signs in this most great, this most glorious Revelation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12976 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12976/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12976/</guid>
      <description>*Taim bilong Lusim Kaikai em long mun bilong ‘Ala (Antap), long namba 2 de bilong mun Mas I go inap long namba 20 de bilong mun Mas. Long ol dispela de long taim bilong san ol Bahá’í i no ken dring o kaikai. Em taim bilong prea bilong strongim spirit. Husat man o meri i no winim 15 krismas o em i raun o em i gat sik o em i lapun tru, em i no mas lusim kaikai.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12977 in Tok Pisin</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12977/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/tpi/bpn12977/</guid>
      <description>Litimapim Nem bilong Yu, O Bikpela, God bilong mi! Mi askim strong long dispela Tokaut, em tokaut i bin mekim tudak i kamap lait. Na em i bin mekim Haus Lotu i kamap, na em i bin raitim Pas Holi, na em i bin mekim Tok Holi i kamap ples klia. Olsem na mi askim strong long en long salim ol gutpela samting i kam daun long mi wantaim ol lain husat i stap wantaim mi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6442 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6442/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6442/</guid>
      <description>Thou seest, O God of Mercy, Thou Whose power pervadeth all created things, these servants of Thine, Thy thralls, who, according to the good-pleasure of Thy Will, observe in the daytime the fast prescribed by Thee, who arise, at the earliest dawn of day, to make mention of Thy Name, and to celebrate Thy praise, in the hope of obtaining their share of the goodly things that are treasured up within the treasuries of Thy grace and bounty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6808 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6808/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6808/</guid>
      <description>O Divine Providence! As I am abstaining from bodily desires and not occupied with eating and drinking, even so purify and sanctify my heart from the love of anyone save Thyself, and shield and protect my soul from corrupt desires and satanic qualities, so that my spirit may commune with the breaths of holiness, and fast from the mention of all else besides Thee.
*Remembrance of God, p. 151-2
(Source category: The Fast) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6833 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6833/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6833/</guid>
      <description>O my God and my Master! Thou seest me among Thy creatures who have rebelled and transgressed against Thee. Every time I invite them unto the ocean of Thy knowledge, their repudiation of Thy Cause increaseth and their rejection of the Dawning-Place of Thy Will waxeth greater. I beg of Thee, O my God, by those who have fasted for love of Thee and have quaffed the living waters of submission from the hands of Thy bounty, to ordain for Thy loved ones, who under the blaze of the orb of Thy trials have clung to the cord of patience, all the good Thou hast reckoned in Thy Books and Thy Tablets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6834 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6834/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn6834/</guid>
      <description>Exalted art Thou, O Lord my God! I beseech Thee by those whom Thou hast bidden to observe the Fast for the sake of Thy love and good-pleasure, who have demonstrated their allegiance to Thy law and followed Thy verses and precepts, and who have broken their fast while enjoying near access to Thee and beholding Thy countenance. By Thy glory! Since they are turning to the court of Thy good-pleasure, all their days are days of fasting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
