<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH07426FOO on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh07426foo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH07426FOO on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh07426foo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07426FOO in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/en/</guid>
      <description>O my Lord! Make Thy beauty to be my food, and Thy presence my drink, and Thy pleasure my hope, and praise of Thee my action, and remembrance of Thee my companion, and the power of Thy sovereignty my succorer, and Thy habitation my home, and my dwelling-place the seat Thou hast sanctified from the limitations imposed upon them who are shut out as by a veil from Thee. Thou art, verily, the Almighty, the All-Glorious, the Most Powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07426FOO in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Eternulo! Faru Vian belecon mia mangaĵo kaj Vian ĉeeston mia trinkaĵo, kaj Vian plaĉon mia espero, kaj gloradon al Vi mia agado, kaj rememoron pri Vi mia akompananto, kaj la potencon de Via suvereneco mia helpo, kaj Vian restadejon mia hejmo, kaj mian vivejon la loko, kiun Vi sanktigis de la limoj metitaj al tiuj, kiuj kvazaŭ per vualo estas forfermitaj de Vi. Vi estas vere la Ĉio-pova, la Plejglora, la Plejpotenca.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07426FOO in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh07426foo/it/</guid>
      <description>O mio Signore! Fa’ che la Tua bellezza sia il mio cibo e la Tua presenza il mio nèttare, e il Tuo compiacimento la mia speranza. e la lode di Te il mio agire, e il ricordo di Te il mio compagno, e la potenza della Tua sovranità il mio soccorso, e la Tua dimora la mia casa, e la mia dimora il seggio che Tu hai purificato dalle limitazioni imposte a coloro che sono separati da Te come da un velo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
