<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lang-ik on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/lang-ik/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lang-ik on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/lang-ik/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn10177 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn10177/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn10177/</guid>
      <description>**Short Children&amp;rsquo;s Prayer
God, aullatiŋŋa, qaunagiŋŋa, suaŋasiḷaaġuŋ qaummataa uummatiŋma suli uvluġiatun qivliatitaġluni iñuusiġa. Ilvich Suaŋŋatiqpaurutin.
O God, guide me, protect me, make of me a shining lamp and a brilliant star. Thou art the Mighty and the Powerful.
(Source category: Iñupiaq - North Slope Dialect) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 10177)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12870 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn12870/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn12870/</guid>
      <description>** Invocation of The Báb God, God-igigikpiñ, Piviutaġigikpiñ, Pisramaaġaatin uummatiġma.
(Source category: Iñupiaq - North Slope Dialect) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 12870)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12873 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn12873/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn12873/</guid>
      <description>** Obligatory Prayer for the Dead
 Instructions for recitation: Una Tuquŋaruanun Aŋaiyyun Bahá’í-it piraksriatualuŋat taiguaksraq aŋaiyuliqiruanun; nipaisaḷḷaġmiŋ makitallaisa aŋaiyuliqiruat atausim ukpiktuam taiguaqtuksraugaa. Bahá’u’lláh-am kaŋiksipkaŋaġaa una aŋaiyyun piraksraq tuquŋaruanun ukiuqtutilaaqaŋaruanun sippiqługu akimiatun, taiguaqtuksraugaa tutquŋaiñŋaan, suli piraksraitchuq saattuksrauvlugu qukinaqtuaq tutguġvia Nalautchaqtim. “Alláh-u-Abhá” taiñaqtuq atausiaglugu; aasi sivullia taapqua itchaksrat uqaluich taiglugi iñuiññaġutaiḷatun. Taitqiġlugu “Alláh-u-Abhá”, aasi tugliat uqalluit taimmilugusuli iñuiññaġutaiḷatun, tainaasi maligilugit piraksriutit naatilluġit uqaluit kisiŋŋuŋaruat. ** Prayer: God-igiraqpin! Uvva kivgan iġñiŋalu kivgaġiraqpich ukpiġutiqagłuni Iliŋnun nalunaiñŋutaġiraġnullu, kiiññiġvigigaatin, allamun tigummiruaguŋitchut iluġnaaqłutin aglaan Ilignun kisian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12875 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn12875/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn12875/</guid>
      <description>**Say: God Sufficeth Uqalagiñ: God aitchuisuuruq naamasivļuta qaaŋiłuaługiļu, qiļaġmilu naagga nunami naamaiichuruk aglaan kisian God-im qaitchaŋa naamasuruq. Iļumupiaġataq, Ilaa Iliminiłuni Iļlisimariuruq, Aitchuiri inuuniksraptigni, Kamanaġniqsrauruq.
Say: God sufficeth all things above all things, and nothing in the heavens or in the earth but God sufficeth. Verily, He is in Himself the Knower, the Sustainer, the Omnipotent. **The Báb
(Source category: Iñupiaq - North Slope Dialect) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 12875)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12876 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn12876/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn12876/</guid>
      <description>**Blessed is the Spot Quviatchaktauli ini, iglulu, nalunaitchuaq inilu, suli iniqpak, uummanlu, iġġiļu, annagvigļu, qaanaaġlu, naqsraġlu, nunalu, taġiuġlu, qikiqtaġlu, nunaraaġlu, tavra tammatkunani God taiļaktuniunnii qutchiksuaġilugu nanġapiaġataġaat.
Blessed is the spot, and the house, and the place, and the city, and the heart, and the mountain, and the refuge, and the cave, and the valley, and the land, and the sea, and the island and the meadow where mention of God hath been made and His praise glorified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9095 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9095/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9095/</guid>
      <description>**Morning Prayer
Kaŋiqsigiga qaunakkutin, God-iiŋ, Ikayuqtausuumaruq paqitchiruaq qaunakkunmik Iliŋni tutqiksimaaġnamallu suaŋammallu.
I have wakened in Thy shelter, O my God, and it becometh him that seeketh that shelter to abide within the Sanctuary of Thy protection and the Stronghold of Thy defense.
(Source category: Iñupiaq - North Slope Dialect) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9095)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9097 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9097/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9097/</guid>
      <description>**Children&amp;rsquo;s Prayer
Ataniiŋ! Ataniiŋ! Miqłiqtuurauruŋa. Iñuusiŋŋa nagliktuutigniñ, iḷitchipkaaŋa nakuaqqutigni, iḷisauttunŋŋa igliġutiluŋa iñuguqtinŋa aatchuutikkun. Taaqtuamiisinnaŋa, qaumapkaŋŋa; ipiqtusuunmiñ piisinŋa, qiñiyunaqtinŋa nautchiani; kivgaullasiŋŋa qiñuiġḷuŋa suli iḷitchuġipkaŋŋa irrusiannik ilauqtuakun iñuuniaqtuat; aatchuutaupkaŋŋa nunami iñuuniaqtuanun aasii niaquġuchiġḷuŋa niaquġutaanik iñuggutim taimuŋa. Iḷumun Suaŋarutin, Tautullarutin, Tusaallarutin.
O my Lord! O my Lord! I am a child of tender years. Nourish me from the breast of Thy mercy, train me in the bosom of Thy love, educate me in the school of Thy guidance and develop me under the shadow of Thy bounty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9098 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9098/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9098/</guid>
      <description>**Prayer for Children God, iḷisauttukki migłiqtut. Migłiqtut ukua nautchiagurut nautchiivigñi. Sialugnik aatchukki; siqiñġanik iḷumun ittuam qaummaġiksitki nakuaqqutikkun. Anuqsraaġiksitki nutaaġuqsaqtut aasii iḷisimalutiglu naulutiglu qiññaġikpagmiḷutik. Pamatchiraurutin. Nagliktaurutin.
O God! Educate these children. These children are the plants of Thine orchard, the flowers of Thy meadow, the roses of Thy garden. Let Thy rain fall upon them; let the Sun of Reality shine upon them with Thy love. Let Thy breeze refresh them in order that they may be trained, grow and develop, and appear in the utmost beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9099 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9099/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9099/</guid>
      <description>**Short Healing Prayer Atqin mamittautigigiga, God-iiŋ, aasii itqaummatiga natqiksautigigiga. Qaninniġa Iliŋnun niġiukkutigigiga, nakuaqqutigalu Iliŋnun piqataupiaqtuq. Naglikkutin uvamnun mamirutauruq ikayuutauvluniḷu paŋmapak nunaptigni qaiñiaqtuamullu. Ilvich iḷumun Sigñataitchutin, Iḷisimałhaaqtutin, Isumatułhaaqtutin.
Thy name is my healing, O my God, and remembrance of Thee is my remedy. Nearness to Thee is my hope, and love for Thee is my companion. Thy mercy to me is my healing and my succor in both this world and the world to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9100 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9100/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9100/</guid>
      <description>**Prayer for Steadfastness Anayanaikkich avluġnipayaavut, Ataniiq, apqutikkun suaŋasaaġlugiḷḷu uummativut kamakkutigni.
Make firm our steps, O Lord, in Thy path and strengthen Thou our hearts in Thine obedience.
(Source category: Iñupiaq - North Slope Dialect) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9100)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9102 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9102/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9102/</guid>
      <description>**Prayer for the Departed (Short)
God-iiŋ! Ilivich suliqutigiŋaisi piluutinik, aitchuirri supayaanik, piiqsiri nagliksaaġutinik! Iḷumutupiaq, Ilignun qiññuaqtuqtuŋa suliqutigiŋaiquvlugich piluutiŋich tainaġruiññaq suksraaqsiruanun timmim annuġaaŋanik aasii mayughutiŋ iḷitqusipayaat nunaŋanun. Ataniiŋ! Salummakkich kilukuaġutipyaanin, piglaktitkich isumaaġutiŋitch, allaŋuġuŋ taaqtuaŋat simmiġlugu qaumaġmik. Isillasikkich nauriaqaġviŋanun quviannaqtuam, salummakkich salumapiaġataqtuamik imiġmik, suli qiniḷasipkakkich qiñiyunaġniksraŋiññik qutchigniqram iġġim.
O my God! O Thou forgiver of sins, bestower of gifts, dispeller of afflictions! Verily, I beseech Thee to forgive the sins of such as have abandoned the physical garment and have ascended to the spiritual world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9103 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9103/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9103/</guid>
      <description>**Remover of Difficulties
God-im avataagun nagliksaaġutit piiqsiqaqpat? Uqallagiñ: Nanġaqtauli God! Ilaa God-tauruq! Iluqaġmik kivgagġigaich kamagivlugu sutqupayaaġmatik.
Is there any Remover of difficulties save God? Say: Praised be God! He is God! All are His servants, and all abide by His bidding!
(Source category: Iñupiaq - North Slope Dialect) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9103)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn9104 in Alaska Native</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9104/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/ik/bpn9104/</guid>
      <description>**Short Obligatory Prayer
Iḷisimarauruŋa, God-iiŋ, Iliŋun savaŋatilaamnik Iḷisimatquvlutin suli nanġaquvlutin. Quliaqtuaġigiga akkupak suaŋŋataiññiġa suli ilvich suaŋŋatiqpaiñ, uvanga iḷiappauniġa suli ilvich umialguniġin. Allamik God-aitchuq ilvich avatikkun, ikayuiḷḷarutin siġġaġniuġnami suli ilimik aŋalatchumiñaiqłuni iḷiruni.
I bear witness, O my God, that Thou hast created me to know Thee and to worship Thee. I testify, at this moment, to my powerlessness and to Thy might, to my poverty and to Thy wealth. There is none other God but Thee, the Help in Peril, the Self-Subsisting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
