<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH06026 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh06026/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH06026 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh06026/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH06026 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/en/</guid>
      <description>He is the Gracious, the All-Bountiful!
O God, my God! Thy call hath attracted me, and the voice of Thy Pen of Glory awakened me. The stream of Thy holy utterance hath enraptured me, and the wine of Thine inspiration entranced me. Thou seest me, O Lord, detached from all things but Thee, clinging to the cord of Thy bounty and craving the wonders of Thy grace. I ask Thee, by the eternal billows of Thy loving-kindness and the shining lights of Thy tender care and favor, to grant that which shall draw me nigh unto Thee and make me rich in Thy wealth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH06026 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/nl/</guid>
      <description>Hij is de Genadige, de Almilddadige! O God, mijn God! Uw roep trok mij aan en de stem van Uw Pen van heerlijkheid heeft mij gewekt. De stroom van Uw heilige woorden heeft mij betoverd en de wijn van Uw bezieling heeft mij in vervoering gebracht. Gij ziet mij, o Heer, onthecht van alles buiten U, mij vastklemmend aan het koord van Uw milddadigheid en hunkerend naar de wonderen van Uw genade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH06026 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/spiritual-growth/bh06026/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ele é o Bondoso, o Generosíssimo! Ó Deus, meu Deus! O Teu chamado atraiu-me e a voz da Tua Pena de Glória despertou-me. O fluxo das Tuas santas palavras enlevou-me, e com o vinho da Tua inspiração extasiei-me. Tu me vês, ó Senhor, desprendido de tudo, menos de Ti, agarrado à corda das Tuas dádivas e desejoso das maravilhas da Tua graça. Peço-Te, pelas ondas eternas da Tua misericórdia e pelas luzes cintilantes da Tua ternura e dos Teus favores – concede o que me aproxime de Ti e me torne rico em Tua riqueza.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
