<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH09399 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09399/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH09399 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh09399/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09399 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09399/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09399/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O my God! My face hath been set towards Thy face, and my face is, verily, Thy face, and my call is Thy call, and my Revelation Thy Revelation, and my self Thy Self, and my Cause Thy Cause, and my behest Thy behest, and my Being Thy Being, and my sovereignty Thy sovereignty, and my glory Thy glory, and my power Thy power. I implore Thee, O Thou Fashioner of the nations and the King of eternity, to guard Thy handmaidens within the tabernacle of Thy chastity, and to cancel such of their deeds as are unworthy of Thy days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09399 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09399/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh09399/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Gloria sea a Ti, oh mi Dios! Mi rostro se ha dirigido hacia Tu rostro, y mi rostro es, ciertamente, Tu rostro, y mi llamamiento es Tu llamamiento, y mi Revelación, Tu Revelación, y mi ser, Tu Ser, y mi Causa, Tu Causa, y mi mandato, Tu mandato, y mi Existencia, Tu Existencia, y mi soberanía, Tu soberanía, y mi gloria, Tu gloria, y mi poder, Tu poder. Yo te imploro, oh Tú Modelador de las naciones y Rey de la eternidad, que resguardes a Tus siervas en el tabernáculo de Tu castidad, y canceles aquellos de sus actos que sean indignos de Tus días.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
