<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Morning on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-morning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Morning on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-morning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009AWA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/en/</guid>
      <description>I give praise to Thee, O my God, that Thou hast awakened me out of my sleep, and brought me forth after my disappearance, and raised me up from my slumber. I have wakened this morning with my face set toward the splendors of the Daystar of thy Revelation, through Which the heavens of Thy power and Thy majesty have been illumined, acknowledging Thy signs, believing in Thy Book, and holding fast unto Thy Cord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009AWA in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/fy/</guid>
      <description>Ik priizgje Jo, o myn God, dat Jo my út &amp;rsquo;e sliep wekker makke hawwe en my út myn fuort-wêzen oproppen hawwe en my út myn slomme ferrize litten hawwe. Ik bin dizze moarn wekker wurden mei myn antlit heve nei de pracht fan de Dei-Stjer fan Jo iepenbiering dêr&amp;rsquo;t de himelen fan Jo macht en Jo majesteit troch ferljochte wurden binne; ik erken Jo tekens, leau yn Jo Boek en hâld fêst oan Jo koarde.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009AWA in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009awa/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ik loof U, o mijn God, dat Gij mij uit mijn slaap deed ontwaken en mij uit mijn verzonken-zijn hebt geroepen en mij uit mijn sluimer deed verrijzen. Ik ben deze morgen ontwaakt met mijn gelaat geheven naar de pracht van de Dagster van Uw Openbaring, die de hemelen van Uw macht en Uw majesteit heeft verlicht; ik erken Uw tekenen, geloof in Uw Boek en houd vast aan Uw koord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009SHE in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009she/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009she/en/</guid>
      <description>I have wakened in Thy shelter, O my God, and it becometh him that seeketh that shelter to abide within the Sanctuary of Thy protection and the Stronghold of Thy defense. Illumine my inner being, O my Lord, with the splendors of the Dayspring of Thy Revelation, even as thou didst illumine my outer being with the morning light of Thy favor.
(Source category: Morning) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 274)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009SHE in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009she/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009she/eo/</guid>
      <description>Mi vekiĝis sub Via ŝirmo, ho mia Dio, kaj decas al tiu, kiu serĉas tiun ŝirmon, restadi en la Sanktejo de Via protekto kaj la Fortikaĵo de Via defendo. Iluminu mian internan estaĵon, ho mia Eternulo, per la majesto de la Tagiĝo de Via Revelacio, samkiel Vi iluminis mian eksteran estaĵon per la matena lumo de Via favoro.
(Source category: Mateno) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 4340)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00009SHE in Frysk</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009she/fy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh00009she/fy/</guid>
      <description>Ik bin ûnder Jo beskutting wekker wurden,o myn God, en it past him dy&amp;rsquo;t dy beskutting siket te ferkearen yn it Hillichdom fan Jo beskerming en yn de Fêsting fan Jo ferdigening. Ferljochtsje myn ynderlik wêzen, o myn Hear, mei de pracht fan de Dage fan Jo iepenbiering, lykas Jo myn uterlik wêzen ferljochte hawwe mei it moarntiidsljocht fan Jo geunst.
(Source category: Moarn) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 6035)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH02848 in Afrikaans</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh02848/af/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh02848/af/</guid>
      <description>O my God en my Meester! Ek is U dienaar en die seun van U dienaar. Ek het met hierdie dagbreek van my kooi af opgestaan toe die Môrester van U eenheid uit die Daeraad van U wil voortgeskyn het, en sy glans oor die hele wêreld gegooi het, ooreenkomstig wat in die Boeke van U Verordening bepaal is.
Lof sy aan U, o my God, dat ons vir die luister van die lig van U kennis waker geword het.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH02848 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh02848/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh02848/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God and my Master! I am Thy servant and the son of Thy servant. I have risen from my couch at this dawntide when the Daystar of Thy oneness hath shone forth from the Dayspring of Thy will, and hath shed its radiance upon the whole world, according to what had been ordained in the Books of Thy Decree. Praise be unto Thee, O my God, that we have wakened to the splendors of the light of Thy knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH02848 in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh02848/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh02848/fr/</guid>
      <description>Ô mon Dieu, mon Maître, je suis ton serviteur et le fils de ton serviteur. J’ai quitté ma couche dès l’aurore, alors que le Soleil de ton unité apparaissait à l’aube de ta volonté et répandait son rayonnement sur le monde entier, comme l’ordonnent les livres de ton décret. Ô mon Dieu, loué sois-tu ! Tu nous as éveillés aux splendeurs de la lumière de ta connaissance. Ô mon Seigneur, fais descendre sur nous ce qui nous permettra de nous libérer de tout attachement et de nous passer de tout sauf de toi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH02848 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh02848/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/morning/bh02848/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó meu Deus e meu Mestre! Sou um servo Teu e filho de um dos Teus servos. Levantei-me do meu leito ao amanhecer, quando o Sol da Tua unicidade brilhou na Aurora do Teu desígnio, irradiando-se por sobre o mundo inteiro, segundo o que fora prescrito nos Livros do Teu Decreto. Louvor a Ti, ó meu Deus, por havermos despertado para os esplendores da luz do Teu conhecimento. Faze, pois, descer sobre nós, ó meu Senhor, o que nos permita dispensar qualquer um salvo a Ti, e de tudo, menos de Ti, nos desprenda.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
