<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Chippewa on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-chippewa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Chippewa on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-chippewa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn4151 in Canadian Indigenous</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-ca/bpn4151/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-ca/bpn4151/</guid>
      <description>Sigakundjigauso peendji okitahgisiwinug dibishko wigiwam, gahyay o-ahbinass, odaynah, odayimah, owahjiw, ininizhimowin, wimbakbikamagud, tahwandinah, akki, gitchegahmi, miniss, gahyay, mashkossigan auneendi gigitowin O Gitche Manito Kosaynaun Missigaygo Gaugezhetod gabyay ahwaineen gezhegoong aindaut, ahwainsen ondji ozhitchigauday ondji.
*Blessed is the spot, and the house, and the place, and the city, and the heart, and the mountain, and the refuge, and the cave, and the valley, and the land, and the sea, and the island, and the meadow where mention of God hath been made, and His praise glorified.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn5405 in American Indian</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-us/bpn5405/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-us/bpn5405/</guid>
      <description>O Gitchi - Manitou! Kegagwetchemin chiminut, ni - manitoum chi - min - ain - dung. Beniton, nedae. Wasseiasiwin - meeng - ni - gashkiewisiwin. Ni - we - pakitinan kakina - danokeen - pindig - Kinindg. Keen - chiweechi - we - un, gaie ni - iningimowin. Kaween, minawa - Kashkendamowessi, gaie, Kaween - inaninawendaman. Ga - aiaa, chi - menaindaman, gaie, gaminawanigos. O Gitchi - Manitou! Kaween, gamoshkinase - chi - migoshkadjidewian, gaie, kaween - niwe - pakitinase - ewai - Kashkendamowin chi - megoshkadjian.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn5406 in American Indian</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-us/bpn5406/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-us/bpn5406/</guid>
      <description>O Manitou Ogwissiman! Neen - nitam - gegitowin - oway: Nin - dan Benidewin, Kijewadisiwin, gaie, Wasseiasiwin kide, eway - Keen, che - atake, Kitchi - Ogimawin, Gete, Gashkiewisiwin gaie kagige. O Son of Spirit! My first counsel is this: Possess a pure, kindly and radiant heart, that thine may be a sovereignty ancient, imperishable and everlasting.
(Source category: Chippewa) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 5406)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn6846 in American Indian</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-us/bpn6846/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/nai-us/bpn6846/</guid>
      <description>Gichi-tawaawan maanpii, miinwaa wiigawaaming, miinwaa oodi, miinwaa oodenaang, miinwaa odewining, miinwaa aazhbikong, miinwaa enji-dabinooshnaang, miinwaa waazhing, miinwaa msagmigaak, miinwaa akiing, miinwaa gichi-gamiing, miinwaa minising, miinwaa mshkodensing, gaa nji kidong dizhinikaazwin Gazhe Manitoo miinwaa wiin gichi-piitendaagoziwin gichi-tawaa-endaagaadeg.
 Baha&#39;u&#39;llah  Blessed is the spot, and the house, and the place, and the city, and the heart, and the mountain, and the refuge, and the cave, and the valley, and the land, and the sea, and the island, and the meadow where mention of God hath been made, and His praise glorified.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
