<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Gatherings on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-gatherings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Gatherings on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-gatherings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blessed is the Spot in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh00074ble/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh00074ble/en/</guid>
      <description>Blessed is the spot, and the house, and the place, and the city, and the heart, and the mountain, and the refuge, and the cave, and the valley, and the land, and the sea, and the island, and the meadow where mention of God hath been made, and His praise glorified.
(Source category: Gatherings) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 4966)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blessed is the Spot in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh00074ble/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh00074ble/eo/</guid>
      <description>Benita estas la punkto, kaj la domo, kaj la loko, kaj la urbo, kaj la koro, kai la monto, kaj la ŝirmejo, kaj la kavo, kaj la valo, kaj la lando, kaj la maro, kaj la insulo, kaj la kampo, kie oni Dion mencias kaj Lin laŭde gloras.
(Source category: Laŭdo kaj Danko) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 4337)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blessed is the Spot in Føroyar</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh00074ble/fo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh00074ble/fo/</guid>
      <description>Vælsignaður er tann blettur, og tað hús, og tað stað, og tann býur, og tað hjarta, og tað fjall, og tað skjól, og tann hola, og tann dalur, og tann jørð, og tað hav, og tann oyggj, og tann hagi, har Gud hevur verið nevndur og lovprísan Hansara dýrdargjørd.
(Source category: Lýdni) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 6075)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blessed is the Spot in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh00074ble/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh00074ble/fr/</guid>
      <description>Béni est le lieu, la maison et l’endroit,la ville et le cœur,la montagne et le refuge,la caverne et la vallée,le pays et la mer,l’île et la prairie,où Dieu est évoqué et sa louange glorifiée.
(Source category: Familles) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9406)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blessed is the Spot in Papiamentu</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh00074ble/pap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh00074ble/pap/</guid>
      <description>*Blessed is the spot…
Santifiká sea e sitio, i e kas, i e lugá, i e siudat, i e kurason, i e seru, i e refuhio, i e kueba, i e vaye, i e tera, i e laman, i e isla, i e pradera, unda ku Dios ta menshoná, i su alabansa ta glorifiká.
(Source category: Gatherings) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 6874)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00388COM in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/ab00388com/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/ab00388com/en/</guid>
      <description>O Divine Providence! This assemblage is composed of Thy friends who are attracted to Thy beauty and are set ablaze by the fire of Thy love. Turn these souls into heavenly angels, resuscitate them through the breath of Thy Holy Spirit, grant them eloquent tongues and resolute hearts, bestow upon them heavenly power and merciful susceptibilities, cause them to become the promulgators of the oneness of mankind and the cause of love and concord in the world of humanity, so that the perilous darkness of ignorant prejudice may vanish through the light of the Sun of Truth, this dreary world may become illumined, this material realm may absorb the rays of the world of spirit, these different colors may merge into one color and the melody of praise may rise to the kingdom of Thy sanctity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00388COM in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/ab00388com/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/ab00388com/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Divina Providência! Essa congregação é formada pelos Teus amigos, atraídos à Tua beleza e inflamados com o fogo do Teu amor. Transforma essas almas em anjos celestiais, ressuscita-as através dos sopros do Teu Espírito Santo, concede-lhes línguas eloquentes e corações resolutos, dota-as de poder celestial e de susceptibilidades misericordiosas, faze com que sejam promotoras da unidade do género humano e a causa de amor e concórdia no mundo humano, para que assim as perigosas trevas do preconceito ignorante se desvaneçam ante a luz do Sol da Verdade, e este mundo sombrio se ilumine, e este reino material possa absorver os raios do mundo do espírito, e essas cores diferentes possam fundir-se numa só cor, e a melodia do louvor possa elevar-se ao reino de Tua santidade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00397HEA in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/ab00397hea/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/ab00397hea/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou loving Provider! These souls have hearkened to the summons of the Kingdom, and have gazed upon the glory of the Sun of Truth. They have risen upward to the refreshing skies of love; they are enamored of Thy nature, and they worship Thy beauty. Unto Thee have they turned themselves, speaking together of Thee, seeking out Thy dwelling, and thirsting for the waterbrooks of Thy heavenly realm. Thou art the Giver, the Bestower, the Ever-Loving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0003DIS in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0003dis/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0003dis/en/</guid>
      <description>##The Nineteen Day Feast
O God! Dispel all those elements which are the cause of discord, and prepare for us all those things which are the cause of unity and accord! O God! Descend upon us Heavenly Fragrance and change this gathering into a gathering of Heaven! Grant to us every benefit and every food. Prepare for us the Food of Love! Give us the Food of Knowledge! Bestow on us the Food of Heavenly Illumination!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0070GAT in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! These are Thy servants who have gathered in this meeting, have turned unto Thy kingdom and are in need of Thy bestowal and blessing. O Thou God! Manifest and make evident the signs of Thy oneness which have been deposited in all the realities of life. Reveal and unfold the virtues which Thou hast made latent and concealed in these human realities.
O God! We are as plants, and Thy bounty is as the rain; refresh and cause these plants to grow through Thy bestowal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0070GAT in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh bondadoso Señor! Estos son Tus siervos que han concurrido a esta reunión, se han vuelto hacia Tu reino y necesitan Tus dádivas y bendiciones. ¡Oh Dios! Manifiesta y haz evidentes las señales de Tu unicidad que han sido depositadas en todas las realidades de la vida. Revela y despliega las virtudes que has dejado latentes y ocultas en estas realidades humanas. ¡Oh Dios! Nosotros somos como plantas y Tu generosidad es como la lluvia; refresca y haz crecer estas plantas mediante Tu favor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0070GAT in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0070gat/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Vi, bonema Dio! Jen Viaj geservantoj, kiuj kolektiĝis en tiu ĉi kunveno, sin turnis al Via regno kaj bezonas Vian favoron kaj benon. Ho Vi Dio! Malkaŝu kaj evidentigu la signojn de Via ununureco entenatajn en ĉiuj realoj de la vivo. Revelaciu kaj disvolvu la virtojn, kiujn Vi metis latentaj kaj kaŝitaj en tiujn ĉi homajn realojn. Ho Dio! Ni estas kvazaŭ plantoj, kaj Via malavaro estas kiel la pluvo; refresigu kaj kreskigu tiujn ĉi plantojn per Via donacado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0095KIN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0095kin/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0095kin/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou forgiving God! These servants are turning to Thy kingdom and seeking Thy grace and bounty. O God! Make their hearts good and pure in order that they may become worthy of Thy love. Purify and sanctify the spirits that the light of the Sun of Reality may shine upon them. Purify and sanctify the eyes that they may perceive Thy light. Purify and sanctify the ears in order that they may hear the call of Thy kingdom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0188TUR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0188tur/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/abu0188tur/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O my God! Verily, these servants are turning to Thee, supplicating Thy kingdom of mercy. Verily, they are attracted by Thy holiness and set aglow with the fire of Thy love, seeking confirmation from Thy wondrous kingdom, and hoping for attainment in Thy heavenly realm. Verily, they long for the descent of Thy bestowal, desiring illumination from the Sun of Reality. O Lord! Make them radiant lamps, merciful signs, fruitful trees and shining stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09848 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh09848/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/bh09848/en/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! I implore Thee by the onrushing winds of Thy grace, and by them Who are the Daysprings of Thy purpose and the Dawning-Places of Thine inspiration, to send down upon me and upon all that have sought Thy face that which beseemeth Thy generosity and bountiful grace, and is worthy of Thy bestowals and favors. Poor and desolate I am, O my Lord! Immerse me in the ocean of Thy wealth; athirst, suffer me to drink from the living waters of Thy loving-kindness.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
