<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB10492 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab10492/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB10492 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab10492/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10492 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! Bestow heavenly confirmation upon this daughter of the kingdom, and graciously aid her that she may remain firm and steadfast in Thy Cause and that she may, even as a nightingale of the rose garden of mysteries, warble melodies in the Abhá Kingdom in the most wondrous tones, thereby bringing happiness to everyone. Make her exalted among the daughters of the kingdom and enable her to attain life eternal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10492 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh bondadoso Señor! Otorga confirmaciones divinas a esta hija del reino, y ayúdala bondadosamente a que se mantenga firme y constante en Tu Causa y, cual ruiseñor del rosedal de los misterios, entone melodías en el Reino de Abhá con los más bellos acordes, y traiga con ello alegría a todos. Enaltécela entre las hijas del reino y permítele alcanzar la vida eterna. Tú eres el Otorgador, el Amoroso.
(Source category: Jóvenes) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB10492 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/youth/ab10492/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij vriendelijk Heer! Schenk deze dochter van het koninkrijk hemelse gaven en help haar genadiglijk standvastig en sterk te blijven in Uw Zaak, opdat zij, gelijk een nachtegaal in de rozentuin van mysteriën, wonderschone melodieën mag zingen in het Abhá-koninkrijk en zo iedereen vreugde mag brengen. Verhef haar onder de dochters van het koninkrijk en laat haar eeuwig leven verwerven. Gij zijt de Schenker, de Liefderijke.
(Source category: Jongeren) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
