<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BB00004REN on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bb00004ren/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BB00004REN on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bb00004ren/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00004REN in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be unto Thee, O Lord, Thou Who hast brought into being all created things, through the power of Thy behest. O Lord! Assist those who have renounced all else but Thee, and grant them a mighty victory. Send down upon them, O Lord, the concourse of the angels in heaven and earth and all that is between, to aid Thy servants, to succor and strengthen them, to enable them to achieve success, to sustain them, to invest them with glory, to confer upon them honor and exaltation, to enrich them and to make them triumphant with a wondrous triumph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00004REN in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/es/</guid>
      <description>Gloria sea a Ti, oh Señor, Tú que has traído a la existencia todas las cosas creadas, mediante el poder de Tu mandato. ¡Oh Señor! Ayuda a aquellos que han renunciado a todo cuanto no seas Tú, y confiéreles una gran victoria. ¡Oh Señor! Haz descender sobre ellos el concurso de los ángeles del cielo y de la tierra y de todo cuanto hay entre ellos, para que asistan a Tus siervos, los socorran y los fortalezcan, les faciliten el éxito, los apoyen, los invistan de gloria, les confieran honor y exaltación, los enriquezcan y les hagan triunfar con una maravillosa victoria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00004REN in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/triumph-of-the-cause/bb00004ren/eo/</guid>
      <description>Gloro estu al Vi, ho Eternulo, Vi Kiu ekzistigis ĉion kreitan per la potenco de Via ordono. Ho Eternulo! Asistu tiujn, kiuj abnegaciis ĉion alian krom Vi, kaj donu al ili grandan venkon. Sendu sur ilin, ho Eternulo, la tutan aron da anĝeloj en la ĉielo kaj sur la tero kaj ĉie inter tiuj, por helpi Viajn servantojn, por asisti kaj fortigi ilin, por igi ilin kapablaj atingi sukceson, por subteni ilin, por kroni ilin per gloro, por doni al ili honoron kaj altecon, por riĉigi ilin kaj por igi ilin triumfantaj en brila venko.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
