<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Protection on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-protection/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Protection on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-protection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001SHI in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab00001shi/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab00001shi/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! Shield Thy trusted servants from the evils of self and passion, protect them with the watchful eye of Thy loving-kindness from all rancor, hate and envy, shelter them in the impregnable stronghold of Thy care and, safe from the darts of doubtfulness, make them the manifestations of Thy glorious signs, illumine their faces with the effulgent rays shed from the Dayspring of Thy divine unity, gladden their hearts with the verses revealed from Thy holy kingdom, strengthen their loins by Thine all-swaying power that cometh from Thy realm of glory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001SHI in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab00001shi/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab00001shi/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Oh Dios, mi Dios! Escuda a Tus siervos leales contra los males del egoísmo y la pasión; protégelos con la mirada vigilante de Tu amorosa bondad de todo rencor, odio y envidia; ampáralos dentro de la fortaleza inexpugnable de Tu cuidado y, libres de los dardos de la duda, hazlos las manifestaciones de Tus gloriosas señales; ilumina sus rostros con los refulgentes rayos emanados de la Aurora de Tu divina unidad; alegra sus corazones con los versículos revelados desde Tu reino de santidad; y fortalece sus espaldas con Tu poder irresistible proveniente de Tu dominio de gloria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001SHI in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab00001shi/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab00001shi/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Dio, mia Dio! Ŝirmu Viajn fidelajn servantojn je la malbonoj de memo kaj pasio, protektu ilin per la gardema okulo de Via amfavoro je ĉiuj malico, malamo kaj envio, ŝirmu ilin en la nekaptebla fortikaĵo de Via prizorgo, kaj, sekuraj je la pikiloj de dubo, faru ilin la malkaŝantoj de Viaj gloraj signoj, lumigu iliajn vizaĝojn per la brilegaj radioj elvenantaj el la Tagiĝo de Via dia unueco, feliĉigu iliajn korojn per la versoj revelaciitaj el Via sankta regno, fortikigu iliajn lumbojn per Via ĉion-reganta potenco, kiu venas el Via regno de gloro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00204PRO in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab00204pro/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab00204pro/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind and loving Providence! The east is astir and the west surgeth even as the eternal billows of the sea. The gentle breezes of holiness are diffused and, from the Unseen Kingdom, the rays of the Orb of Truth shine forth resplendent. The anthems of divine unity are being chanted and the ensigns of celestial might are waving. The angelic Voice is raised and, even as the roaring of the leviathan, soundeth the call to selflessness and evanescence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB07759 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab07759/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab07759/en/</guid>
      <description>O my Lord! Thou knowest that the people are encircled with pain and calamities and are environed with hardships and trouble. Every trial doth attack man and every dire adversity doth assail him like unto the assault of a serpent. There is no shelter and asylum for him except under the wing of Thy protection, preservation, guard and custody. O Thou the Merciful One! O my Lord! Make Thy protection my armor, Thy preservation my shield, humbleness before the door of Thy oneness my guard, and Thy custody and defense my fortress and my abode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB07759 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab07759/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/ab07759/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho mia Eternulo! Vi scias, ke la homoj estas ĉirkaŭataj de doloroj kaj afliktoj kaj de malfacilaĵoj kaj ĉagrenoj. Ĉiu tento kaptas la homon, kaj ĉiu terura mizero atakas lin kvazaŭ serpento. Ne estas ŝirmo kaj rifuĝo por li krom sub la flugiloj de Viaj protekto, gardo, zorgo kaj konservado. Ho Vi Kompatema! Ho mia Eternulo! Via protektado estu mia armo, Via konservado mia ŝirmo, humileco antaŭ la pordo de Via unueco mia gvardio, kaj Viaj zorgado kaj defendo miaj fortikaĵo kaj restadejo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00100EXI in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bb00100exi/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bb00100exi/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O God! Thou art the God Who hath existed before all things, Who will exist after all things and will last beyond all things. Thou art the God Who knoweth all things, and is supreme over all things. Thou art the God Who dealeth mercifully with all things, Who judgeth between all things and Whose vision embraceth all things. Thou art God my Lord, Thou art aware of my position, Thou dost witness my inner and outer being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00100EXI in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bb00100exi/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bb00100exi/nl/</guid>
      <description>Glorie zij U, o God! Gij zijt de God die vóór alle dingen bestond, die na alle dingen zal bestaan en die voorbij alle dingen voortduurt. Gij zijt de God die alle dingen kent en over alle dingen heerst. Gij zijt de God die alle dingen barmhartig behandelt, die over alle dingen recht spreekt en Wiens blik alle dingen omvat. Gij zijt God mijn Heer, Gij weet waar ik sta, Gij ziet en kent mijn innerlijk en mijn uiterlijk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00147ORD in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bb00147ord/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bb00147ord/en/</guid>
      <description>Ordain for me, O my Lord, and for those who believe in Thee that which is deemed best for us in Thine estimation, as set forth in the Mother Book, for within the grasp of Thy hand Thou holdest the determined measures of all things. Thy goodly gifts are unceasingly showered upon such as cherish Thy love, and the wondrous tokens of Thy heavenly bounties are amply bestowed on those who recognize Thy divine Unity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00490 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bb00490/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bb00490/en/</guid>
      <description>In the Name of God, the Lord of overpowering majesty, the All-Compelling.
Hallowed be the Lord in Whose hand is the source of dominion. He createth whatsoever He willeth by His Word of command “Be,” and it is. His hath been the power of authority heretofore, and it shall remain His hereafter. He maketh victorious whomsoever He pleaseth, through the potency of His behest. He is in truth the Powerful, the Almighty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00490 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bb00490/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bb00490/nl/</guid>
      <description>In Naam van God, de Heer van overweldigende majesteit, de Algebiedende. Geheiligd zij de Heer in Wiens hand de bron van heerschappij ligt. Hij schept wat Hij ook maar wil door Zijn gebiedend Woord “Wees” en het is. Immer heeft de kracht van gezag aan Hem behoord en deze zal Hem blijven behoren. Hij schenkt de overwinning aan wie het Hem behaagt door de kracht van Zijn bevel. Hij is in waarheid de Krachtige, de Almachtige.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH05801 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh05801/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh05801/en/</guid>
      <description>In His Name, the Exalted, the All-Highest, the Most Sublime!
Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! O Thou Who art my God, and my Master, and my Lord, and my Support, and my Hope, and my Refuge, and my Light. I ask of Thee, by Thy Hidden and Treasured Name, that none knoweth save Thine own Self, to protect the bearer of this Tablet from every calamity and pestilence, and from every wicked man and woman; from the evil of the evil-doers, and from the scheming of the unbelievers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH05801 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh05801/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh05801/es/</guid>
      <description>¡En Su Nombre, el Exaltado, el Altísimo, el Sublime! ¡Glorificado eres, oh Señor, mi Dios! ¡Oh Tú que eres mi Dios y mi Amo, y mi Señor, y mi Apoyo, y mi Esperanza, y mi Refugio, y mi Luz! Te pido, por Tu Nombre Oculto y Atesorado que nadie conoce sino Tu propio Ser, que protejas al portador de esta Tabla de toda calamidad y pestilencia, de toda persona malvada, del daño de los malhechores y de las intrigas de los descreídos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07113 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh07113/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh07113/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise be to Thee, O Lord my God! Thou seest and knowest that I have called upon Thy servants to turn nowhere except in the direction of Thy bestowals, and have bidden them observe naught save the things Thou didst prescribe in Thy Perspicuous Book, the Book which hath been sent down according to Thine inscrutable decree and irrevocable purpose. I can utter no word, O my God, unless I be permitted by Thee, and can move in no direction until I obtain Thy sanction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH09872 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh09872/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh09872/en/</guid>
      <description>Praised be Thou, O Lord my God! This is Thy servant who hath quaffed from the hands of Thy grace the wine of Thy tender mercy, and tasted of the savor of Thy love in Thy days. I beseech Thee, by the embodiments of Thy names whom no grief can hinder from rejoicing in Thy love or from gazing on Thy face, and whom all the hosts of the heedless are powerless to cause to turn aside from the path of Thy pleasure, to supply him with the good things Thou dost possess, and to raise him up to such heights that he will regard the world even as a shadow that vanisheth swifter than the twinkling of an eye.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10578 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/en/</guid>
      <description>Lauded be Thy name, O Lord my God! I entreat Thee by Thy Name through which the Hour hath struck, and the Resurrection came to pass, and fear and trembling seized all that are in heaven and all that are on earth, to rain down, out of the heaven of Thy mercy and the clouds of Thy tender compassion, what will gladden the hearts of Thy servants, who have turned towards Thee and helped Thy Cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10578 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Alabado sea Tu Nombre, oh Señor mi Dios! Te suplico, por Tu Nombre, mediante el cual ha sonado la Hora, la Resurrección ha tenido lugar y el miedo y el estremecimiento se han apoderado de todos los que están en el cielo y en la tierra, que hagas llover del cielo de Tu misericordia y de las nubes de Tu tierna compasión aquello que alegre los corazones de Tus siervos, que se han vuelto hacia Ti y han ayudado a Tu Causa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10578 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/eo/</guid>
      <description>Laŭdata estu Via nomo, ho Eternulo mia Dio! Mi petegas Vin je Via Nomo, per kiu eksonis la Horo kaj venis la Releviĝo, kaj kaptis timo kaj tremo ĉiujn, kiuj estas en la ĉielo kaj sur la tero, pluvigu el la firmamento de Via mizerikordo kaj el la nuboj de Via tenera kompatemo tion, kio ĝojigos la korojn de Viaj servantoj, kiuj turnis sin al Vi kaj helpis Vian Aferon. Protektu Viajn geservantojn, ho mia Eternulo, kontraŭ la sagoj de vantaj kapricoj kaj vanaj imagoj, kaj donu al ili, el la manoj de Via graco, trinkon de la milde fluanta akvo de Via kono.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10578 in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/it/</guid>
      <description>Lodato sia il Tuo Nome, o Signore mio Dio! Ti supplico per il Tuo Nome per mezzo del quale l’Ora è scoccata e la Resurrezione è avvenuta, e timore e tremore hanno colto tutti coloro che sono in cielo e in terra, di far piovere dal cielo della Tua misericordia e dalle nubi della Tua tenera compassione, ciò che rallegrerà i cuori dei Tuoi servi che si sono volti verso di Te e hanno aiutato la Tua Causa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
