<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Nearness to God on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-nearness-to-god/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Nearness to God on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-nearness-to-god/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB02866 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab02866/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab02866/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord, my God and my Haven in my distress! My Shield and my Shelter in my woes! My Asylum and Refuge in time of need and in my loneliness my Companion! In my anguish my Solace, and in my solitude a loving Friend! The Remover of the pangs of my sorrows and the Pardoner of my sins! Wholly unto Thee do I turn, fervently imploring Thee with all my heart, my mind and my tongue, to shield me from all that runs counter to Thy will in this, the cycle of Thy divine unity, and to cleanse me of all defilement that will hinder me from seeking, stainless and unsullied, the shade of the tree of Thy grace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB06012 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab06012/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/ab06012/en/</guid>
      <description>He is the Compassionate, the All-Bountiful! O God, my God! Thou seest me, Thou knowest me; Thou art my Haven and my Refuge. None have I sought nor any will I seek save Thee; no path have I trodden nor any will I tread but the path of Thy love. In the darksome night of despair, my eye turneth expectant and full of hope to the morn of Thy boundless favor and at the hour of dawn my drooping soul is refreshed and strengthened in remembrance of Thy beauty and perfection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00018ANG in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bb00018ang/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bb00018ang/en/</guid>
      <description>O my God! There is no one but Thee to allay the anguish of my soul, and Thou art my highest aspiration, O my God. My heart is wedded to none save Thee and such as Thou dost love. I solemnly declare that my life and death are both for Thee. Verily Thou art incomparable and hast no partner. O my Lord! I beg Thee to forgive me for shutting myself out from Thee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00556 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bb00556/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bb00556/en/</guid>
      <description>Verily I am Thy servant, O my God, and Thy poor one and Thy suppliant and Thy wretched creature. I have arrived at Thy gate, seeking Thy shelter. I have found no contentment save in Thy love, no exultation except in Thy remembrance, no eagerness but in obedience to Thee, no joy save in Thy nearness, and no tranquillity except in reunion with Thee, notwithstanding that I am conscious that all created things are debarred from Thy sublime Essence and the entire creation is denied access to Thine inmost Being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BBU0015 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/bbu0015/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/bbu0015/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God, my Beloved, my heart&amp;rsquo;s Desire.
(Source category: Nearness to God) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 279)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08264 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bh08264/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/nearness-to-god/bh08264/en/</guid>
      <description>Glory be to Thee, O my God! Thou hearest Thine ardent lovers lamenting in their separation from Thee, and such as have recognized Thee wailing because of their remoteness from Thy presence. Open Thou outwardly to their faces, O my Lord, the gates of Thy grace, that they may enter them by Thy leave and in conformity with Thy will, and may stand before the throne of Thy majesty, and catch the accents of Thy voice, and be illumined with the splendors of the light of Thy face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn12487 in Samoan</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12487/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/sm/bpn12487/</guid>
      <description>O Lord, my God and my Heaven in my distress
Le Ali’i e, lo’u Atua ma lo’u fa’amalumaluga i o’u puapuagā! O lo’u Talitā ma lo’u Malu i a’u auega! O lo’u sulufa’iga ma le Lafitaga i le taimi o le tu’ulafoa’ina ma i lo’u to’atasi o lo’u Soātau! I o’u tigā o la’u Fa’amatalaloto, ma i lo’u to’atasi o se Uō alofa! O le Puluvaga i tigā o o’u fa’anoanoaga ma o le Fa’amagalo i a’u agasala!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13371 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13371/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13371/</guid>
      <description>O Dduw, fy Nuw, f’anwylyd, Dymuniad fy nghalon.
O God, my God, my Beloved, my heart&amp;rsquo;s Desire,
(Source category: Nearness to God) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 13371)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn13372 in Cymraeg</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13372/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/cy/bpn13372/</guid>
      <description>O Arglwydd, fy Nuw, a&amp;rsquo;m Noddfa yn fy mlinder! Fy Nharian a&amp;rsquo;m Cysgod yn fy nhrallod! Fy Ngobaith a&amp;rsquo;m Lloches yn nydd fy angen! Ti yw fy Niddanydd mewn dyddiau o wae, fy Nghydymaith yn y tywyllwch, a&amp;rsquo;m Cyfaill annwyl yn fy unigrwydd. Ti sydd yn symud ymaith poenau ein galar ac yn maddau ein pechodau
Atat Ti yn unig y gallaf agoshâu, gan erfyn â&amp;rsquo;m holl gallon, âm meddwl, ac â&amp;rsquo;m tafod, ar i Ti fy nghadw rhag pob peth sydd yn groes i&amp;rsquo;th Ewyllys Di, yn hwn, cylch Dy undod duwiol.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
