<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH10578 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh10578/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH10578 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh10578/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10578 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/en/</guid>
      <description>Lauded be Thy name, O Lord my God! I entreat Thee by Thy Name through which the Hour hath struck, and the Resurrection came to pass, and fear and trembling seized all that are in heaven and all that are on earth, to rain down, out of the heaven of Thy mercy and the clouds of Thy tender compassion, what will gladden the hearts of Thy servants, who have turned towards Thee and helped Thy Cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10578 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Alabado sea Tu Nombre, oh Señor mi Dios! Te suplico, por Tu Nombre, mediante el cual ha sonado la Hora, la Resurrección ha tenido lugar y el miedo y el estremecimiento se han apoderado de todos los que están en el cielo y en la tierra, que hagas llover del cielo de Tu misericordia y de las nubes de Tu tierna compasión aquello que alegre los corazones de Tus siervos, que se han vuelto hacia Ti y han ayudado a Tu Causa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10578 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/eo/</guid>
      <description>Laŭdata estu Via nomo, ho Eternulo mia Dio! Mi petegas Vin je Via Nomo, per kiu eksonis la Horo kaj venis la Releviĝo, kaj kaptis timo kaj tremo ĉiujn, kiuj estas en la ĉielo kaj sur la tero, pluvigu el la firmamento de Via mizerikordo kaj el la nuboj de Via tenera kompatemo tion, kio ĝojigos la korojn de Viaj servantoj, kiuj turnis sin al Vi kaj helpis Vian Aferon. Protektu Viajn geservantojn, ho mia Eternulo, kontraŭ la sagoj de vantaj kapricoj kaj vanaj imagoj, kaj donu al ili, el la manoj de Via graco, trinkon de la milde fluanta akvo de Via kono.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH10578 in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/protection/bh10578/it/</guid>
      <description>Lodato sia il Tuo Nome, o Signore mio Dio! Ti supplico per il Tuo Nome per mezzo del quale l’Ora è scoccata e la Resurrezione è avvenuta, e timore e tremore hanno colto tutti coloro che sono in cielo e in terra, di far piovere dal cielo della Tua misericordia e dalle nubi della Tua tenera compassione, ciò che rallegrerà i cuori dei Tuoi servi che si sono volti verso di Te e hanno aiutato la Tua Causa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
