<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH08822 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh08822/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH08822 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh08822/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08822 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/en/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! I beseech Thee by Him Who is Thy Most Great Name, Who hath been sorely afflicted by such of Thy creatures as have repudiated Thy truth, and Who hath been hemmed in by sorrows which no tongue can describe, to grant that I may remember Thee and celebrate Thy praise, in these days when all have turned away from Thy beauty, have disputed with Thee, and turned away disdainfully from Him Who is the Revealer of Thy Cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08822 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Glorificado eres, oh Señor mi Dios! Te imploro, por Aquel que es Tu Más Grande Nombre, Quien ha sido penosamente afligido por aquellas de Tus criaturas que han repudiado Tu verdad, y Quien ha estado rodeado de tales infortunios que ninguna lengua puede describir, que me permitas recordarte y celebrar Tu alabanza en estos días en que todos se han apartado de Tu belleza, han disputado contigo y se han alejado desdeñosamente de Aquel que es el Revelador de Tu Causa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08822 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/eo/</guid>
      <description>Glorata estu Vi, ho Eternulo mia Dio! Mi petegas Vin je Li, Kiu estas Via Plej Alta Nomo, Kiun amare afliktis tiuj el Viaj kreitoj, kiuj rifuzis Vian veron, kaj Kiu estis ĉirkaŭata de angoroj, kiajn neniu buŝo povus eldiri, permesu, ke mi memoru Vin kaj festu Vian laŭdon en ĉi tagoj, kiam ĉiuj sin turnis for de Via beleco, disputis kontraŭ Vi kaj senestime sin turnis for de Tiu, Kiu estas la Revelacianto de Via Kredo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08822 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/pt/</guid>
      <description>Glorificado és Tu, ó Senhor meu Deus! Suplico-Te, por Aquele que é Teu Nome Supremo, que foi severamente afligido por aquelas criaturas Tuas que repudiaram a Tua verdade - Aquele que foi assediado por tristezas que língua alguma pode descrever - permite que eu Te recorde e celebre o Teu louvor, nesses dias em que todos se afastaram da Tua beleza, duvidaram de Ti e, com desdém, voltaram as costas Àquele que é o Revelador da Tua Causa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
