<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH07426DRE on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh07426dre/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH07426DRE on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh07426dre/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07426DRE in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh07426dre/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh07426dre/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou, at Whose dreadful majesty all things have trembled, in Whose grasp are the affairs of all men, towards Whose grace and mercy are set the faces of all Thy creatures! I entreat Thee, by Thy Name which Thou hast ordained to be the spirit of all names that are in the kingdom of names, to shield us from the whisperings of those who have turned away from Thee, and have repudiated the truth of Thy most august and most exalted Self, in this Revelation that hath caused the kingdom of Thy names to tremble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07426DRE in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh07426dre/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/women/bh07426dre/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij, voor Wiens ontzaglijke majesteit alle dingen beven, in Wiens greep de aangelegenheden van alle mensen liggen, naar Wiens genade en barmhartigheid het gelaat van al Uw schepselen is gericht! Ik smeek U, bij Uw Naam die Gij hebt verordend tot de geest van alle namen die in het koninkrijk van namen bestaan, ons in deze Openbaring die het koninkrijk van Uw namen heeft doen beven af te schermen van de influisteringen van hen die zich van U hebben afgekeerd en de waarheid van Uw grootste en verhevenste Wezen hebben verworpen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
