<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>category-Steadfastness on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/category-steadfastness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in category-Steadfastness on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/category-steadfastness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001FIR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/en/</guid>
      <description>O Lord my God! Assist Thy loved ones to be firm in Thy Faith, to walk in Thy ways, to be steadfast in Thy Cause. Give them Thy grace to withstand the onslaught of self and passion, to follow the light of divine guidance. Thou art the Powerful, the Gracious, the Self-Subsisting, the Bestower, the Compassionate, the Almighty, the All-Bountiful.
(Source category: Steadfastness) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 319)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001FIR in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/eo/</guid>
      <description>Ho Eternulo, mia Dio! Asistu Viajn amatojn, por ke ili estu firmaj en Via Kredo, iru Viajn vojojn kaj estu persistemaj en Via Afero. Donu al ili Vian gracon por kontraŭstari la atakojn de egoismo kaj pasio kaj por sekvi la lumon de la ĉiela gvidado. Vi estas la Potenca, la Graca, la Mem-Ekzistanta, la Donacanto, la Kompatema, la Ĉio-pova, la Plej Malavara.
(Source category: Firmeco en la Interligo) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 4333)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001FIR in Italiano</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/it/</guid>
      <description>O Signore mio Dio! Assisti i Tuoi amati ad essere saldi nella Tua Fede, a camminare sulle Tue vie, ad essere costanti nella Tua Causa. Da’ loro la Tua grazia onde sopportino i furiosi assalti dell’egoismo e della passione, e seguano la luce della guida divina. Tu sei il Potente, il Benevolo, Colui Che Esiste da Sé, il Donatore, il Compassionevole, l’Onnipotente, il Generosissimo.
(Source category: Saldezza) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 7913)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001FIR in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Heer, mijn God! Help Uw geliefden sterk te staan in Uw Geloof, Uw wegen te bewandelen en standvastig te zijn in Uw Zaak. Geef hun Uw genade om de aanvallen van zelfzucht en hartstocht te weerstaan en het licht van goddelijke leiding te volgen. Gij zijt de Krachtige, de Genadige, de Bij-zich-bestaande, de Schenker, de Meedogende, de Almachtige, de Almilddadige.
(Source category: Standvastigheid) (Bahaiprayers.net ID: 9713)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00001FIR in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00001fir/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Senhor, meu Deus! Ajuda aqueles que Te amam a permanecerem firmes na Tua Fé, a prosseguirem nos Teus caminhos e serem constantes na Tua Causa. Dispensa-lhes a Tua graça, para que resistam às investidas do ego e da paixão e se guiem pela luz da guia divina. Tu és o Poderoso, o Benévolo, O que subsiste por Si próprio, o Magnânimo, o Compassivo, o Omnipotente, a Suprema Bondade.
(Source category: Firmeza e Constância) (Bahaiprayers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00687SEE in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00687see/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00687see/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou, my God, Who guidest the seeker to the pathway that leadeth aright, Who deliverest the lost and blinded soul out of the wastes of perdition, Thou Who bestowest upon the sincere great bounties and favors, Who guardest the frightened within Thine impregnable refuge, Who answerest, from Thine all-highest horizon, the cry of those who cry out unto Thee. Praised be Thou, O my Lord! Thou hast guided the distracted out of the death of unbelief, and hast brought those who draw nigh unto Thee to the journey&amp;rsquo;s goal, and hast rejoiced the assured among Thy servants by granting them their most cherished desires, and hast, from Thy Kingdom of beauty, opened before the faces of those who yearn after Thee the gates of reunion, and hast rescued them from the fires of deprivation and loss—so that they hastened unto Thee and gained Thy presence, and arrived at Thy welcoming door, and received of gifts an abundant share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00687SEE in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00687see/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/ab00687see/nl/</guid>
      <description>O Gij mijn God, die de zoeker naar het rechte pad leidt, die de verloren en verblinde zielen uit de woestenij van verderf bevrijdt, Gij die de oprechten grote gaven en gunsten schenkt, die de bevreesden beschermt in Uw onneembare toevluchtsoord, die vanuit Uw allerhoogste horizon de roep van hen die U aanroepen beantwoordt. Geprezen zijt Gij, o mijn Heer! Gij hebt de verwarden weggeleid van de dood van ongeloof, en hebt hen die U nabij zijn naar het doel van de reis gebracht, en hebt de onverschrokkenen onder Uw dienaren verblijd door hun dierbaarste wensen te vervullen, en hebt vanuit Uw Koninkrijk van schoonheid de poorten van hereniging geopend voor de ogen van hen die hevig naar U verlangen, en hen gered uit het vuur van ontbering en verlies – zodat zij zich naar U hebben gehaast en Uw tegenwoordigheid hebben bereikt, en bij Uw open deur zijn aangekomen en een overvloed aan geschenken hebben ontvangen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00554 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bb00554/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bb00554/en/</guid>
      <description>Praise be to Thee, O Lord, my Best Beloved! Make me steadfast in Thy Cause, and grant that I may be reckoned among those who have not violated Thy Covenant nor followed the gods of their own idle fancy. Enable me, then, to obtain a seat of truth in Thy presence, bestow upon me a token of Thy mercy and let me join with such of Thy servants as shall have no fear nor shall they be put to grief.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00554 in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bb00554/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bb00554/nl/</guid>
      <description>Ere zij U, o Heer, mijn Meestgeliefde! Maak mij standvastig in Uw Zaak en geef dat ik gerekend mag worden tot hen die Uw Verbond niet hebben geschonden, noch de goden van hun eigen ijdele verbeelding hebben gevolgd. Laat mij dan een zetel van waarheid verkrijgen in Uw tegenwoordigheid, verleen mij een teken van Uw erbarmen en laat mij aansluiten bij dezulken Uwer dienaren die geen vrees zullen kennen, noch door smart getroffen zullen worden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00621 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bb00621/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bb00621/en/</guid>
      <description>Praised and glorified art Thou, O God! Grant that the day of attaining Thy holy presence may be fast approaching. Cheer our hearts through the potency of Thy love and good-pleasure, and bestow upon us steadfastness that we may willingly submit to Thy Will and Thy Decree. Verily, Thy knowledge embraceth all the things Thou hast created or wilt create, and Thy celestial might transcendeth whatsoever Thou hast called or wilt call into being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BB00621 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bb00621/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bb00621/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Alabado y glorificado eres Tú, oh Dios! Haz que se aproxime rápidamente el día de la llegada a Tu santa presencia. Alegra nuestros corazones mediante la fuerza de Tu amor y Tu complacencia, y concédenos firmeza para que nos sometamos gustosos a Tu Voluntad y Tu Decreto. Verdaderamente, Tu conocimiento abarca todas las cosas que has creado o hayas de crear, y Tu poder celestial trasciende todo cuanto has traído o hayas de traer a la existencia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH00053MAG in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh00053mag/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh00053mag/en/</guid>
      <description>I magnify Thy Name, O my God, and offer thanksgiving unto Thee, O my Desire, inasmuch as Thou hast enabled me to clearly perceive Thy straight Path, hast unveiled Thy Great Announcement before mine eyes and hast aided me to set my face towards the Dayspring of Thy Revelation and the Fountainhead of Thy Cause, whilst Thy servants and Thy people turned away from Thee. I entreat Thee, O Lord of the Kingdom of eternity, by the shrill voice of the Pen of Glory, and by the Burning Fire which calleth aloud from the verdant Tree, and by the Ark which Thou hast specially chosen for the people of Bahá, to grant that I may remain steadfast in my love for Thee, be well pleased with whatsoever Thou hast prescribed for me in Thy Book and may stand firm in Thy service and in the service of Thy loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH07775 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh07775/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh07775/en/</guid>
      <description>O God, my God! I have turned in repentance unto Thee, and verily Thou art the Pardoner, the Compassionate. O God, my God! I have returned to Thee, and verily Thou art the the Ever-Forgiving, the Gracious. O God, my God! I have clung to the cord of Thy bounty, and with Thee is the storehouse of all that is in heaven and earth. O God, my God! I have hastened toward Thee, and verily Thou art the Forgiver, the Lord of grace abounding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08244 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08244/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08244/en/</guid>
      <description>Glorified be Thy name, O Lord my God! I beseech Thee by Thy power that hath encompassed all created things, and by Thy Sovereignty that hath transcended the entire creation, and by Thy Word which was hidden in Thy wisdom and whereby Thou didst create Thy heaven and Thy earth, both to enable us to be steadfast in our love for Thee and in our obedience to Thy pleasure, and to fix our gaze upon Thy face, and celebrate Thy glory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08244 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08244/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08244/eo/</guid>
      <description>Glorata estu Via Nomo, ho Eternulo, mia Dio! Mi petegas Vin je Via potenco, kiu ĉirkaŭas ĉiujn kreitaĵojn, kaj je Via suvereneco, kiu superas la tutan universon, kaj je Via Vorto, Kiu estas kaŝita pro Via saĝeco kaj per Kiu Vi kreis la ĉielon kaj la teron, ke Vi ebligu al ni esti konstantaj en nia amo al Vi kaj en nia obeado al Via volo, kaj ke ni fiksu nian rigardon al Via Vizaĝo kaj atestu Vian gloron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08604 in Afrikaans</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08604/af/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08604/af/</guid>
      <description>O U Wie se nabyheid my wens is, Wie se teenwoordigheid my hoop is, Wie se aandenking my begeerte is, Wie se gloriehof my doel is, Wie se woonplek my strewe is, Wie se naam my genesing is, Wie se liefde die glans van my hart is, Wie sie diens my hoogste strewe is! Ek smeek U by U Naam, waardeur U diegene wat U herken het in staat gestel om na die verhewenste hoogtes van die kennis van U te sweef en dié wat U toegewyd aanbid in staat gestel het om op te styg na die omgewing van die voorhof van U heilige gunste, om my te help om my gesig na U gesig te wend, om my oë op U te rig, en om van U heerlikheid te praat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08604 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08604/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08604/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou Whose nearness is my wish, Whose presence is my hope, Whose remembrance is my desire, Whose court of glory is my goal, Whose abode is my aim, Whose name is my healing, Whose love is the radiance of my heart, Whose service is my highest aspiration! I beseech Thee by Thy Name, through which Thou hast enabled them that have recognized Thee to soar to the sublimest heights of the knowledge of Thee and empowered such as devoutly worship Thee to ascend into the precincts of the court of Thy holy favors, to aid me to turn my face towards Thy face, to fix mine eyes upon Thee, and to speak of Thy glory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08822 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/en/</guid>
      <description>Glorified art Thou, O Lord my God! I beseech Thee by Him Who is Thy Most Great Name, Who hath been sorely afflicted by such of Thy creatures as have repudiated Thy truth, and Who hath been hemmed in by sorrows which no tongue can describe, to grant that I may remember Thee and celebrate Thy praise, in these days when all have turned away from Thy beauty, have disputed with Thee, and turned away disdainfully from Him Who is the Revealer of Thy Cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08822 in Español</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/es/</guid>
      <description>¡Glorificado eres, oh Señor mi Dios! Te imploro, por Aquel que es Tu Más Grande Nombre, Quien ha sido penosamente afligido por aquellas de Tus criaturas que han repudiado Tu verdad, y Quien ha estado rodeado de tales infortunios que ninguna lengua puede describir, que me permitas recordarte y celebrar Tu alabanza en estos días en que todos se han apartado de Tu belleza, han disputado contigo y se han alejado desdeñosamente de Aquel que es el Revelador de Tu Causa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08822 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/eo/</guid>
      <description>Glorata estu Vi, ho Eternulo mia Dio! Mi petegas Vin je Li, Kiu estas Via Plej Alta Nomo, Kiun amare afliktis tiuj el Viaj kreitoj, kiuj rifuzis Vian veron, kaj Kiu estis ĉirkaŭata de angoroj, kiajn neniu buŝo povus eldiri, permesu, ke mi memoru Vin kaj festu Vian laŭdon en ĉi tagoj, kiam ĉiuj sin turnis for de Via beleco, disputis kontraŭ Vi kaj senestime sin turnis for de Tiu, Kiu estas la Revelacianto de Via Kredo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08822 in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/steadfastness/bh08822/pt/</guid>
      <description>Glorificado és Tu, ó Senhor meu Deus! Suplico-Te, por Aquele que é Teu Nome Supremo, que foi severamente afligido por aquelas criaturas Tuas que repudiaram a Tua verdade - Aquele que foi assediado por tristezas que língua alguma pode descrever - permite que eu Te recorde e celebre o Teu louvor, nesses dias em que todos se afastaram da Tua beleza, duvidaram de Ti e, com desdém, voltaram as costas Àquele que é o Revelador da Tua Causa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
