<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH08433 on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh08433/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH08433 on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh08433/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08433 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/en/</guid>
      <description>Magnified be Thy name, O my God, for that Thou hast manifested the Day which is the King of Days, the Day which Thou didst announce unto Thy chosen Ones and Thy Prophets in Thy most excellent Tablets, the Day whereon Thou didst shed the splendor of the glory of all Thy names upon all created things. Great is his blessedness whosoever hath set himself towards Thee, and entered Thy presence, and caught the accents of Thy voice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08433 in Esperanto</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/eo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/eo/</guid>
      <description>Laŭdegata estu Via nomo, ho mia Dio, ĉar Vi manifestis tiun Tagon, kiu estas la Reĝo de la Tagoj, la Tagon, kiun Vi anoncis al Viaj Elektitoj kaj Viaj Profetoj en Viaj plej elstaraj Epistoloj, la Tagon, en kiu Vi elverŝis la lumon de la gloro de ĉiuj Viaj nomoj super la tuta kreitaro. Granda estas la beniteco de ĉiu ajn, kiu direktis sin al Vi kaj eniris Vian ĉeeston kaj kaptis la sonojn de Via voĉo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH08433 in Français</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/teaching/bh08433/fr/</guid>
      <description>Magnifié soit ton nom, ô mon Dieu, car tu as révélé le jour qui est le roi des jours, le jour annoncé à tes élus et à tes prophètes dans tes épîtres les plus merveilleuses, le jour où tu as répandu la splendeur de la gloire de tous tes noms sur toutes choses créées. Béni celui qui avance vers toi, parvient en ta présence et perçoit les intonations de ta voix.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
