<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-Ascension of Bahá’u’lláh on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-ascension-of-bah%C3%A1ull%C3%A1h/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-Ascension of Bahá’u’lláh on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-ascension-of-bah%C3%A1ull%C3%A1h/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8257 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8257/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8257/</guid>
      <description>#Súriy-i-Ghusn ##Tablet of the Branch
He it is Who abideth forever in the Realm of Glory.
The Cause of God hath come down upon the clouds of utterance, while they that have joined partners with Him are afflicted with a sore torment. The hosts of Divine Revelation, bearing the banners of celestial inspiration, have descended from the heaven of His Tablet in the name of God, the Almighty, the Most Powerful, and the faithful rejoice in His victory and dominion, while the deniers are filled with dismay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8258 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8258/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8258/</guid>
      <description>#Lawh-i-Rasúl ##Tablet to Rasúl
Verily, I am the One Who abideth disconsolate beneath the canopy of this world.
O Rasúl! Shouldst thou ask concerning the Sun of the heaven of inner meaning, know that it hath been eclipsed by the clouds of envy; and shouldst thou enquire regarding the Moon of the realm of everlasting holiness, be apprised that it hath been obscured by the shrouds of hatred; and shouldst thou search after the Star of the firmament of unseen reality, be informed that it hath sunk below the horizon of malice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8259 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8259/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8259/</guid>
      <description>#Lawh-i-Maryam ##Tablet to Maryam
Sorrowful is He at My sorrows.
O Maryam! The wrongs which I suffer have blotted out the wrongs suffered by My First Name[22] from the Tablet of creation. The clouds of divine decree have at every moment rained down upon this manifest Beauty the showers of tribulation. My banishment from My homeland was for the sake of none but the Beloved; My exile was in no other path save that of His good-pleasure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn8260 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8260/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn8260/</guid>
      <description>#Kitáb-i-‘Ahd ##Book of the Covenant
Although the Realm of Glory hath none of the vanities of the world, yet within the treasury of trust and resignation We have bequeathed to Our heirs an excellent and priceless Heritage. Earthly treasures We have not bequeathed, nor have We added such cares as they entail. By God! In earthly riches fear is hidden and peril is concealed. Consider ye and call to mind that which the All-Merciful hath revealed in the Qur’án: “Woe betide every slanderer and defamer, him that layeth up riches and counteth them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
