<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cat-America on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-america/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cat-America on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/cat-america/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00032DAR in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/america/ab00032dar/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/america/ab00032dar/en/</guid>
      <description>##Revealed to the Bahá’ís of the United States and Canada
O God, my God! Thou seest how black darkness is enshrouding all regions, how all countries are burning with the flame of dissension, and the fire of war and carnage is blazing throughout the East and the West. Blood is flowing, corpses bestrew the ground, and severed heads are fallen on the dust of the battlefield. O Lord! Have pity on these ignorant ones, and look upon them with the eye of forgiveness and pardon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00963IMP in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/america/ab00963imp/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/america/ab00963imp/en/</guid>
      <description>#Mother Temple of the West O God, my God! I implore Thee with a throbbing heart and streaming tears to aid whosoever expendeth his energy for the erection of this House, and the construction of this Building wherein Thy name is mentioned every morn and every eve.
O God! Send down Thy divine increase on whosoever endeavoreth to serve this edifice and exerteth himself to raise it amongst the kindreds and religions of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB08704NEW in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/america/ab08704new/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/america/ab08704new/en/</guid>
      <description>Bless Thou, O King of Kings, the city of New York! Cause the friends there to be kind to one another. Purify their souls and make their hearts to be free and detached. Illumine the world of their consciousness. Exhilarate their spirits and bestow celestial power and confirmation upon them. Establish there a heavenly realm, so that the City of Baha may prosper and New York be favoured with blessings from the Abha Kingdom, that this region may become like the all-highest Paradise, may develop into a vineyard of God and be transformed into a heavenly orchard and a spiritual rose garden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer ABU0394GAT in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/america/abu0394gat/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/america/abu0394gat/en/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind Lord! This gathering is turning to Thee. These hearts are radiant with Thy love. These minds and spirits are exhilarated by the message of Thy glad-tidings. O God! Let this American democracy become glorious in spiritual degrees even as it has aspired to material degrees, and render this just government victorious. Confirm this revered nation to upraise the standard of the oneness of humanity, to promulgate the Most Great Peace, to become thereby most glorious and praiseworthy among all the nations of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn10519 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10519/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn10519/</guid>
      <description>O Thou kind God!
From America, that distant country, we hastened to the Holy Land and directed our steps toward this blessed Spot. We attained unto the two blessed and sacred Thresholds and obtained boundless grace therefrom. We have now come to Mount Carmel, which is Thy sacred garden. Most of the Prophets turned to Thee in prayer upon this holy mountain, communing with Thee in the utmost humility at the midnight hour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer bpn11699 in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn11699/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/unsorted/en/bpn11699/</guid>
      <description>O my God! O Thou Who endowest every just power and equitable dominion with abiding glory and everlasting might, with permanence and stability, with constancy and honour! Aid Thou by Thy heavenly grace every government that acteth justly towards its subjects and every sovereign authority, derived from Thee, that shieldeth the poor and the weak under the banner of its protection.
I beseech Thee, by Thy divine grace and surpassing bounty, to aid this just government, the canopy of whose authority is spread over vast and mighty lands and the evidences of whose justice are apparent in its prosperous and flourishing regions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
