<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-BH01554HUQ on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh01554huq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-BH01554HUQ on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-bh01554huq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01554HUQ in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/huq%C3%BAqull%C3%A1h/bh01554huq/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/huq%C3%BAqull%C3%A1h/bh01554huq/en/</guid>
      <description>Magnified art Thou, O Lord of the entire creation, the One unto Whom all things must turn. With my inner and outer tongues I bear witness that thou hast manifested and revealed Thyself, sent down Thy signs, and proclaimed Thy testimonies. I testify to Thy self-sufficiency from aught else except Thee, and Thy sanctity above all earthly things. I entreat Thee by the transcendent glory of Thy Cause and the supreme potency of Thy Word to grant confirmation unto him who desireth to offer what Thou hast prescribed unto him in Thy Book and to observe that which will shed forth the fragrance of Thine acceptance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01554HUQ in Nederlands</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/huq%C3%BAqull%C3%A1h/bh01554huq/nl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/huq%C3%BAqull%C3%A1h/bh01554huq/nl/</guid>
      <description>*Ḥuqúqu&amp;rsquo;lláh is waarlijk een grootse wet. Iedereen is verplicht dit offer te brengen omdat dit een bron is van genade, van overvloed en van al het goede. Het is een milddadigheid die bij iedere ziel zal blijven in elke wereld van de werelden van God, de Albezittende, de Almilddadige. Bahá&amp;rsquo;u&amp;rsquo;lláh
Verheerlijkt zijt Gij, o Heer van de gehele schepping, Degeen tot Wie alle dingen zich moeten wenden. Ik getuig van binnen en hardop dat Gij Uzelf kenbaar hebt gemaakt en hebt geopenbaard, Uw tekenen hebt neergezonden en Uw getuigenissen hebt verkondigd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer BH01554HUQ in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/huq%C3%BAqull%C3%A1h/bh01554huq/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/huq%C3%BAqull%C3%A1h/bh01554huq/pt/</guid>
      <description>Magnificado és Tu, ó Senhor da criação inteira, Aquele a Quem todas as coisas devem volver-se. Com a minha língua interior e exterior dou testemunho de que Tu Te tens manifestado e revelado, mandado descer os Teus sinais e proclamado as Tuas provas. Atesto a Tua auto-suficiência de tudo salvo de Ti e a Tua Santidade acima de todas as coisas terrenas. Suplico-Te, pela transcendente glória da Tua Causa e pela suprema potência da Tua Palavra, que concedas confirmação àquele que desejar ofertar aquilo que Tu lhe prescreveste no Teu Livro e que observe aquilo que difundirá a fragrância da Tua aceitação.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
