<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prayer-AB00388COM on devotional.gq</title>
    <link>https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00388com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prayer-AB00388COM on devotional.gq</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://devotional.gq/tags/prayer-ab00388com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00388COM in English</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/ab00388com/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/ab00388com/en/</guid>
      <description>O Divine Providence! This assemblage is composed of Thy friends who are attracted to Thy beauty and are set ablaze by the fire of Thy love. Turn these souls into heavenly angels, resuscitate them through the breath of Thy Holy Spirit, grant them eloquent tongues and resolute hearts, bestow upon them heavenly power and merciful susceptibilities, cause them to become the promulgators of the oneness of mankind and the cause of love and concord in the world of humanity, so that the perilous darkness of ignorant prejudice may vanish through the light of the Sun of Truth, this dreary world may become illumined, this material realm may absorb the rays of the world of spirit, these different colors may merge into one color and the melody of praise may rise to the kingdom of Thy sanctity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prayer AB00388COM in Português (BR)</title>
      <link>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/ab00388com/pt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devotional.gq/prayer/gatherings/ab00388com/pt/</guid>
      <description>Ó Divina Providência! Essa congregação é formada pelos Teus amigos, atraídos à Tua beleza e inflamados com o fogo do Teu amor. Transforma essas almas em anjos celestiais, ressuscita-as através dos sopros do Teu Espírito Santo, concede-lhes línguas eloquentes e corações resolutos, dota-as de poder celestial e de susceptibilidades misericordiosas, faze com que sejam promotoras da unidade do género humano e a causa de amor e concórdia no mundo humano, para que assim as perigosas trevas do preconceito ignorante se desvaneçam ante a luz do Sol da Verdade, e este mundo sombrio se ilumine, e este reino material possa absorver os raios do mundo do espírito, e essas cores diferentes possam fundir-se numa só cor, e a melodia do louvor possa elevar-se ao reino de Tua santidade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
